The lyrics are SO good
Teishotoku P!!
I like this way too much
It's good...
I'm listening to it again today
Teishotoku P's new song is totally the best!
Ow!
I was enjoying a moment of supreme bliss!
What the hell are you doing?!
So, can I say something amazing right now?
No, you can't!
The thing is, it's occurred to me.
Wh-what has?
It's about the first person who ever wore underwear.
WHY do you think that person decided to wear them?
What?!
Uh... What's your point?
At some point, that person looked at
the next guy over and realized:
Keep Back
Danger
"Huh. When you look closely,
this guy's junk is on full display."
"And that's just no good."
No way! Are you serious?!
Hey, what the heck?
I didn't forget to put them on.
Don't scare me like that!
No, not THAT underwear..
What I'm talking about is underwear of the heart.
Oh, jeez. "Underwear of the heart," huh?
Wait, what? What does that even mean?!
You were on full display and very much leaking.
Note: "Leaking" as in her music was audible
What was? Hey, what was?!
What was on display?! Wait up!
Wait right there! TELL ME!
Yo
Mic check
JK (High school girl)
Huh?
Yeah!
Isn't that usually where one-two is best?
The moon is a quiet beast during the daytime
What about the moon? That was sudden
Once it becomes night, under cover of darkness
You're so dazzling, wallflower
Want to be like you, lunatic girls
Want to jump on that bandwagon, dazzling JK
The present state of
Always lazing around is okay!
Everything in your mind...
Emptying all that will make you efficient
Is that so? You know?
Animal instinct (Meow!)
A word to society, a maiden's roar
Ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Innovative shout
Ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
So, there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
So, "dass" is German, huh?
Background music that makes you want to
eat curry so hot that you cry!
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather 'round
Mic check JK, one-two, JK, one-two
Anything's okay, everyday
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Sushi, ramen, gyudon, tonkatsu, kishimen
Background music that makes you want to eat anything
Don't ever begrudge individuality
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather 'round!
Surprise it, toward an unlooked direction
Even if it's pointless let's go, a treasure before long
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you want to cry...
Wholeheartedly cry and cry, it's gratifying
Every day feels refreshing
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Even if you don't want to you'll cheer up
for sure, and yeah, you'll smile
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
Yamai
Humans are such foolish creatures.
They seek not to take pride in themselves.
Hence, they are quickly blinded by greed.
Yamamoto.
We need to talk.
You intend to spirit me away?
That's right.
Interesting. Feel free to try, but I shall not yield.
I'll give you a sweet bun and it'll be our secret.
Let's go.
Career Guidance Room
Yamamoto...
You're wearing even more bandages than usual.
It appears that you've seriously injured.
What happened?
Fear not. This is but a trifle.
No. As a teacher, I can't just turn a blind eye.
Either take off those bandages
and show me your condition
or you get taken to the hospital right now.
The choice is your-
Wait! This...!
The skin-to-filling ratio of this sweet bun is just OFF!
That's because it's the thin-skinned variety.
That's hardly worth interrupting someone
in mid-conversation, though.
Oh, jeez. You want to know my secret that badly?
Well, fine.
After all, I am indebted to you for this tasty treat...
Putting aside the other points you should feel
indebted to me for, did you like it that much?
That I did.
Very well. I will make an exception and show you.
My left arm bears that
which was carved into me
by a hallway collision with a boy in my
second year of elementary school:
The Black Pain!
Pencil
Black
Lead
Pain
Uh... Oh. And?
Wh-what?! You amateur!
Can you not see how perilous this wound is?
If the lead had gone any deeper into my veins,
it could have reached my heart and
may very well have killed me!
I see.
So, would you mind showing me
what's under those other bandages?
You're a rather impertinent man, aren't you?
What is that?
An acquired heat rash!
An "acquired"...
Um, heat rashes generally aren't hereditary.
You just wanted to say that, didn't you?
Th-those are heat rashes too, aren't they?!
I put these bandages on thinking they'd
look cool, but this was the result.
And it's very itchy.
It would seem the bandages are clearly to blame.
You may be right.
You may be right, and yet...!
Right now, we're not discussing whether it was
the bandages or the rashes that came first, are we?!
Don't suddenly shift into high gear
when your teacher isn't even on board yet.
All this was merely a preview.
There will be no room for regret
once you've seen my wrist.
Your wrist? Don't tell me you...
I drew this yesterday, but I messed it all up.
You never fail to disappoint, do you?
I was trying to draw a cool-looking coat of arms,
but more and more it started to look
like out-of-control arm hair,
so I had to shift gears and draw a watch instead.
I see.
So, if you will allow me this question as well:
Why do you always have a bandage on your cheek?
Make no mistake.
This is no bandage. It serves as a mystic seal.
It is to contain the evil spirit that lies within me,
with its magic forming a powerful barrier.
Ah, so that one's spiritual in nature. Understood.
Should this be removed, even I would be unable to...
I say this for your own good:
You seem to have unusually sensitive skin,
so please avoid using bandages for the time being.
That is not possible.
These, you see, are my
"standard specifications," my identity,
and while the layperson may see them
as mere heat rashes,
You yourself just called them heat rashes.
rather, they are a stigmata
that shows I am of the Dragon race.
And as proof of that...
When I awoke one night...
B-blood?!
In various spots, the blood ran freely...
Because you scratched them! That was you!
In any case, that just leaves
the bandage on your forehead...
I can't!
That is the one thing I can't show!
My pride won't allow it!
I believe there's still one of those buns left.
What?!
Please, no matter what... don't tell anyone about this!
So your pride is worth less than 100 yen.
The truth is, I never wanted to show this to anyone...
You. Must. Be. Joking.
After all that, it's just pimples?
Okay, no more!
Yamamoto...
Getting these because I've been eating
too many sweets is incredibly uncool!
Yamamoto...
Getting these because I've been eating
too many sweets is incredibly uncool!
I have half a mind to start charging you
to pay for these glasses.
And don't eat that bun!
I told you, didn't I?
It's not a big deal.
Thanks for the food!
You just don't get it, Yamamoto.
You're far more ill than you think...
What was I...? I can't remember.
My head is-!
Hey! You may have the day off,
but how long do you plan to sleep in?!
Hurry and eat up your breakfast!
This is the food of the human world, is it?
It's like pig slop.
The problem of suicide among children
due to bullying is continuing to worsen.
It's like pig slop.
The problem of suicide among children
due to bullying is continuing to worsen.
In every era,
According to a study by MEXT,
school-related bullying is actually...
humans remain weak and foolish creatures.
This is a surprise.
Rinachi here. ♥
I'm bored, so if this gets 30 retweets,
I'll show my face.
50 retweets, and I'll post a pic
of my boyfriend and me. ♥
That species known as "attention seekers,"
those who would die if not always
in the spotlight, has managed to survive.
What's this?
It's going completely "viral."
I'm sure it won't be that popular, though.
Black Rabbit (Kuroto) @kurousagi
I'm bored, so if this gets 30 retweets,  I'll show my face.
50 retweets, and I'll post a pic of my boyfriend and me. ♥
This lot...
Normally, they tend not to come together,
but in cases such as these they display
a frightening level of solidarity.
I'm going to pretend I didn't see this.
It's a stuffed Giant Isopod Girl doll!
I want it. I want it! I totally want it!
200 yen
1 try
500 yen
3 tries
0 tries left
I'll get this in one try!
Yes! It's grabbing on tight!
S-seriously?
No...
There must be some way to best this thing!
I've been left with no choice.
O Other Me that lies dormant within...
Awaken!
Other Me... You're so weak!
Eek! What is this?!
I like it! I want it! Get it for me!
Huh? THIS is what you want?
C'mon, please!
Plebeians! I had slowly been
bending that machine to my will, yet...
Wait a minute. If I let them have a few tries,
this device will be nice and warmed up,
and that's when I will strike!
I'm sensing unbridled malevolence
coming from behind us...
Loathsome hyenas.
Whatever you do, do not make eye contact.
Yours shall become my blood, my flesh!
You'll be cursed.
I'm so happy. Thank you!
It was pretty easy to get.
Okay, I'm putting in a new prize.
Is that... a zashiki-warashi?
Note: A mischievous house spirit that can bring good fortune
That girl's been here for a while now.
Maybe I should help her out a bit.
Barring anything unusual,
she should be able to get this.
Good luck, zashiki-warashi girl.
All right! I'll get it this time for sure!
Yes! I caught it!
That was unusual!
Oh, that thing's trending right now!
C'mon, get it for me.
I'm not sure if that girl's finished, though...
It'll be fine, right? She's just, like, standing there.
Excuse me. We're not done yet.
Whoa, that guy is super hot!
Majime? What are you doing here?
Um, are you busy? Do you want to go on a date?
I was just passing by.
Anyway, do you want that stuffed animal?
Yumi-chan! I'm standing right here, you know.
I-I-I wouldn't say I want it, but...
Huh? Are we even a couple?
Wait, you mean we aren't?!
You do want it, don't you?
The thing is, Maa-kun...
Understood.
This won't take long.
Standard tactics could prove difficult...
It's not possible! I tried again and again,
I think it would be best to focus on the rotation axis.
but it barely moved, and that arm has no grip!
From here, perhaps.
That's awesome!
I retrieved it. Here you are.
Huh? But you got it, so it should be yours.
Sadly, collecting stuffed animals
is not a hobby of mine. Farewell.
W-wait!
What about the money? I'll give you 200 yen!
Must be nice! I want a boyfriend like that.
Yumi-chan!
M-Majime!
U-um...
Would you like to t-take a photo together?
As a reminder of when you got this for me.
I got 50 retweets, so here's that pic
of me and my boyfriend. ♥
Kuroto-san, your boyfriend is handsome!
I'm jealous!
Kuroto-san, you're cute too!
Seriously handsome couple
Where did you two meet?
Being in the spotlight sure is a rush!
The species known as
"Attention Seekers"
Yamamoto-san is...
so very easy to understand.
I got him
Yup!
"Mericar"?
Yup. It's an app that lets you buy clothes or bags,
stuff that people don't need anymore.
Say, why don't you try selling
some things that you don't need?
That I don't need?
There are some items I no longer
require for my compounds.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I guess you don't have anything after all...
I-I do! I'll go look for some now!
You don't have to force yourself to find something!
Here. These!
Whoa. It's like random stuff you'd find
washed up on the beach...
A gas mask?
But why? Seriously, this is pretty creepy.
Still, collectors might go for this sort of thing!
With this colored contact, I shall have
the mismatched eyes I've always wanted!
GO!
What the hell? Get in already!
Vile eyelid! Begone!
Enough! Keep it down already!
My "Mismatched Eye" plan is a no-go.
Is there some other, fearsome item
I can use instead?
This is one freakishly cool item!
Type 97 Gas Mask (original)
What's more, the price is right!
Luck is on my side!
Hey, Yamai.
That's one scary eye!
What happened? You've got, like, mismatched eyes!
Huh?
Um, well...
Just when did you realize my eyes are mismatched?
Enough of that. Just hurry up
and get to the nurse's office!
Nurse's Office
Okay, this should do the trick.
An eyepatch! This is so cool!
It looks like your eye got infected.
It shouldn't take long to heal.
That being said...
You've been covered in bandages since
the entrance ceremony, haven't you?
Did something happen to you?
I could tell you, but if I did that, Sensei, then-
Just call me "Shiikyon." Everyobody else does.
Then, Shiikyon, your life could be at risk.
Oh, my. I'm perfectly fine with that.
Should it come down to it,
I can perform first aid on myself.
I see. Well then, if you insist.
...And so, I was wounded while trying to rescue
that half-Demon, half-Human child.
My enemy was a fearsome one,
but just when I thought I was done for,
the crest on my arm began to shine.
Incidentally, I'm a half-blood of the
peoples of Altania and the Dragon race,
but up until that point, my Dragon powers
had yet to awaken, and so...
Yamamoto-san, I don't mind speaking with you,
but you should be getting back to class now.
No! I haven't even told you about the
global war against the Demon race yet!
And you can feel free to tell me anytime.
I want to tell you now! Just a little longer!
Yamamoto-san, I really didn't
want to admit this, but...
The truth is, I have one too: a crest on my arm.
I was quite shocked.
To think, someone at this school knows
the truth about us, the Demon race!
It can't be! Shiikyon, you're a...?
But the Demon race was sealed within the Crystal.
They should all still be dormant.
Huh? They are?
Removing the seal is said to require
the seed of Yggdrasil!
Yes, that's right. Our kind was indeed imprisoned,
but a handful of the Demon race,
those who were righteous and
pure of heart, awakened
and - like me - have lived quietly in the human world.
So I'm asking you, Yamamoto-san:
please leave us in peace.
Well, there's the bell. I guess I'll head back to class.
It seems whatever bacteria got into my eye
has entered my ears as well.
If that were true, that would be bad...
So, you can relax.
I didn't hear a word of what you said.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
See you, Shiikyon!
I can't believe she left so obligingly...
That burn I got grilling meat yesterday
sure came in handy!
In any case, what a delightfully pure-hearted girl.
I see. So that was Shiikyon's secret...
I'll visit the nurse's office again to ask her more.
Delivery.
Thanks very much
for your purchase!
Sure enough, this thing is super cool!
BLAM!
Let go! It would be dangerous to continue this!
Should this mask be removed, it will release
Wh-what was that just now?
a power great enough to destroy the world!
Beats me. But I do know it would be
pointless to think too much about it.
a power great enough to destroy the world!
Beats me. But I do know it would be
pointless to think too much about it.
The prelude to the beginning of the end shall-
Beats me. But I do know it would be
pointless to think too much about it.
Enough. You're coming with me.
Your voice is so muffled that I can't understand you!
Take this off!
Whoa! Give it back!
Don't bring such useless things to school.
I'm confiscating it!
Curses! I guess this is the end...
I'll take responsibility for it, so for now just hand it over.
Baka! Run!
Take it and run!
No! To have the nightmare of tag teams
come together at a time like this...!
I did just as I was told, and I ran!
Not knowing why, not giving it any thought -
I simply kept running!
But...
Then I got tired, so I soon went back to walking.
That was rough! And what is this anyway?
A wrestling mask?
Eew!
Well, I guess I'll stash it somewhere for now.
But if someone finds it, I'm sure it'll get taken.
Ah! I know just the place!
I swear. Waseda, you bastard!
He thwarts me at every turn!
Still, it was quite sensible of Baka
to think of storing it in the nurse's office.
Shiikyon is one of those with whom I can reason, so-
Yamai-san?
M-M-Majo?! What are you doing here?
When I come to school, I can't seem
to be able to breathe very well...
Wouldn't you be better off if you just quit?
Shiikyon!
Excuse us.
Ah.
You've got the wrong...!
Okay, you don't have the wrong idea.
But hear me out.
Despite how it looks, I'm just fine, okay?
That's my-!
Mine!
Huh?
So it was you who bought it. I'm glad.
Why's that?
The truth is, that mask was used by
military platoons during chemical warfare.
The original owner was found
stabbed to death while still wearing it,
and banishing the spirit of vengeance
that still inhabits it has been quite difficult.
But if you're the new owner, Yamai-san,
I can act quickly to exorcise
the spirit should it return.
Huh?
Yamai-san?
Remarkable!
Never before have I felt magic of this strength.
A normal human would no doubt have had
his very soul devoured just by looking at it.
However, it chose the wrong person to challenge.
Because I know. This is...
It's a trap!
No, this can't be!
I tried sticking my face in, just a little,
but it's gripped me tight!
I can't break free! Is this the curse of the gas mask?
Release me, damn you!
No, no! Waseda said that the next time I'm late,
he'll shave off the top of my head
and slather it with Vaseline!
Don't look at me!
What the heck? That is too funny!
I said, don't look!
I'd forgotten what a hopelessly stupid
human being you are.
I'm not a human right now. I'm a koala mom.
What are we supposed to do
now that you're stuck too?
Oh, shut up! The koala has it worse,
being all stooped over with a baby on her back!
It's hard work raising a kid, you stupid deer!
It can't be! Karma had to kick in now?
What's wrong?
I need to go to the toilet.
What?! For Number 1, 1.5, or 2?
Number 1. Wait, what's "1.5"?
A shart.
I shouldn't have asked.
We're out of options. You wanna go to
a house nearby and ask to use their toilet?
I-I couldn't do that. It's too risky!
If they say no, I won't be able
to hold it and I'll wet myself.
Just the shock of being refused
will make me wet myself!
Ah, so there's a 200% chance of wetting yourself, huh?
In that case, we've got no choice.
We'll walk back to school as-is!
One, two. One, two. One, two.
One, two-
Oh, no! My shoelace came untied.
Don't think about that!
Just walk, keep moving forward!
One, two. One, two.
It's no good. I can't hold it anymore!
Don't give up! You can do it.
Once we turn that corner, we're almost at the school!
One, two. One, two-
You two.
Waseda!
I was told you'd left for school, but I got
concerned when you still hadn't shown up...
But something this ridiculous
just shouldn't be possible.
I'll go get some tools to cut you out.
Till then, just wait there.
Waseda...
Finally, we've been freed!
Still, that was just a little bit fun, right?
What?
Well, compared to when I was alone,
having you there was somewhat...
No, it was very reassuring. You have my thanks.
Nah, no problem.
I think that maybe, just maybe...
We couldn't help it that we were late,
so that ended up saving my scalp!
Plus, I got to feel what it's like to be a koala mom.
I could get along with this person.
If there's a next time,
If it's not just all in my head, that is.
I'd like to try being an alpaca dad!
Let's all give a round of applause
for the Badminton Club
for their excellent performance at the nationals.
I'm sure "that one" will rise to the challenge.
Thank you very much.
Timing it just right, till the last possible moment
where one won't get yelled at...
Thank you very much.
Timing it just right, till the last possible moment
where one won't get yelled at...
And thanks to all our team members.
to make the final move!
One who makes the last move
The Last Clapper
Next up, a round of applause for 3rd year
It is a thrilling game.
Naoko Fujiwara for having won the
Outstanding Performance Award in the Art Competition.
Thank you very much.
But to be honest, I wanted to get the Grand Prize.
I knew it.
You didn't disappoint, Baka.
However, when more than one Last Clapper
occupies the same space,
Next up, a hand for our student council, which
the risk of being discovered increases greatly.
received a commendation for its volunteer activities.
It is quite dangerous.
And now, I make the finishing move!
Everyone, let's all go pick up trash together!
We'll be waiting in front of the school gates at 7:00 am.
Behold: a final clap after everyone
has fallen completely silent.
We'll be waiting in front of the school gates at 7:00 am.
Behold: a final clap after everyone
has fallen completely silent.
Topping that would be-
Wh-what?!
And she even raised her hands to clap.
That is truly the heresy of heresies!
You see? The teachers have begun to stir.
And now, a final round of applause
for everyone on stage.
They have fully locked on to our position.
And now, a final round of applause
for everyone on stage.
In this business, once you've
been noticed, it's all over.
It's can't be helped.
Unfortunately, it's time to close up shop.
Knowing when to call it quits is also
the skill of a true professional.
Even Baka must have enough brains to know
not to make a move under these conditions.
She... friggin' clapped!
What's more, she went with an ipponjime rhythm!
Note: A clap used to celebrate something's conclusion
This isn't "thrilling,"
and we're way past it being a "game"!
It's just suicidal!
Wait. Did you take things that far
to try to tell me something?
I fear being yelled at,
have been acting in the shadows, but...
"You should be yourself." That's it.
I got your message loud and clear.
And so, this concludes the awards ceremony.
Next up, our school song.
Sainotama Girls' High School - School Song
Lyrics: Atsushi Oniyamada
Music: Moehiko Sakaguchi
Kin no asahi ni sobieru kousha
The school building stands tall in the golden morning sun
Hiatari ryoukou natsu atsui
Excellent sun exposure, summers are hot
Nisshouken de jimoto to momete
Disputed with the locals on right to sunlight
Kensetsu yotei ga zurekonda
Construction schedule was delayed
Aa dai wa shou o kaneru
Ah! Better too big than too small
Sainotama tama tama tama
Gin no yuuhi ni mukau wa warera
We face into the silvery setting sun
Danbou zenkai fuyu mo atsui
Heaters on max, winters are also hot
Nioi no hanninsagashi wa suruna
Don't do a search for the culprit of the smell
Don't worry be happy
Aa mina kusakerya ki ni naranu
Ah! If we all smell then no one minds
Sainotama tama tama tama