Yo
Mic check
JK
Eh?
Hai!
Soko wa futsuu one-two ga best?
Tsuki tte hiruma wa shizuka na beast
Tsuki ga nan datte? Ikinari toutotsu
Yoru ni natte kara kurayami magirete
Kirakira shichatte tereyasan
Ayakaritai lunatic girls
Sore binjou shitai no, kirakira JK
Genjyou shotchuu
Daradara OK~!
Atamannaka zenbu
Karappo ni dekita nara yuunou
Sou na no? You know?
Yasei no honnou (Nya~)
Seken ni hitokoto otome no otakebi
Wawawawawa~!
Zanshin shout
Wawawawawawawa~!
Tsuki tte usagi inai ndane
Dassu tte doitsugo nan dane
Karakute nakinagara curry ga tabetakunaru BGM!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Wa ni natte
Mic check JK one-two JK one-two
Nan datte OK everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Iki sutte
Shiisuu ramen gyudon tonkatsu kishimen
Nandemo tabetakunaru BGM
Kosei wa zettai dashioshimi shinai
Kusuburu honnou minna de wa! tto
Odorokashite sa, mada minu hou e
Muda demo let's go, itsushika treasure
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Nakitai toki wa
Omoikitte naite naite tsuukai
Soukai na kibun sa every day
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Hora sono ato wa
Iya demo kitto harete sou egao ni narusa
Wa! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
In mid-ceremony
Except
Kohaku
Keep out!
Th-this could be...
quite bad!
Hey, Sis, the bath is...
What's wrong?
Kohaku!
Huh? Wait, whoa, what's going on?
Wh-wh-what should I do?
At this rate, Baka-san is...
Baka-san will...!
Friends
I'm bored.
Wanna go do something?
Such as?
A New Year's shrine visit.
But it's March.
Plus, it's cold.
Right.
Hey, would you get mad if I cracked a fart in here?
I would erase your existence.
What are you grinning about?
Hey!
You seriously suck! Get out of here!
I haven't fired anything off. Not yet!
What do you mean, "not yet"?
You were totally going to do it!
It's complete: Himeji Castle.
That's on you, so you'd better eat it.
My nose is running. Grab me a tissue, Wota.
Get it yourself.
Oh, come on. You're closer.
Barely. And don't scooch away.
No, you are closer, by eight centimeters.
I just measured!
Measured it how?
Base times height divided by two.
The only thing "base" here is you.
Eew, now it's starting to drip!
Now Wota's house will be coated with snot,
a stain that will never be removed!
If you've got time to talk, you've got time to blow.
I've led... a good life.
Blow your nose already!
And you, Robo, don't make the
Toyotomi family tree out of mandarin oranges!
Note: Toyotomi Hideyoshi was the samurai general who unified Japan
I thought I was gonna drown in a sea of snot.
Hey, Robo, are you the type who
looks at the tissue after blowing?
Indeed.
Yeah, I thought so!
Wota, what about...?
What the hell?!
I don't know why, but Wota's losing it.
Drowning in a "sea of snot"?
Who's ever heard of someone dying like that?!
Her funny bone is more like a funny ligament.
Good God...
I'm bored. Wanna go do something?
Such as?
A New Year's shrine visit.
But it's March.
Plus, it's cold.
Right...
This is nice, isn't it?
Yeah, it's nice.
You know, for the next 10 or 20 years,
we're probably gonna be repeating the same
conversation over and over again, huh?
What? What did you just say?
How many times must I say it?
If you don't do your best on your final exams,
you will be held back a year.
I am unflinchingly serious.
I have also been nagging you almost every day about it.
Surely you didn't think I was joking, did you?
That's what I thought.
Would a blow to the head help?
Believe me when I say that if you
get an F on even one subject,
you will be held back, Tanaka.
Held... back?
That's totally what he said!
Uh, there's nothing funny about that at all.
And he was looking way serious!
I think your nervous system is broken.
Are you really okay?
Huh?
The heck is this?
I thought it might help reality sink in a little.
Baka-san! Baka-san! Baka-san!
Hey there! It's been a week.
Good morning.
Held Back
I-I knew it! It's just like the fortune said!
Oh dear.
Hey, what...? Not this again!
It's been a while since I've run.
Yeah, well... You said a fortune, right?
Yes. My fortune-telling is almost never wrong.
Are you okay?
This isn't the time for you to be
worried about someone else, is it?
You've missed so many days
that you're in trouble too, right?
There's nothing to worry about!
For a while now, I've actually been
doing a special study method!
"Special"?
You plebs...
It's called "sleep-learning."
Do you know it?
I saw it on TV recently.
Apparently, people's brains can learn
while they're sleeping.
Oh, really?
Yeah, so now I'm sleeping 12 hours a day!
Robo, this is...
So, I'm auto-learning like crazy. Like, for real!
Yes. This is precarious.
Isn't sleep-learning awesome?
Baka, the thing is...
It's only sleep-learning
if you've slept after you've studied.
If you haven't studied,
it's just regular sleep. It's meaningless.
You're sleeping way too much, Baka.
Really?
Really.
H-hey, this is bad!
Finals are coming up soon!
That's on you! Why did you think things
would work out if you just slept?!
I thought I could take the easy route
and when I went to bed,
I could remember what I heard in class.
The truth comes out.
But you sleep in class too!
Oh. You're right!
I swear...
All that sleep has improved your skin,
but it's just wasted on you!
I'm sure your blood would be
quite pretty if drawn right now...
The thing is, even on my best days,
I'll score about a 20 on my tests.
So, it's kinda impossible for me to get
over a 40 on all subjects, right?
Don't you guys think so?
Aah, I really might be the only one
who has to repeat a grade.
Baka-san...
Note: Slang for "Senpai"
Even if we're in different grades, please let me
eat lunch with you sometimes, Paisen.
How long you plan on living
in slumber land? Snap out of it!
Well, next, I thought I'd take the easy route
and take some protein to improve brain-
Listen up: You do not sleep a wink until exam time!
That's how hard you have to study!
You got that?!
U-understood, Paisen.
Look, you really need to cut that out!
Ow!
Okay, let's start with Japanese history.
The treaty signed in 1895 after
the Sino-Japanese War was...?
To critical acclaim.
"Acclaim" has nothing to do with it!
It was the Treaty of Shimonoseki!
So, after that, what were the three countries
of the Triple Intervention,
which called for the return of the Liaodong Peninsula?
Uh, gimme three choices, please.
That would be giving you the answers!
Elementary-School Science
Even a Monkey Could Understand
You're just being mean and
giving me the hard ones, meanie!
Anyone in elementary school
could get these, you halfwit!
You know, the way you word
these questions is super confusing!
Um, Saginomiya-san?
I'm just reading them the way they're written!
Is it true that the next test will determine
if Tanaka-san can move up a grade?
Then how you're reading them means
something must be wrong with your brain.
What does that even mean?
You just want to mouth off at me, don't you?!
Yes, it would seem to be true.
If you don't take this seriously, I'll rip your bangs off!
Kikuchi-san!
In my opinion...
it's not possible to teach Tanaka-san
using so-called "orthodox" methods.
I believe that would be like
trying to teach an insect to do tricks.
Please, let me handle this!
Majime!
And so, to dive right into it...
We shall begin with this.
The heck is that?
Is "H-He-Li-Be" a spell to summon up
a dead pirate or something?
It's a mnemonic to help memorize the periodic table.
Still, the problem is how to make her
remember a mnemonic.
Love
Lie-be
You won't forget if you create
a mental image when memorizing.
Liebe means "love" in German...
So, if you use "H-He-Li-Be-B-C-N-O-F-Ne" to imagine...
"Handsome Hero, LiBe, Brushing Cheeks
Nuzzling on Frigate Nearby," you can remember it.
I love me
some boat
Well, it certainly packs a punch...
Still, what is that next "Nature's Magic, All Milk"
thing supposed to be? I seriously don't get it.
Well, you see...
Once upon a time, there lived a handsome hero
who loved his frigate a little too much...
...and they lived happily ever after.
That counts as a happy ending?
And so! This mnemonic is all about handsome heroes
on the high seas. What do you think?
Yeah! I totally memorized it!
What? With that?
I'm glad you get better, Mr. Seaman!
Okay, let's keep going.
Yeah!
Accepting Applications for Upcoming Semester
Okay, next. What does photosynthesis require?
Water and determination.
You know that's not it. Use common sense!
And you, Robo! Don't do that here!
Use common sense!
2X squared minus 3A times base...
Are you a follower of the Church of Base or something?!
Start again!
At this point, she might be the founder of that church.
Nah, it's no good. I just wanna sleep for a-
No sleeping! That nap will cost you everything!
Y-yes, Ma'am.
Ari-ori-haberi-imasokari.
Tori-sugari-no-ariyoshi. Dararai dararai-
Wrong!
Do that part one more time!
Ari-ori-haberi-imasokari...
Ah! N-Nino!
Hey, Loli. 'Morning.
Kari-gurashi-no-arirarira.
Wrong! One more time!
Butt-of-the-rishiri-kelp-riri...
Oh. It's Baka, huh?
Ari-ori-haberi-imasokari.
Giant-anteater-waited-upon...
Tanaka-san, good morning.
One-year-passed-since-husband-was-killed....
How far have you gotten?
Widow-still-in-her-prime...
Next up, let's do Japanese history.
Ugh, that again?
Stop whining and get to it!
There's a lot of memorization
on the first and second days,
so I think it would be better to tackle that first.
I'm hungry.
We barely just finished second period!
Eat something sweet to get yourself motivated!
Loli... Blessings upon you!
These are for everyone!
Thank you for this!
Thanks.
Thank you!
Hey! Don't eat 'em! Those are mine!
I-it's not like I brought these snacks for you, you know.
Now's my chance!
Hey! That's just nasty.
Now, all those belong to me!
Are you for real?
Yet another misfortune!
Now they're just filthy!
Please calm down. It's all right.
In one instant, those sweets turned into filth!
Hey! You need to apologize to Loli
and then pay for those!
The ones in the box are still clean.
We just have to throw out the
non-chocolate parts used to hold them.
What's this? What are you all up to?
Oh no! What should I do?
They should still be edible.
Worst-case scenario, we could wash them...
Oh, sweets.
I claim one!
Don't just steal one!!
- Lily!
- Someya-san!
Spit it! Spit that thing out!
Lily! Medic! Medic! Nurse!
Hang in there! We'll get you to the nurse's office!
First off, just hurry and spit that out.
And so, a sacrifice has finally appeared...
Throw up everything you've eaten. All of it!
Goliath frog...
Okay, next.
Who is the author of "I Am a Cat"?
Natsume Soseki.
Good.
And what year did the Manchurian Incident occur?
The year one-nine-three-one.
Correct. You've burned through a lot of this, huh?
At this rate, you can probably make
more than 40 on all subjects!
My stomach's not doing so good...
Maybe it's Loli and Lily's curse.
It hurts! It really hurts!
The biggest wave in human history
is splashing on my shores!
J-just hurry up and go to the toilet!
That solder stinks, Robo.
Oh? I think it smells nice.
Man, that cleared things out!
I guess all this unfamiliar "studying"
made me constipated!
Your face really looks nice and refreshed.
Huh? It does?
Hold on. You didn't refresh
your brain as well, did you?
You didn't core dump your memory
while taking a dump, right?!
What a funny thing to say, Wota!
Who is the author of "I Am a Cat"?
Uh...
What year did the Manchurian Incident occur?
I don't remember.
Hey! You knew the answers to these
just a minute ago...!
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me you've forgotten everything
you've memorized in these last few days!
Nah, as if! There's no way that... That...
Uh, yeah. Maybe.
This can't be happening!
There's no time left, and now you have to
learn everything all over again?!
Seriously, what kind of brain do you have in there?!
All over again? No! No, I don't want to!
I don't wanna study anymore!
The Toilet is Prohibited!!
I've rearranged the schedule.
If you follow this precisely, you should
be able to just barely hit 40 points.
Wh-what about time for sleeping?
Or eating, or taking baths?
Or going to the bathroom?!
There is none.
You fool! Either you do this, or it's game over!
Forget it, forgot it, four goats and a tit!
This will totally kill me!
Now listen up!
In this fight, you will either die or
move on to the next grade!
Um, I...
I... I give up being a high school girl!
What?! H-hey!
What are we supposed to do now?
Attendance Log
Tanaka is absent again?
That makes three days now, right?
Could it be that she doesn't plan on coming back?
N-no! I don't want to part with Baka-san like this!
Green Tea
Loquat
Apparently, she's here.
That's what Baka's mom told me.
Help Wanted
Still, why a hog farm?
There must be plenty of other part-jobs.
It is like her, though.
Yeah, but still...
You want one?
Thank you.
It sure is quiet without Baka around, huh?
That's true.
You know, I thought of something.
Maybe the reason I've hung out with her...
is that sense of security from having
someone "beneath" me.
If that were true...
I think that would make me a horrible person.
Still, it turns out that's not the case, huh?
That makes me glad. For real.
I was sure the office staff said that
she's working around here...
Blgh! It stinks like animals!
It's the scent of animals engaging in activity.
I don't mind it.
You've got sort of a weird smell fetish, Robo.
Ah. Over there.
Hey, Ba-!
You sure eat a lot, Wota.
You eat much more, and you'll lose that figure.
Oh, wait. You never really had one!
Robo, you're as emotionless as always.
Still, how come you're so popular with the guys? Jeez!
Oink.
Guys sure do like the silent type, huh?
Oh, Loli! Wanna get up on my shoulders?
And, Lily! You don't break out into hives
when I touch you anymore, huh?
You self-conscious jerk!
And quit harping on everything, Majime!
Plus, I don't get 95% of what you say.
And YOU, you're like, "I don't want to hang out with
the group," but you're so easily tempted by food.
It's not like I hate you, though, Yamai.
And you need to stop just silently
staring off into space, Majo. It's freaky!
I'm not going back! I don't wanna study anymore!
I'm done being a high school girl!
Plus, I have lots of friends here and I don't have to study!
Is this for real?
Yup. It's for real!
Oh. Well, that's a waste.
Being a "high school girl" is the most powerful
of weapons, yet you're tossing it aside.
I'll be fine! I may not be a high school girl,
but I'm super popular here!
I've got handsome male swine
chasing me around every day!
All right, fine. I get it...
But what about ME?
Someone like you, who's worthy of
my scathing retorts, is a rare find.
If you're not around, my days will get so boring
that I'll just give up and die!
Without you, Baka,
there's no point in me attending Saijo.
That's right! For your sake and ours,
come back already!
Come talk that stupid talk you always do! C'mon!
The truth is, this work is pretty tough...
I have to get up early and
there's so much I have to learn.
I've started to think that I can try to run away,
but nothing good will come of it.
Baka...
If either choice is just as tough...
I'll buckle down and study!
Then, we can all be 2nd-years together!
I... I'm gonna quit my quit being a high school girl!
Baka!
Robo... Wota!
Thank you, Wota!
Uh, I don't think that's who she should be grateful to...
Still, the sentiment is not mistaken.
Robo! Thank you!
Hey!
Yeah, but still...
The fact that Baka's in danger of being
kept back hasn't changed at all.
What do we do now, Robo?
Whoa, hey! What are you doing?!
I'm using tactile means to make her learn.
You can erase this once you've memorized it.
Will this even come off?
Sure enough, it won't come off!
Dammit! It's un-erasable! It's unbelievable!
Well, I guess it kinda does work...
This is a pen!
Also... When you get sleepy, put this on.
S-sine... cosine. In... In...
Mathematics
Guidelines on
Tax Evasion
The effects are confirmed.
Pretend you don't know her. You don't know her...
Akane Kikuchi
Sawa-sawa-sawa-sawa... Warsaw sawa-sa...
Don't you think she’s about at her limit?
One nine five five five.
Tests begin tomorrow, so this does not look good.
Czech-czech-czech... Czechoslovakia....
Gary-gary-gary-gary Hungary...
I-I finished it, Baka-san!
I'm sorry I kept you waiting!
Please, down this all at once!
Wh-what did you make her drink, Majo?!
Also, are you okay with your absentee rate?
She'll be fine. It's an energy enhancer
I made in order to change her fate.
What's in it?
I can't say.
Why not?
Wow. Seriously, wow...
The dosage is rather close to the lethal limit.
It's all so clear now.
So what's in it?!
Majo, thank you!
She's all hopped up!
A-are you okay, Tanaka-san?
We don't have time, so come on!
We gotta hurry and keep going!
Ah, I suppose I'll study with you as well.
Me too!
Popo... Po.
Next, let's go over the periodic table.
She's losing it. Go get some water.
Ari-ori-haberi-imasokari.
What? Splashing that on her would be too cruel!
And no "poppopo."
It's for her to drink, you fool!
The Warsaw Pact, 1955.
Poppopo... Portsmouth!
She truly has some good friends.
Indeed.
Tanaka will probably be all right...
Though, in another sense, she is not all right.
However, the real problem here...
...is you, Yamamoto.
Attention required!!
Would you mind coming with me?
I'm sure you know the reason why.
I don't knowee!
Akane Kikuchi
My dream
I want to be a manga artist!
I will definitely become one!
I am Sawatari, and I'll be in charge
of Class 2-2 for the next year.
For those of you from Class 1-2 who chose to
move forward pursuing Liberal Arts,
it's hardly worth mentioning at this point, but...
School Entrance Guide
And so, Robo!
I thought it was a cat, so I was all
"Meow, meow" as I moved closer,
but when I picked it up, it was just a wig!
There's no way you'd think a wig
would be lying in the street, right?
I bet they're totally looking for it right now!
Hey, Baka.
Oh, Yamai! I'm glad you were able to do
makeup work and move forward.
We might be in a bit of trouble here, you know.
Why's that?
It's possible that...
we've been transferred to another world.
Huh? You mean, that thing that's totally popular now?
It's actually not so much anymore.
Look at the members of this guild.
Aren't you seeing a group of unfamiliar faces?
Now that you mention it...
Uh, um...
Who the hell are you?! You're not even Robo, are you?!
You're saying that NOW?
Do you know about parallel worlds?
Not one bit.
I thought as much.
For whatever reason, we've somehow
slipped into a world that looks familiar,
but is quite different from our own.
As proof of that: look.
W-Wasedaaaaaaa?!
The Waseda of this world has become extremely old!
Waseda?
There are two of them?
I'm terribly sorry.
To think, students from my class
would cause such trouble...
What the heck, Young Waseda?!
Why are there two of you?
Which is the real you?
Oh. So that's it.
If you're really you, then answer this: Which do you
prefer, high school girls or college women?
Oh. So that's it.
Please excuse us now.
Be quiet! Your classroom is this way.
If a standard interview business suit or
a middy blouse school uniform was on the ground,
which would you deliver to the police-
Oh, yeah. We're 2nd-years as of today.
At last, I have achieved a higher station in-
Enough! Walk on your own
and get over here, you idiots!
Those are 2nd-years?
Is this school okay?
No Tree Climbing
Hey, can I say something amazing right now?
Like what?
You can eat panettone,
but you can't eat panties, can you?
Even though you're a 2nd-year,
you still like going on about panties, huh?
Why didn't you use frying pans or pandas instead?
Also, a high school girl is a high school girl, but-
Stop that, Ma-kun!
Come on, Miu-Miu. You were enjoying it too.
No, stop it! Ma-kun, you meanie!
It's your fault for being too cute, Miu-Miu.
Huh? Cut that out!
Miu-Miu, I swear...
The ones who are popular...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaa
are the few with pretty faces, and the ones who go
to co-ed schools where there aren't many girls.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaa
Reality sure is tough, huh?
Robo! Did you just make a face
like this doesn't concern you?!
Robo, we're all on the same side, right?
Right?!
Say something!
SOMETHING!
...Tapeworm.
What was that about.
I don't get it.
Anyway, what's so amazing?
I don't mind listening.
Oh, yeah! So, don't tell anyone, okay?
But high school girls are actually...