Hey, wanna hear something amazing?
Again?
No, for real, this time it's seriously amazing.
Just how amazing is it...
It's like when a sea otter takes its favorite rock to break open shells-
Never mind that. Hurry up and say it.
You know, whether it's a dream or whatever...
If you give up now, the game is over, right?
No, this is where it gets really amazing!
Okay? At least pretend to be interested!
Anyway, you're just quoting Coach Anzai aren't you?
Coach Anzai?
You said it without knowing that?!
Well, last night on my way home
from the convenience store,
If you give up now, the game is over...
there was a drunk businessman who was throwing up and crying,
and I was listening to him talk to a utility pole, yeah.
Boss, I want to do route sales...
Wasn't it game over for that sort of businessman a long time ago?
Still, I think it's a nice quote, you know?
If you give up now, the game is over!
Kinda cheers you up, you know?
I think it's amazing.
Oh!
The fact that you can still be impressed
by those lines, even though the game's already over.
Huh?
What?!
The game's over? It is?
Manga
Sleepy...
Whoa! For real?!
Teishotoku-P's dropped a new song! Yes!
Teishotoku P
This is Teishotoku. This is my 2nd work.
To grow older is to grow more regretful.
The PV and the lyrics are heart-wrenching.
This is nice. It's sick!
Tanaka
I'm so bored I'm going all out on selfies.
Aren't I cute?
That's why I've decided...
You're like... You're like...
To become stronger for your sake...
That smile...
Everyone's so amazing. They've all got talent...
I wonder what it's like to be judged by society?
Maho
Thump
Someday I too...
will become famous and have
the dream life of living off royalties!
Really, don't ignore me!
And it was when I was seriously researching
ways of taking selfies that'll win over guys.
Shut up. Unlike you, I've got a lot of stuff to do.
You know, because of you, Nerd,
I was almost bored to death yesterday!
That so? It would've been nice if
you'd just gone ahead and died then...
What about you, Robot? What'd you do on the weekend?
I went to sleep on Friday,
and when I woke up, it was Monday.
Oh.
Hey, Yamamoto.
What's up with the blond hair?
Do you want to be a foreigner or something?
Mr. Sawatari.
Well, that's because I'm a half-blood of the peoples
of the Altania Kingdom and the Dragonia race.
I see.
In that case, next time bring the
records of your family register then.
Kikuchi.
Isn't your hair color lighter than before,
and your skirt shorter as well?
Mr. Sawatari...
Well, that's because I'm a half-blood of the Instagram model race and the e-girls.
I see. Then there's nothing that can be done.
What do you mean nothing can be done!
That's where your quip goes!
Tanaka.
You...
Don't give up.
Honestly, kids these days...
It's like they have a sharp tongue.
If I say this, then they say that.
It's like they look down at adults.
It's difficult to deal with...
Well...
Everyone around that age can go through it.
So that those girls can become fine college wom-!
Can become adults. Our job is to watch over them for that purpose.
That's true, I guess...
Anyway...
Isn't this guy way too sensitive to hot things?!
No! Stop it!
What are you doing?
Serious! Help!
Idiot's trying to take my clothes off!
T-take your clothes off...?!
It's fine, just show me. It's no big deal.
No!
Tanaka, you can see that
she doesn't want to, right?
It is true that in actuality, you don't lose anything,
even if someone sees you naked.
However, it is possible that something precious
within someone's heart can be stripped off.
If you show me just a little then... I'll give you this!
What the hell is that?!
Parsley!
I don't want it!
Um... I think that even if it is just
among women, if you go too far,
then this matter could inevitably lead to you being
charged with the crime of sexual assault...
Not something like that.
Even though she's definitely not hurt, she's covered in bandages so I thought I'd find what's up.
Enough of that.
This girl suffers from a serious mental illness.
You should leave her alone.
More importantly, let's hurry and get to the cafeteria.
They say that today's lunch set B
is a parsley rice bowl.
For real? You guys should come too!
Th-that sounds good.
And if you don't like parsley,
then there is always the option of lunch set A.
Oh, sorry, but...
I don't like hanging out in groups.
Plus, the food in this lower realm
doesn't suite my tastes, you see.
See ya.
Green Tea
Draft
Post
Black Rabbit (Kuroto)
Solo meal rn lololol
Convenience store sandwiches are delish.
I like eating the tuna one last lol
Solo meal rn looool
Why do girls like to hang out in groups lol
That stuff is a pain.
Compared to other girls, I'm kinda chill lool
I'm an idiot.
I should probably head back now.
Whoa!
How long have you been there?!
Oh, I guess your panties are normal.
The trope requires striped panties, you know!
Normal panties, as in what?
Like normal ones.
An abnormal person like you
shouldn't be talking about normal.
Oh...
It's the last one...
I don't want an unpleasant dispute
over just one piece of chocolate.
It is time for...
Rock-paper-scissors!
First up is rock!
Hold up!
When you really think about it,
what's with that "first up is rock" thing?
That's your problem of all things?!
Well, it doesn't make sense, you know?
There's no reason why rock
has to be the first one up, right?
Who even cares. You take charge then.
Then, here goes...
First up is...
X!
Wait, wait, wait!
Ready, set-
What?! I was just getting to the good part...
What's with X?
You have to explain something like that before you just do it.
That's where you just do it.
Not possible! Plus, I've never heard of that!
Anyway, Robot, your adaptability is incredible!
It was a mistake to leave it up to her.
Robot, you do it.
Understood. I'll do it.
A normal one's fine, okay?
Okay. Here goes.
Ready, set...
Go.
And so therefore...
Wait, who was that?
Suzuki.
I found it on my way to school this morning.
Officer
Suzuki Masayoshi
That he'd lose his badge is, well...
He definitely fails as a police officer, this guy.
Anyway, why does throwing Suzuki
mean that Robot wins, huh?
Because Suzuki's brain is blank...
...as a sheet of paper.
Suzuki!
Intercepting Chopsticks!
No!
Having a dispute is unpleasant after all...
Yeah. More than having a dispute,
there's something we have to do.
All right, let's go.
To rescue Suzuki.
North Tokyo Police Station
Yasaka Branch
I was in serious trouble!
Thank you! You guys are my saviors!
Also, please have this chocolate snack.
And why is that?
Anyway...
Is it okay to waste time like this?
Ba-dump!
Maho
Akane Kikuchi
My dream
I want to be a manga artist!
"If you give up now, the game's over, right?"
What?
Nerd, you want me to read your manga?
Even though it's as embarrassing
as if you were stark naked,
you want me to read the manga
and let you know what I think?
Why me, and not Idiot?
Well, if I showed it to her, then she'd definitely...
What?! Nerd, this is the manga you drew?!
You're so delusional you actually think this is good!
Come on, Miss Nerd.
Sign my back, please? Come on, come on!
Sir, can we keep this masterpiece
that will go down in history in this library?
You know that's how it'd end up.
It would. For sure.
That's why, please!
Then, I'll go ahead and read it right away.
Magic by Maho
I don't even know how to feel right now...
I read it.
H-h-h-how was it?!
This is a report that raises
objections to our country's disorderliness
regarding the energy problem, right?
I think it's interesting.
No, it's fully just a shojo manga.
There's a little something that's bugging me, though.
What?! Where, where?!
That can't be, can it?
Only Maho and I
share this secret.
This scene...
These two remain seated and don't appear to move,
but the microwave-like thing in the back
totally comes up close in the next panel.
Oh, unless the main character has the ability
to draw in nearby electronic appliances,
when her feelings get excited
above a certain level, or something?
No. There's no edgy setting like that.
It's just a drawing mistake.
Also...
this scene.
That's...!
That's more or less this manga's
biggest highlighted love scene, but...
Is this person under a curse
that doesn't let him bend his knees?
If this is a story about the main character
battling to break this curse,
it might be better to foreshadow
the knee issue at an earlier stage...
I'll study drawing and start over!
The road to becoming a professional was never gonna be easy.
I've gotta practice drawing a lot more.
Who thinks Shoji would be good?
Yes!
Huh? What?!
I'm Maho Shoji. Fourteen years old.
By some strange coincidence
I got nominated by everyone in class,
and by majority vote,
I became a magical girl.
Meanwhile, my secret crush who studied abroad
and is super smart, Leon
had something totally unexpected
happen to his body...
Maho...
My knees won't bend, no matter what.
N-no way!
They won't... Ugh! Bend...
It's not a symptom of old age?
Even though I'm only twenty years old?
At first, I thought it was something
to do with aging, but I was wrong...
It appears that people who can't
bend their knees in the same way,
are appearing all over the country one after another.
Maho, ain't old age! Curse!
So, this was your doing after all!
The incarnation of evil, Pandemic!
Die! Democracy!
Take that!
To be blunt, I was being forced into a
desperate fight in the battle against Pandemic.
Maho. Impossible. Can't!
To be blunt, he's awfully strong...
What's wrong, little girl?!
Don't you care what happens to this guy?!
Maho!
Leon!
Don't worry about me.
Do it!
Unforgiveable...
Leon's... knees...
Give them back!
That's the auto skill that triggers
when her feelings are out of control!
Pena-Sonic!
Pena-Sonic
Electronic appliances get pulled in and released
Not good...
I'm taking a day off today.
Huh? Is Nerd absent today?
Several months until Halloween
Breakfast
Around the World
Have you heard anything?
I don't know.
Maybe her knees aren't doing well.
Whoa!
Hey, hey, come on! You gotta be kidding me!
That is way too cute!
Like
Of course, he'd cry!
If he was that cute, then not only would I cry,
I'd be bleeding too!
Oh! Don't! If he gets that close, then...
So cute
Shut up!
Oh!
All right! Bless!
I got to savour him licking tears! Bless!
I can't take this... This is beyond awesome...
Not to mention, they're just
minor characters coupling up.
This artist understands...
Oh! Shortcake!
Morning!
Wh-who the hell are you?!
That's Nerd. Although her face
has been low-efforted by the animators.
Huh? What?
So, Nerd's Maiden Week has started up again, huh?
M-maiden Week?
When Nerd falls for with an anime character or
a voice actor or a Pocaro-Pro, this is what happens.
She means vocaloid producer.
L-love?
In regards to Nerd, there are cases when she can
be infatuated by relationships between two men,
so I don't think you can make the sweeping
generalization that she harbors romantic feelings, right?
Between two men?
What does that mean?
For example...
Her heart will skip a beat when she sees stuff like that.
So that being said, about tomorrow's staff meeting...
Stop it! Shortcake's not ready for that!
Yeah, leave it to me...
Her heart will skip a beat...?
What?
Are you sure?
No problem. I don't mind.
No, that's impossible.
The degree of difficulty is too high.
Her face is back to normal...
As expected, Oxbridge and Gotsumori
just wouldn't work, you know.
No... Wait a sec.
BL Vision!
Are you sure? We are in school here.
I-I don't mind. If that's what you want then...
Nah, no way.
For sure, no matter how you look at it,
that's way too extreme.
Yeah, of course!
Oh, I'm gonna go to the restroom.
I could even make Oxbri-Gotsu happen...
Ace A
Officer Frog
calendar
Why would you
say that?
I… was only thinking of you…
I don't want to hear that!
That's not what I wanted to hear!
DASH!
To be blunt...
I don't quite have confidence in the story,
and my drawings suck.
What was I trying to make anyway?
That reminds me. I should have the the first manga I wrote somewhere around here.
This thing is giving off some
seriously messed up vibes.
Was I around a fourth-year in elementary,
when I wrote this? Even still...
Braised Burdock Root's Love
Isn't the cat way too big?
Well you know, animals are hard right?
I'm not good at them now either.
On the contrary, my attitude to challenge myself
to draw something I couldn't is admirable.
Leaving that aside...
The impression the title gives...
What? The main character is a burdock root?
Was this a story about a burdock root falling in love?
Oh, I see. This is a love that started with
the braised burdock root as the trigger.
You've got burdock root
on your head!
It's scary how it's basically all about burdock root.
Braised burdock root!
Oh! It's because
I ate it for breakfast!
How embarrassing!
It's way more than just on her!
This is only the cover and the first page?
Looks like i'm gonna be busy tonight.
Hey, fourth-year Akane.
First-year of high school Akane's gonna show you her newfound prowess and wit.
Her favourite food is eel
The buildings all look like chocolate bars!
Apartment
Building
Trudge trudge trudge
What happened to the back of his head?!
You can have this!
You like them, right?
Now there's an actual chocolate bar?!
A chocolate bar!
Yay!
Thank you
What even is perspective?!
Thump-thump
Sometimes he's nice
and sometimes he's mean...
Which is real?
Lockers
Desk
This is
a classroom
Door
Friend
Alice's head
Random lettering doesn't make up for your inability to draw you know?
Actually...
stairs
What is up with these stage-like stairs?!
Oh god, his running!
DASH
Wait
I guess I wasn't great at drawing joints back then.
Huh? It's already over?
I love you!!
The End
What?
At this weird half-way mark?
Afterword
So, what happens to Alice after Rikuto has confessed
his love to her? Actually, they start dating.
On the following Sunday, the two of them go on a date
to the aquarium and they run into the rival, Marika.
She asks, "do you two love each other?" and Rikuto says...
The important part was explained in the afterword!
The actual story is in the afterword!
A-amazing.
Elementary students are way too carefree.
And I definitely had some doubts about it, but...
From start to finish, that cat never showed up!
This was awful.
This was way worse than I thought...
Why would you
say that?
I… was only thinking of you…
I don't want to hear that!
That's not what I wanted to hear!
DASH!
But, you know,
compared to my past self...
It looks like I have really improved.
Wow! I wanna draw something like this!
I wanna eat piroshki till I'm stuffed...
The story will go like...
Paneling is really tough.
Whatcha drawing?
I-it's nothing!
I did it!
I kinda feel a little motivated.
All right!
I guess I'll give it another go!
Why would you
say that?
Please
make it in time
Train
And yet the knees still haven't improved!
Well, well.
You're gonna need my power soon, right?
Theory of Relativity
I can see right through everything, you know.
Huh?
It's silent yet again today.
Yamamoto.
Guidance Counsel Room
Do you know why you were called here today?
I dunderstand.
That word doesn't exist in English, Yamamoto.
The back of the test you did today...
Usable only for
light attributes
Extreme Flash
Salamander Hurricane
Eternal Galaxy Blizzard
Killer
Health recovers
Love Stream Shot
Kill Breath (Poison)
Heart Break
Galaxy
Just what exactly is this?
What's wrong? Cat got your tongue?
The black cat is...
Cat?
Every morning at the exact same time,
in the exact same location,
there's a cat, but it doesn't seem
very cat-like, you see.
No matter how I look at it, it seems unnatural.
As a test...
Amoebas assist Amelia A E I O U!
I tried doing squats while saying vocal exercises, and it wouldn't even move a muscle.
No matter how you look at it,
you are the one who's unnatural, Yamamoto.
There's a good chance that thing isn't a normal cat...
It is a normal cat.
It must be a messenger. From another world.
Wait, Yamamoto.
Do not leave me behind and
head further towards dreamland.
I am here asking you about
the scribbles on the back of your test.
So!
That cat is a cat that came from another world,
and it called upon me as the chosen one,
and what if it started saying something
like "please save this world"?!
Calm down.
What if I have to fight against Dark Soul or something?!
Calm down, Yamamoto.
I'll need a special move, you know?!
Even so...
Let's suppose that cat is
a messenger from another world,
then why would you be chosen, Yamamoto?
Please observe, Mr. Sawatari.
These moles on my arm...
They look like a dragon crest, right?
Even Aries would be a stretch.
For the longest time,
I didn't understand the purpose of my life.
But, I realize it now.
I am the chosen Dragon Warrior.
That messenger is waiting for my power.
So, you are saying that you have been thinking up
special moves in preparation for that forthcoming day?
That's right.
But as your Teacher, I don't think you need to go
out of your way to come up with that kind of-
Then!
What if, when that crunch time comes I can't think up
of a cool move, and on the spur of the moment...
Um...
No... No... No...
Nougat!
If I say something like that,
then what are you gonna do about it?!
There's no way I'd recover!
Well, here's the thing.
Try not to obsess over it.
Scribbles should be written on
notebooks during recess.
Thank you, civilian.
Shut it.
Now that I understand the issue of the back side of the test...
How do you intend to explain this grade
on the front side, Yamamoto?!
Math: QuizFull name: Yamamoto Minami
Points
Simplify the following expressions
Expand the following expressions
What?! No way! Dark Soul?
Gotta go to the restroom...
No!
Stomach's doing a Guerilla Blizzard!
That's even worse than Nougat!
Yamamoto!