Hey, can I say something amazing right now?
Again?
No, this time for sure, it's seriously amazing.
As for how amazing it is...
It's like when a sea otter takes its favorite rock
in order to break open shells-
Never mind that. Hurry up and say it.
You know, whether it's a dream or something else...
If you give up, the game's already over, right?
No, it gets amazing from here!
Okay? Show a bit more interest in it?
Speaking of, in the first place,
that's Anzai-sensei's famous saying, you know?
Anzai-sensei?
You said it without knowing that?!
Well, last night on my way home
from the convenience store,
If you give up, the game's already over...
there was a drunk businessman who was throwing up and crying,
and I was listening to him talk to a utility pole, you see.
General Manager, I want to do route sales...
Hasn't the era of that kinda businessman had its end, in a lot of ways already?
Still, I think it's a rather nice phrase, you know?
If you give up, the game is already over!
I kinda get cheered up by it, you know?
I think it's amazing.
Oh!
Based on the fact that you can still be impressed
by those lines, even though the game's already over.
Huh...?
What?!
The game's over? It is?
Manga
Sleepy...
Whoa! For real?!
Teishotoku-P-san's uploaded a new song! Yes!
The PV and the lyrics are heart-wrenching.
This is nice. It's sick!
Tanaka
I'm so bored I'm going all out on selfies.
Don't I look cute?
That's why I've decided...
You're like... You're like...
To become stronger for your sake...
That smile...
Everyone's so amazing. They've all got talent...
I wonder what it's like to be judged by society...?
Someday I too...
will become famous and have
the dream life of living off royalties!
No really, don't ignore me.
And it was when I was seriously researching
ways of taking selfies that'll win over guys.
Shut up. Unlike you, I've got a lot of stuff to do.
Aw! You know, because of you, Wota,
I was almost bored to death yesterday!
That so? It would've been nice if
you'd just gone ahead and died then...
And you, Robo? What'd you do on the weekend?
I went to sleep on Friday,
and when I woke up, it was Monday.
Oh...
Hey, Yamamoto.
What's up with the blond hair?
Do you want to be a foreigner or something?
Sensei.
Well, that's because I'm a half-blood of the peoples
of the Altania Kingdom and the Dragonia race.
I see.
In that case, next time bring the
records of your family register then.
Kikuchi.
Isn't your hair color lighter than before,
and your skirt shorter as well?
Sensei...
Well, that's because I'm a half-blood of the peoples
of the Tochigi and Hokkaido prefectures...
I see. Then there's nothing that can be done.
No! Not nothing can be done!
You're supposed to say a witty comeback there!
Tanaka.
You...
Don't give up.
Honestly, kids these days...
It's like they have a way with words.
If I say this, then they say that.
It's like they look down at adults.
It's difficult to deal with...
Well...
Everyone around that age can go through it.
So that those girls can become fine college wom-!
Can become adults. Our job is to watch over them for that purpose.
That's true, I guess...
Anyway...
Isn't this guy way too sensitive to hot things?!
No! Stop it!
What are you doing?
Majime! Help!
Baka's trying to take my clothes off!
T-take your clothes off...?!
It's fine. Just show me.
It's not like you lose anything by doing it.
No!
Tanaka-san, you can see that
she doesn't want to, right?
It is true that in actuality, you don't lose anything,
even if someone sees you naked.
However, it is possible that something precious
within someone's heart can be stripped off.
If you show me just a little then... I'll give you this!
What the hell is that?!
Parsley!
I don't want it!
Um... I think that even if it is just
among women, if you go too far,
then this matter could inevitably lead to you being
charged with the crime of indecent assault...
Not something like that.
Enough of that now.
This girl suffers from a serious mental injury.
You should leave her alone.
More importantly, let's hurry and get to the cafeteria.
They say that today's lunch set B
is a parsley rice bowl.
For real?! You guys should come too!
Th-that sounds good.
And if you don't like parsley,
then there is always the option of lunch set A.
Oh, sorry, but...
I don't like hanging out in groups.
Plus, the food in this lower realm
doesn't suite my tastes, you see.
See ya.
Green Tea
Black Rabbit (Kuroto)
Meal by myself now
The convenience store's sandwiches are delish.
I prefer eating the tuna one last.
Why do women immediately
want to hang out in groups?
That kinda thing is a hassle.
Compared to normal girls,
I'm kinda chill, you see.
I'm an idiot.
I should probably head back now.
Whoa!
Since when have you been there...?!
Oh, I guess your panties are normal.
That's where you're supposed to wear
striped panties, you know!
Normal panties, as in what?
Like normal ones.
An abnormal person like you
shouldn't be talking about normal.
Oh...
It's the last one...
I don't want an ugly dispute
over just one chocolate snack piece.
This is where we...
Go by rock-paper-scissors...!
First up is...Rock!
Wait!
When you really think about it,
what's with that "first up is rock" thing?
That's what you're hung up on, at this moment?!
Well, it doesn't make sense, you know?
There's no reason why rock
has to be the first one up, right?
It doesn't really matter. Then you take charge.
Then, here goes...
First up is...
X!
Wait, wait, wait!
Ready, set-
What?! I was just getting to the good part...
What's with X?!
That's too confusing to put out quickly.
That's where you just do it.
Not possible! Plus, I've never heard of that!
Speaking of, Robo, your adaptability is amazing!
It was a mistake to leave it up to this one.
Robo, you do it.
Got it. I'll do it.
A normal one's fine, okay?
Okay. Here goes.
Ready, set...
Go.
And so therefore...
Huh?! Wait, who was that just now?!
Oh...!
Suzuki.
I found it on my way to school this morning.
Officer
Masayoshi Suzuki
That he'd lose his police ID is, well...
He certainly fails as a police officer, this Suzuki...
Anyway, why does putting out Suzuki
mean that Robo wins, huh?!
Because Suzuki's brain is blank...
As a sheet of paper.
Suzuki!
Intercepting Chopsticks!
Oh no!
Having a dispute is ugly, after all...
Yeah. More than having a dispute,
there's something we have to do.
All right, let's go.
To rescue Suzuki...!
North Tokyo Police Station
Yasaka Substation
Aw! I was in serious trouble!
Thank you! You guys are my saviors!
Also, please have this chocolate snack.
And why is that?
Speaking of...
Is it okay to wastefully spend time like this?
Ba-dump!
Maho-chan
Akane Kikuchi
My dream
I want to be a manga artist!
"If you give up, the game's already over, right?"
What?
Wota, you want me to read your manga?
Even though it's as embarrassing
as if you were stark naked,
you want me to read the manga
and let you know what I think?
Why me, and not Baka?
Well, if I showed it to her, then she'd definitely...
What?! Wota, this is the manga you drew?!
You're so delusional you see through
rose-colored glasses!
Come on, Wota-sensei.
Sign my back, please? Come on, come on!
Sensei, can we keep this masterpiece
that will go down in history, in this library?
You know that's how it'd end up.
It would. For sure.
That's why, please...!
Then, I'll go ahead and read it right away.
Magic by Maho
I can't even describe this moment in time...
I read it...
H-h-h-how was it?!
This is a proposed document that raises
objections to our country's disorderliness,
regarding the energy problem, right?
I think it's interesting.
No, it's thoroughly just a shojo manga.
There's a little something that's bugging me, though.
What?! Where, where?!
It's a secret between
Maho-chan and me
This scene...
These two remain seated and don't appear to move,
but the microwave-like thing in the back
totally comes up close in the next panel.
Oh, unless the main character has the ability
to draw in nearby electronic appliances,
when her feelings get excited
above a certain level, or something?
No. There's no edgy setting like that.
It's just a drawing mistake.
Also...
this scene.
That's...!
That's more or less this manga's
biggest highlighted love scene, but...
Is this person under a curse
that doesn't let him bend his knees?
If this is a story about the main character
battling to break this curse,
it might be better to foreshadow
the knee thing at an earlier stage...
I'll study drawing and start over!
The road to becoming a professional
is tough after all.
I've gotta practice drawing a lot more.
Who thinks Shoji-san would be good?
Yes!
Huh?! What?!
I'm Maho Shoji. Fourteen years old.
By a strange coincidence
I got nominated by everyone in class,
and by majority vote,
I became a magical girl.
Meanwhile, my secret crush who studied abroad
and is super smart, Leon-kun,
had something totally unexpected
happen to his body...
Maho-chan...
My knees won't bend, no matter what...
N-no way...!
They won't... Ugh! Bend...
It's not a symptom of old age?
Even though I'm only twenty years old?
At first, I thought it was something
to do with aging, but I was wrong...
It appears that people who can't
bend their knees in the same way,
are appearing all over the country one after another.
Maho, this not old age! Curse!
So, this was your doing after all!
The incarnation of evil, Pandemic!
Die! Democracy!
Take that!
To be blunt, I was being forced into a
desperate fight, in the battle against Pandemic.
Maho. Impossible. You can't!
To be blunt, he's awfully strong...
What's wrong, little girl?!
Don't you care what happens to this guy?!
Maho-chan!
Leon-kun!
Don't worry about me.
Do it!
Unforgiveable...
Leon-kun's... knees...
Give them back!
That's the auto skill that triggers
when her feelings are out of control!
Pena-Sonic!
Pena-Sonic
Electronic appliances are drawn in and then let loose
Not good...
I'm taking a day off today.
Huh? Is Wota absent today?
Breakfasts
of the World
Have you heard anything?
I don't know.
Maybe her knees aren't doing well...
Whoa!
Hey, hey, come on! You gotta be kidding me!
That is way too cute!
Like
Of course, he'd cry!
If he was that cute, then not only would I cry,
I'd be bleeding too!
Oh! Don't! If he gets that close, then...!
So cute
Shut up!
Oh!
All right! Thankya!
I got to enjoy him "licking tears"! Thankya!
I can't take this... This is beyond awesome...
Not to mention, they're just
minor characters coupling up...
This artist understands...
Oh! Loli!
Morning!
Wh-who the hell are you?!
That's Wota. Although her face
has been distorted by QUALITY.
Huh? What?
So, Wota's Maiden Week has started up again, huh...?
M-maiden Week?
When Wota falls in love with an anime character or
a voice actor or a Pokari-Po, this is what happens.
She means Vocalo-P.
L-love...?
In regards to Wota, there are cases when she can
be infatuated by relationships between two men,
so I don't think you can make the sweeping
generalization that she harbors romantic feelings, right?
Between two men?
What does that mean?
For example...
Her heart will skip a beat when she sees stuff like that.
So that being said, about tomorrow's staff meeting...
Stop it! Loli's not ready for that!
Yeah, leave it to me...
Her heart will skip a beat...?
What?
Are you sure?
No problem. I don't mind.
Now that's impossible.
The degree of difficulty is too high.
Her face is back to normal...
As expected, Waseda and Gotsumori
just wouldn't work, you know.
No... Wait a sec...
B&L eyes!
Are you sure? We are in school here.
I-I don't mind. If that's what you want then...
Impossible. No way.
For sure, no matter how you look at it,
that's way too extreme.
Well, of course!
Oh, I'm gonna go to the restroom.
Wase-Gotsu was easily doable...!
Ace A
Why would you
say that?
I am thinking of your sake...
I don't want to hear that!
I didn't want to hear
something like that!
DASH!
To be blunt...
I don't quite have confidence in the story,
and my drawings suck...
Just what was it that I was trying to
make in the first place...?
That reminds me. I should have the manga
that I first wrote, somewhere around here.
This thing is giving off some
seriously dangerous vibes.
Was I around a 4th-year in elementary,
when I wrote this? Even still...
Kinpira Gobo's Love
Isn't the cat way too big?
Well, you know, animals are hard, right?
I'm not good at them now either.
On the contrary, my attitude to challenge myself
to draw something I couldn't draw, is admirable.
Leaving that aside...
The impact of the title...
What? The main character is a burdock root?
Was this a story about a burdock root falling in love?
Oh, I see. This is a love that started with
the kinpira gobo as the trigger.
You've got kinpira
on your head!
I was shocked because the subject was
based completely on the burdock root.
Kinpira gobo
Oh! It's because
I ate it for breakfast!
How embarrassing!
It's beyond the level of just being on her!
This is only the cover and the first page...?!
Character Introductions
Alice
Rikuto
Cat
Now this looks like I'm gonna get busy tonight.
Hey, fourth grade Akane.
The Akane who's become a 1st-year in high school
will show you her real abilities for witty retorts...
Favorite food is Eel
The buildings are all like chocolate bars!
Building
Trudge trudge trudge
Apartments
What happened to the back of his head?!
You can have this!
You like them, right?
And a real chocolate bar has appeared too?!
A chocolate bar!
Yay!
Thank you
The concept of perspective drawing?!
Heart-thumping
He's nice sometimes
and mean sometimes...
Which is real?
Desk
This is
a classroom
Door
This has been going on for a while, but don't try to cover your lack of drawing ability
with hand-drawn lettering!
Actually...
What is up with these stage-like stairs?!
His running style!
DASH
Wait
I guess I wasn't good at drawing joints,
starting from around that time, huh...?
Huh? It's already over?
I love you!!
The End
What?!
At such an odd half-way point...?
Afterword
So, what happens to Alice after Rikuto has confessed
his love to her? Actually, they start dating.
On the following Sunday, the two of them go on a date
to the aquarium and they run into the rival, Marika.
She asks, "do you two love each other?" and Rikuto says...
The important part was explained in the afterword!
A-amazing...
Elementary students are way too carefree.
Not to mention, I kinda faintly had a bad feeling, but...
Even to the very end, there never was
an appearance of this cat!
This was awful...
This was more awful than I thought...
I am thinking of your sake...
I don't want to hear that!
I didn't want to hear
something like that!
DASH!
Why would you
say that?
But, you know...
if I look at things starting from the past...
It looks like I have really improved...
Wow! I wanna draw something like this!
I wanna eat piroshky til I'm stuffed...
The story will be...
Panel layouts are difficult.
Whatcha drawing?
I-it's nothing!
I did it!
I kinda feel a little motivated.
All right!
I guess I'll give it another go!
Why would you
say that?
Please
make it
in time
And yet! The knees still haven't improved!
Train
Well, well.
You're gonna need my power soon, right?
Theory of Relativity
I can see right through everything, you know.
Huh?
It's not talking to me again today.
Yamamoto.
Career Guidance Room
Do you know why you were called here today?
I don't knowee.
That word doesn't exist in Japanese, Yamamoto.
The back of the test you did today...
Usable only for
light attributes
Extreme Flash
Salamander Hurricane
Eternal Galaxy Blizzard
Killer
Health recovers
Love Stream Shot
Kill Breath (Poison)
Heart Break
Galaxy
Just what exactly is this?
What's wrong? Is it something hard to say out loud?
The black cat is...
Cat?
Every morning at the exact same time,
in the exact same location,
there's a cat, but it doesn't seem
very cat-like, you see.
No matter how I look at it, it seems unnatural.
As a test...
Amoebas assist Amelia A E I O U!
I tried doing squats while saying vocal exercises, and it wouldn't even stir an inch.
No matter how you look at it,
you are the one who's unnatural, Yamamoto.
Probably, that thing isn't a normal cat...
It is a normal cat.
It must be a messenger. From another world.
Wait, Yamamoto.
Do not leave Sensei behind and
head further towards dreamland.
I am here asking you about
the scribbles on the back of your test.
So!
That cat is a cat that came from another world,
and it called upon me as the chosen one,
and what if it started saying something
like please save this world?!
Calm down.
What if I have to fight against Dark Soul or something?!
Calm down, Yamamoto.
I'll need a special move, you know?!
Even so...
Let's suppose that cat is
a messenger from another world,
then why would you be chosen, Yamamoto?
Please take a look at this, Sensei.
These moles on my arm...
They look like a dragon crest, right?
It's a stretch to even say the Ram constellation.
For the longest time,
I didn't know why I had been born.
But, I realize it now.
I am the chosen Dragon Warrior.
That messenger is waiting for my power.
So, you are saying that you have been thinking up
special moves, in preparation for that forthcoming day?
That's right.
But, I, your Sensei, don't think you need to go
out of your way to come up with that kind of-
Then!
What if, when that crunch time comes I can't think up
of a cool move, and on the spur of the moment...
Um...
Na... Na... Na...
Namul!
If I say something like that,
then what are you gonna do about that?!
I won't be able to recover from it!
Well, here's the thing.
Try not to obsess over it.
Scribbles should be written on
notebooks during recess.
Thank you, good citizen.
Shut it.
Now that I know about the issue
of the back of the test...
How do you intend to explain this score
on the front side, Yamamoto?!
Math: Mini test
Minami Yamamoto
What?! No way! Dark Soul?
Um, uh...
Gotta go to the restroom...
No!
S... S...
Stomach's doing a Guerilla Blizzard!
That's even worse than Namul!
Yamamoto!