Hey, can I say something amazing right now?
This again...
No, this time for sure, it's seriously amazing.
As for how amazing it is...
the twin brothers inside a kangaroo's pouch-
Never mind that. Hurry up and say it.
So, you know the thing about a "miracle" is...
it won't happen if you're just waiting for it!
No, that's not the amazing part!
Try to be a bit more interested, okay?
Last night, I got a little hungry,
so I went to a convenience store.
And when I went up to the register...
The change ended up being three yen more,
or something like that, right?
Idiot! It wasn't a pathetic miracle like that!
That will be 98 yen.
BUDDA
Whoa!
Let's go! Let's go!
Great Buddha!
That's an urna.
Let's see, "an urna is the right-spiraled white hair
that is on the forehead of the Buddha"...
Huh? That's hair?
Oh yeah! I sure got to see a good thing!
After all, the thing about a miracle is, you gotta
make it happen yourself or else, you know!
Wait...! What the hell was that just now?!
I desperately don't give a damn about your miracle.
Great Buddha? Hey, Great Buddha?
Yo
Mike check
JK
E?
Hai! Soko wa futsuu one two ga best?
Tsukitte hiruma wa shizuka na beast
Tsuki ga nandatte? Ikinari toutotsu
Yoru ni natte kara kurayami magirete
Kirakira shichatte tereyasann
Ayakaritai lunatic girls
Sore binjyou shitaino kirakira JK
Genjyou shotchuu daradara OK~!
Atamannaka zenbu karappo ni dekita nara yuunou
Sounano? You know? Yasei no honnou (Nya~)
Seken ni hitokoto otome no otakebi wawawawawa~!
Zanshin Shout wawawawawawawa~!
Tsukitte usagi inaindane
Dassutte doitsugo nandane
Karakute nakinagara curry ga tabetakunaru BGM!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Wa ni natte
Mike check JK one two JK one two
Nandatte OK everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Iki sutte
Shiisuu ramen gyudon tonkatsu kishimen
Nandemo tabetakunaru BGM
Kosei wa zettai dashioshimi shinai
Kusuburu honnou minnade watto
Odorokashite sa mada minu hou e
Muda demo let's go itsushika treasure
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Nakitai toki wa
Omoikitte naite naite tsuukai
Soukai na kibun sa everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Hora sono ato wa
Iya demo kitto harete sou egao ni narusa
Wa! Moon! Dass! Cry! Everyday
Majime
Hey Robo.
Why were you absent yesterday?
No big deal.
"No big deal"? But, you...
I had a dream about going to school,
and I thought it was unreasonable that I have to
go to school both in my dreams and in reality, so...
That's true. There's a valid point there.
No there isn't.
Yes, there is.
There isn't.
There is!
Isn't.
May 15th, Wednesday. 12:40 PM.
Is!
Isn't.
Is.
Isn't... Oh!
To Saginomiya-san's mysterious reason for her absence,
Gotcha!
Damn it! Wota, you jerk!
Tanaka-san counters with a "there's a valid point there."
This time, try saying pizza ten times...
Oh! It's Ninomae-san!
Aw! You know, no matter when you
look at her, she's so cool!
I'm not good with that...
That uniquely girlish world that's adorned
with pink and hearts and stuff...
That day of the entrance exam...
if I hadn't had a fever running over 40 degrees
and diarrhea and nausea
and a headache and chicken pox and
a strained back and sprained fingers...
I wouldn't have been at this high school...
See? Pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza!
Sainotama Girls' High School
A tough three years is about to start.
As I steeled myself that way,
on the day of the entrance ceremony...
1st-year Class Lists
Shiori Saginomiya
What?
Saginomiya...?
We're in the same class?!
You're right.
Not to mention, we're in the same grade.
Saginomiya-san!
It's... a miracle!
Well of course that's obvious.
I wonder if you can skip grades here.
She was always the top of the class in middle school.
There was even a rumor, that she was ranked in
the top ten of the nationwide mock exams.
That Saginomiya-san...
The fact that I ran into her at this school,
where it's said that it's standard score ranking
Aw, my future is being painted over in the color of mud.
It's just your imagination.
is only as high as the intelligence level
of a four-year old is...!
She of all is the solitary genius!
Ah... How beautiful!
Due to being overwhelmed by that mysterious aura,
I hadn't been able to talk to you up until now,
but this time for sure,
I want to become acquainted with you...
I know! I'll show you my best bit!
Imitation of roast pork fat!
Ha! You do resemble it.
What...?!
I was surprised...
Even though you never once let
that poker face slip in middle school...
You...
Laughed?!
I'll look forward to the next time too.
Sure, leave it to me.
That Saginomiya-san laughed...?!
Wota, you try doing the roast pork fat too.
I have therefore formulated a hypothesis.
I'm not doing it.
It can just be Iborico pork.
How's that any different than regular pork?
In order to become acquainted with you...
Also, it's not Iborico, it's Iberico.
Apparently, it is essential that I appropriate
something like Tanaka-san's approach!
Ibirico?
Iberico.
Iburico?
Iberico!
Very well. I will prove that I can solve
this mathematical factor for you!
It has been one month and ten days since that day,
and I have continued my observation of Tanaka-san.
However, I have yet to arrive at a solution...
Have you ever smelled an ankle?
One doesn't normally smell that, you know.
Wanna have some? It's a new flavor, you see!
Oh, you sure?
Yay! Thanks!
Aiight! H-here goes.
Isn't that where it should be shiitake mushrooms?
H-hey, you guys!
E-eat! Bocky!
Y-yeah, thank you, Loli.
Thank you, I'll have some.
But that was rather sudden.
Here, Tanaka, you too-
Chomp!
Huh...?
Why, you...!
Ouch! What are you, a gorilla?!
Stop bullying Loli like that! Apologize!
Loli...
Listen up. This is a dream.
You're just having a bad dream, that's all.
Hey! You gotta properly apologize to Loli-
Come on, Loli! Jump!
Jump and overcome your sadness!
Come on! You gotta jump! Loli!
Let's go over here, Loli.
If you're not gonna jump, then I'll jump!
Is this a bad dream?
I'll jump like crazy! I won't be held...!
The fact that you summoned me,
means it's about that, isn't it?
1st-year Midterm Exams Schedule
Career Guidance Room
That you've finally come around
to liking high school girls...
But sorry, I'm not interested in you, Sensei.
In terms of sushi toppings, I like warasa yellow-tail.
Huh?
Warasa is the common name of regular buri yellowtail
during the mid-point of their growth,
and the even younger fish are called inada.
Huh...
Warasa aren't as gummy as inada are.
Uh-huh...
The clear appeal of warasa comes from
the umami of the exquisite layering of fat it has.
Uh-huh...
Therefore, it is not possible for me
to ever like buri or inada.
In other words, that's how it is.
Um, I don't get what you're saying.
Well then, let's have an
easy to understand conversation.
Your grades are at Earth annihilation levels.
Seriously?!
During the midterm exams, if you get
failing scores on more than three subjects,
you will choose either to receive
one month of supplementary lessons,
or you will get a crew cut.
What?! That's going too far!
Have you ever seen
high school girls with crew cuts?
Are they eating Choco Bats with a crew cut?
Huh? You serious?!
Well then, that's how it is.
Can it be a 70% crew cut?
Oh no! This is a girl emergency!
When is Robo gonna get here?
She said she was coming,
but there haven't been any messages.
What? Seriously?
To think that they get to study for tests
after school with Saginomiya-san...
Should we get started for the time being?
Huh? Wait a sec. We're seriously gonna study?
Makes me so envious from the bottom of my heart...!
Huh?! You're the one who said let's study
for tests at a casual restaurant chain.
Something like that's obviously
just an excuse, you know!
What?! What for?
An excuse to prevent you, Wota,
from studying. Tee-hee!
Don't worry. You're not alone.
Let's both fall down together to the bowels
of the Earth, with these upcoming tests.
Just you should fall. Sink to the bottom.
Aw! You know, I've got no motivation without
eating some thick meat or something.
Wota, treat me! I'll pay you back when I'm successful.
I don't have money to give to
someone who can't succeed.
What're you doing?
High speed lip licking!
Bathroom break.
Oh? Poop?
Like big poop?
Why am I hanging out with that one?
It's because she has at least
one good thing about her, right?
Think back. Something good about her.
Oh, there's none.
Oh, that was fast.
Was it like roller coaster poop?
Stop saying "poop" in a loud voice!
Gotcha!
That's orange coffee cola cocoa
infused soda with tabasco!
You really drank it!
C-consciousness is...
Hey Wota, you okay?
Snap out of it! Wota?! Wota?!
Kikuchi! Kikuchi!
Tanaka!
Watcha drawing? Manga?
Don't look!
Aw, come on, it's fine. So what?
You aiming to become a manga artist?
What?! Th-that's not it! In the first place,
it's not like I could become one!
It's not that easy of a world to get into!
Huh?! Well of course, if you don't think
you can become one, then you won't.
But if you think you can become one,
then you can, right?
Huh?!
Right?
Oh...
There's hijiki seaweed stuck in her teeth.
Hey...
Hey Wota... Wota!
Hey! Snap out of it!
Hijiki... The hijiki seaweed...
What about hijiki?!
Uh... I-I'm okay.
I had a minor flashback, that's all...
Sorry, I overdid it.
That's right. Thanks to that, I remember now.
When I'm with this one,
although it's frustrating to admit...
Were you remembering a past life,
where you were a hijiki or something?
She sure is funny.
Huh?!
This time it's spinach?!
Huh? Spinach?
After a bout of mischief against Kikuchi-san,
she bares her teeth and grins like a chimpanzee...
You're right. Lucky! Got me a snack!
So goes Tanaka-san.
Ma-ji-me!
C-can I help you...?
Your math notes.
Lend them to me?
Oh, actually, instead of just math,
make it all your notes on all subjects,
and the printouts of the exercises.
Lend them to me?
Um, I'm asking just in case, but if I do lend you those,
then what exactly do you plan to do with them?
Well of course that's obvious. I'll gratefully...
bury them in the ground.
And, that was a Mexican joke.
Majime, I'll be copying your serious notes exactly as is.
And then, when I get failing scores on all the subjects...
See? I did make sure to do all the studying.
Aha...
And that's how I'll make my appeal.
It's far more efficient to study,
than to resort to cheap tricks like that, you know!
Why aren't you using that energy properly?!
Well, well.
Take a look at my quiz results.
I'd like you to not look down at my academic abilities.
English, twelve points. Math, one point.
One point?!
Just what could you possibly be doing,
to get scores like this?!
Th-this is...
A royal straight flush?!
So, you found me out.
Whoa there! I didn't say for free.
How about for two pieces of
Tanaka family secret recipe fried chicken?!
By any chance, is that a no?!
Why would you think that I would accept, for that?
Fine! Then how about three pieces?!
You can go ahead and squirt lemon on it too!
That face is scary!
Besides, it's not an issue of how many!
Sorry, thanks! I'll copy them and
get them back to you ASAP, okay?!
Okay...
S-something else?
The thing about fried chicken is,
no matter how I look at it, it's tasty,
and men and women of all ages like it.
Don't you think it might as well be made
into the currency of the world or something?
Because then, I think the world
would be at peace, you know?
I-I understand, all right?
Go ahead and take those and please leave me be.
Not good.
When I talk to Tanaka-san,
I get hit by a headache and an illusion
that I'm losing my sense of equilibrium.
But, if that Tanaka-san's abnormal tendencies
are what attracted Saginomiya-san's interest, then...
Th-the thing about fried chicken is,
it's really delicious, and...
e-everyone likes it, and... and, well...
I wish it might as well be made into the currency
of the world or something! You know?!
I don't understand what you mean, at all.
Oh...!
The one thing I did figure out, however,
is that you are an intense fanatic of fried chicken.
N...! N...!
Now I've gone and done it!
Saginomiya-san was totally put off by me!
She must think I'm an insane fried chicken fanatic
who not only eats fried chicken for every
meal of the day, but takes fried chicken baths,
sleeps in a fried chicken bed and
juggles fried chicken in her spare time!
For sure!
I know! I must review my observation notes
to see what I did wrong.
I ended up lending my observation notes
along with the others, to Tanaka-san...
Those who are absent today are Kujyo and...
I guess, Ninomae.
Oh no, what do I do...?
What do I do?! What do I do? What do I do?
That notebook is all about Tanaka-san!
Tanaka-san did...
Tanaka-san was...
Tanaka-san is...
That makes it look like...
I'm a crazy fan of Tanaka-san...
and it makes it look like I'm stalking her every day!
Oh crap! Crap crap crap!
Given that it is Tanaka-san, I can't think that
she would just let it go, as if nothing had happened.
What to do... Come on me, think!
As far as I can imagine, based on her behavior pattern,
she has 328 anticipated courses of action.
Of course, she may easily skip over those
and I can anticipate that she
may diverge from what I imagine.
Don't get me wrong.
This is just part of a biological study.
Kanade. I brought some rice porridge, but...
It's not as if I like Tanaka-san or anything like that!
Oh, it's not as if I don't like her either!
So! If it was between Tanaka-san and shoelaces,
I would still like the shoelaces better!
If it was Tanaka-san or shoe soles,
then the shoe soles would still be...
My daughter has gone crazy from her fever...
But, well, by no means do I want to be stepped on
by shoe soles or something either...
Are you sure you're okay?
Maybe you should rest another day or two...
There is a battle that I can't
just keep running away from, so...
I'm headed off.
My daughter, you've never won a battle while
you're this weak, both physically and mentally…
You didn't study for the tests?
I slept well.
All right, Tanaka-san! If you're going to show up,
then feel free to show up anytime!
Come on, take your seats!
Huh...?
The test is starting.
Tanaka-san hasn't shown up?!
Put away the things on your desks!
Surely, she's not abandoning the fight, is she?
Anyone not get an exam paper?
Well, no, if it was her, then she'd
unashamedly take it and get a zero on it.
Sensei, I haven't.
Begin!
Hang on. This makes it seem like I
thoroughly know everything about Tanaka-san...
Focus, focus!
Tana... Oh!
T..Tanaka-san?!
A crew cut's too lenient,
so I went with going completely bald.
Supplementary
lessons
I know you made the effort to
lend these to me, so sorry.
Majime, your notes were too serious, you know?
You see, since the writing was
packed tight like black sesame seeds,
the moment I opened them, I got sleepy.
I was only able to copy the first line of
ancient literature. Hey, I'm sorry.
N-no, it's fine.
She didn't see it! I'm so glad I live life seriously!
More importantly, that hairstyle looks good on you.
Oh, yeah? You think so too?
What a wonderful day it was...
Even everyday scenery like this
looks like it's sparkling...
Another sudden evening shower, huh?
This voice is...?!
I-if we wait just a little, it looks like it'll stop.
You think so?
That I get to wait out the rain together with
Saginomiya-san is, well, hooray to evening showers!
Oh, shoot! I have to initiate some kind of conversation.
Whoa! It's really raining!
I'm glad I kept a spare umbrella!
Let me in, let me in!
Sure!
Not good. I have absolutely no idea what to talk about!
At a time like this, I wonder what
typical girls talk about.
TV? Performing arts? Fashion?
No good. My knowledge is lacking in all of those.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Because of this silence,
it's steadily turning into a heavy atmosphere.
Oh, I know!
This would be the time for
the Tanaka-san Observation Notes!
There has to be some hint in here, on how to
have a lively conversation with Saginomiya-san!
Can I not even have one conversation
with the person I admire,
without relying on other people's help...?
Well, it won't stop immediately, right?
In that case, goodbye.
S..Saginomiya-san, you'll get wet!
Huh?
Well, of course I'll get wet. It is rain after all.
That's true, but... that's not it.
Wouldn't it be better to wait until it tapers off?
I...
I've always made the decision that
I'll wait up to three minutes only.
You know, cup ramen in general
are like that too, right?
What?!
B-but, if you just wait five minutes,
the rain will taper off!
See? The sky in the west is brightening up!
It's irritating that something like rain is
preventing me from leaving, for even five minutes.
Um, actually, I have an umbrella.
So... please use this!
But then you'll be...
I'll be fine! Come on, hurry and use it!
But...
I...!
I like getting wet with my clothes on.
See?
Crap! I've turned into like a high-level freak!
Ah! It feels good!
I can't get enough of the adhesion of cotton to skin!
Oh rain! Come down harder!
Aw! Yet again I've failed in making
my acquaintance with you...!
Ah! More! More adhesion!
What an interesting girl.
You've got it wrong...
I'm not like a freak.
I just genuinely like getting wet
with my clothes on, that's all.
Dear daughter...
I like how the wet cotton adheres to my skin...
Society in general would call
someone like that a freak.
I'm in a bit of trouble.
Like it happens in anime a lot...
That "Whoosh!" thing is something
I wanted to do, so I climbed up, but...
It's really scary. And I've got the shivers badly.
It's been four hours and
I haven't been able to get down.
And I can't hold going to the restroom
much longer, so what do I do?
On top of that...
A bird has started making a nest.
I have to make a decision,
before that bird gets back.
What an insignificant person. That's what I am.
Majime?!
Why're you here at this time of day?!
Huh!? Yamamoto-san?
"Why?" Well, I had gone to the hospital
and now I'm going to school,
but Yamamoto-san, what are you doing
at this time of day in a place like that?
Huh?! Oh, I-I-I-I-I am, that is...
Now that you've seen me, I've got no choice.
I'll reveal my secret to you.
Secret?
I'm on the lookout you see. For them.
Them?
At the very least there's five of them,
uh no, s-seven of them...
At worst, there's fourteen of them.
So, you truly have no idea then.
Well, as long as I'm here on the lookout,
they can't easily make a move, you know.
Wouldn't it be better to call the police or something?
N-no way!
They're not the kind of opponent that
normal people can go up against!
Th-those guys...
Th-those guys, the "B-B-Blue Tree Bones" are...
Note: The clinic's name includes the kanji characters for:
Blue, Tree, Order, Bone, Clinic
Aoki Osteopathic Clinic
Those guys are dangerous.
Blue Tree Bones?
They show no mercy, even if its women or children.
Majime, you should also hurry and get outta here.
Yamamoto-san, will you be fine by yourself?
I'll be fine. Plus, I'm not alone.
Ah, it appears it's back.
My familiar, Spiritus, you see.
Now then, hurry before they notice!
Spiritus?
V-very well then.
Oh!
Oh no!
The truth is, I wanted her to rescue me...
I'm an idiot...
Come on!
You know, there is no way I would
blindly accept a story like that.
You!
Why would you also...? You won't be able to get down-
I can get down, if it's like this.
Please hold on tight!
Are you all right?
Awesome!
That was like an anime! My dream came true!
Huh?
Oh, uh, I mean...
Really, you had to go and do something unnecessary.
Sorry but, I'm gonna have to get going.
My client, a certain organization...
Organization?
No, a city.
City?!
No, it's a country, that's it.
Country?
That's right. You see, a country is waiting for me!
School is waiting for you too.
Oh yeah. Earlier, you were saying something
about being an insignificant person, but...
You're at least worth the value of someone like
a knight of the Dragonia Kingdom.
If you like, I could hire you.
Sawagashikute yakamashikute
Demo itoshikute
Ano hi no warai koe
Maki modesenai story
Seishun te yatsu wa zutto hikari to kage
Kurayami no naka
Kagayaku rettousei
Furi kaereba kojiraseta
Utsukushi sugiru hibi
Itsumo haru wa fui ni toori sugita ato
Kimi no kotoba mune ni reverb
Itsuka haru ga zenbu tsure satte shimau
Sono hi made wa baka de ii
Kake nukeru kara
Ma-ji-me!
T..Tanaka-san!
I hadn't given you the fried chicken thank you gift
for your notes yet, right?
You really don't have to worry about it.
Not good!
But, my bad, I already ate my bento, so...
I wouldn't call this a replacement for it, but...
"Imitation of fried chicken."
Huh? Majime?
Majime? Majime?!
Kikuchi.
You don't need a gaming console at school, you know.
Hey, Majime?!
That'll be confiscated.
Ugh! This sucks!
Saginomiya.
There's no need for cultivated bacteria
at school, you know.
That'll be confiscated.
I don't mind, but Sensei,
please handle them with extreme caution.
You see, they're troublesome bacteria,
if they're exposed to air.
You can have them back.