Hey, can I say something amazing right now?
That bit again?
No, this time definitely, for sure, it's seriously amazing.
As for how amazing it is...
With the shell from when a crayfish molts-
Never mind that. Hurry up and say it. Ugh!
So, you know the thing about "hair" is,
it grows in order to protect the body, right?
The hair on top protects the head, and eyelashes
are there to make sure dust doesn't get in the eyes...
Or something like that.
Yeah...
Well then, don't you think it's weird that
chest hair doesn't grow thick and wild,
in order to protect the heart?
So, you're saying you want to become hairy
in order to increase your heart's defenses?
Well, women have tits...
The fat in their breasts acts as cushions,
so they don't need it, right?
Gah!
There are women who don't have cushions
to serve that function, you know!
Right here!
That's true!
That being said, humans ought to have
more unnecessary hair growing thick and wild.
And yet, isn't everyone in society
way too into being smooth?
As if smooth is righteous!
Something like that is wrong!
Well?
I thought it was amazing.
You're probably the only one who's sulking,
for the reason of not having chest hair.
Right, Robo?
Speaking of, what have you
been making there for a while?
A heart with strong defenses.
Amazing...
Gross!
Yo
Mike check
JK
Huh?
Okay! Isn't that usually where one two is best?
So the moon is a quiet beast during the daytime
What about the moon? That's suddenly out of the blue
Once it becomes night, under cover of darkness
There you go being sparkly, wallflower
Want to be like you, lunatic girls
Want to jump on that bandwagon, sparkly JK
The present state of always lazing around is okay!
You're efficient if you can totally empty your mind of all thoughts
Is that so? You know? Wild instinct (Rawr!)
A word to society, a maiden's roar, ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Innovative Shout, ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
So there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
So dass is German, huh?
A BGM that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather round.
Mike check JK, one two, JK, one two
Anything's okay, everyday
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Sushi, ramen, gyudon, tonkatsu, kishimen
A BGM that makes you want to eat anything
Don't ever begrudge individuality
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather round!
Surprise it towards an unlooked direction
Let's go even if it's pointless. A treasure before long
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you want to cry...
Wholeheartedly cry and cry. It's gratifying
Everyday feels refreshing
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Even if you don't want to you'll cheer up
for sure, and yeah, you'll smile
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Everyday
Forgotten Item
The way I personally look. I always hated it.
Look at that girl.
Aw! So tiny!
Don't wanna get looked down upon!
S-stop looking at me, you scum...!
That's why I became a delinquent.
Loli! Loli, Loli, Loli!
Y-you jerk! Told you not to call me Loli!
Huh?! Come on, it's okay. It's cute.
It's totally not okay! And it's not cute!
Note: This is a nod to Studio Ghibli & Hayao Miyazaki's anime,
"Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind"
I'm not getting on!
I... I'm not gonna speak to you anymore!
That reminds me, Waseda said just a while ago,
for you to come to the faculty room.
You should have said that sooner-
There, you spoke to me! Loli, you lose!
Damn it!
Huh? I didn't ask for you in particular.
Huh? But Tanaka said...
What about Tanaka? Oh, perfect timing.
Please tell Tanaka to get her
preferred course request form in.
That jerk!
Please tell Tanaka to get her
preferred course request form in.
Well, that's when it should be silken tofu-
Tanaka!
Put out what you need to put out!
What? But I'm kinda really constipated right now.
Why'd you think I was talking about that?!
The preferred course request form!
Oh, you meant that.
Oh, also...
Y-you jerk! How dare you trick me earlier!
Sorry Loli, it was because you said
you wouldn't speak to me anymore.
You know...! If you keep making
those kinda worthless lies...
your house will be the only one that Santa
won't come to this year, you know!
Is she serious?
Yeah...
Well... That was rather shocking, you know...
H-hey... Why're you being all secretive?
But it's not impossible, you know?
That's true...
Whaddya think? That's gotta be a joke, right?
Even if she looks like that,
she is a high schooler, after all.
Oh, I've heard rumors about it.
That Loli lives together with just her grandma.
Under a strict grandmother...
Maybe she grew up in an environment on par with
a prison, where information was restricted.
That's way too strict!
There might also be the possibility
that she's an immoral granny
who's spent many years hypnotizing Loli...
Your idea is what's immoral!
H-hey! I said, hey!
Huh?
What're you talking about?!
Wh-what?
Sorry about that, Loli...
T-Tanaka...!
I told you I'm not gettin' on, jackass!
Damn it! That Tanaka really pisses me off...!
It's not like I wanted to look this way!
Anyway, who's the jerk who littered?!
What an asshole!
Jeez... Every last one of them...
They're all bastards... Damn bastards...
Hey there, welcome home, Saku.
Grandma!
Does it taste good?
Yeah!
How's school? Is it fun?
Have you made a lot of friends?
Wh-what's for dinner tonight?
Well, let's see...
Saku, shall I make your favorite, hamburger?
Yay! Hamburger! Hamburger!
Well then, I should probably go grocery shopping.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Oh! Grandma!
What's wrong? Does it hurt somewhere?
Ahh... Well, it looks like my knee is hurting just a little.
What?
No need to worry...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Grandma, you sit and rest.
I can go do the grocery shopping by myself!
Will you by okay?
Last time I asked you, you got lost
and the police officer had to help you out, so...
Th-that was only because he voluntarily
started talking to me and just followed me!
You be careful.
Don't go anywhere with some strange person.
Let's see. Onions, milk and eggs.
Hmm?
Corn
Onions
Eggs
Scallions
Ground mixed meat
Spinach
Tomato
Milk
Daikon radish
Tofu
Mix... Meat?
How do you read this?
Maybe it's a Chinese character?
One stick every day!
You'll get fat.
I'm gonna buy the Choco Bat Ace!
I wish they'd come out with a natto flavor!
That wouldn't go well with chocolate, you know.
It could work if it included macadamia nuts.
That was close. I can't take being picked on
by that jerk after school too.
This'll do.
What about the grown-up Choco Bat?
It's gotta be the Choco Bat Ace for me!
Compared to the Choco Bat, where one home run stick
or four hit sticks will get you one more stick...
With the Choco Bat Ace,
you can win a wonderful free gift with
one ace stick or mailing in three strike cards.
It's sold-out here too!
Just how much do you like Choco Bats, huh?!
I just realized I've come all the way
to the next town now...
I expect she wouldn't come this far-
All right!
Choco Bat
Found it!
She's here!
Hey, since we came all the way to Jusco, let's go play!
My parents are saying they made dinner,
so I'm going home.
Then me too.
What?! No! No, no!
I wanna play more! I wanna play!
Loli!
Perfect timing! Let's play together!
Idiot! As if I'd play!
You know, unlike you, I'm busy!
Don't say something like that. Come on...!
Whether it's toys or stuffed animals,
Uncle here will buy you as many as you want!
Motchinyan Dolls
All 5 types
980 yen (tax not included)
"Don't go anywhere with some strange person."
I'll pass!
Loli!
Grandma! I won!
I resisted Tanaka's temptations!
Hey, let's go already.
For real...?
I... absolutely will not move...
Come on! How long you plan on lying there?!
No!
This is embarrassing for us!
Hurry up! Let's go!
Stop it!
You stop it!
Robo, hold her up front.
No good. She's stuck on airtight like a barnacle.
Wota, hang on just a sec.
Dressing room
Please put a coin in. You can play together with me.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Who?!
Excuse me. Please lend us that mop.
We're going to utilize the principles
of leverage to peel her off.
Note: Hanamaru, meaning knobby nose
Hanamaru-san, sorry to ask, but would you mind
crouching down in this space between?
It's Shibazaki.
Here goes.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's digging in! It's digging in! It just creaked!
I definitely will not go home!
What's with this...?
This is ridiculous.
Let's leave her and go home, Robo.
Hanamaru-san, thank you for your cooperation.
It's Shibazaki.
Ouch! Ow, ow...
Jeez. She doesn't think we'll leave her behind,
so she's gotten all relaxed now...
She's begun rotating mysteriously…
Now she's starting to move to the side.
Under the vending machine...?
No way...
Maybe she found money or something.
That's pathetic. That's not something
a high schooler should do.
Huh?
She got it! She's got that pleased look on her face!
Thrill Land
A medal?!
A medal, huh?
How dare you get my hopes up! Thrill Land?!
This is like a waste of time.
Oh please! Change your name to Dejection Land!
Let's go home.
You're right.
Jeez! Gimme back my thrill! Argh!
Crisp Corn
Uh...
Um...
Eggs
Ground mixed meat
That's ground mixed meat.
Aren't you a good girl for running errands.
Here you go.
Thank...
Domestic products used
Recommended
for hamburgers!
Ground mixed beef and pork meat
With that I've got everything to buy.
Choco Bat
Includes a
prize chance
Wow!
Mama! I want this, this, and this!
No. You're a big brother now, you know.
A big brother should be able to
settle with just one, right?
Yes!
All right!
Choco Bat
Includes a
prize chance
Just one is...
Having just one is safe.
Your total comes to 1,826 yen.
What?!
I... I don't have enough money! What do I do?!
U-um... then I won't get this.
Not that. This one!
Very well.
I was able to buy everything except the meat...
I won't ask you anymore, Saku...
You really are a bad child.
Santa won't come for the rest of your life.
Oh! Are you all right? Oh...
Uh, um...
Grandma, I'm sorry.
I couldn't buy the meat.
Instead...
I'll give you this...
There's really no way to make
hamburgers out of Choco Bats.
Oh! Then I'll go back one more time!
It'll be okay.
Leave it to Grandma.
Wow!
It's a hamburger!
It's soft and yummy!
You see, tofu and panko bread crumbs
can turn into a meat-like texture.
Grandma, you're amazing!
I love you!
Aw! No! I wanna play!
No! Mama's gonna go ahead and go home.
Just a little more...!
Mama, wait!
Spoiled wussy brat.
Go home and suck on
your mama's tits or something.
Huh?
H-hey!
Wota, Robo, you're over there, right?
I said, hey!
Hanamaru-san.
It's Shibazaki.
Don't litter outside!!
Especially lighted
cigarette butts!!
Whatcha gonna do
if they catch on fire?!
For example, let's say that there is a
monomial of 3ABXH to the nth-power here.
Class is boring.
For example, let's say that there is a
monomial of 3ABXH to the nth-power here.
Class is boring.
In the situation where this will be considered
a monomial of X versus a monomial of A...
Robo's seriously taking notes...
In the situation where this will be considered
a monomial of X versus a monomial of A...
SEA OF HELL
EXPLOSION
START
HELL
Is she a genius...?!
In the situation where this will be considered
a monomial of X versus a monomial of A...
Is she a genius...?!
The degrees and coefficients
will each end up being different.
Become immortal
and be all alone
with no family
She's in despair over the maze she created herself...
The degrees and coefficients
will each end up being different.
She's in despair over the maze she created herself...
A polynomial is where a monomial
is added and subtracted...
Or so I thought...
A polynomial is where a monomial
is added and subtracted...
Delight...?!
For example, the monomial 3XY multiplied by
the monomial of 7AB equals 4ABXY, and this again...
All Wota's probably thinking about is BL stuff...
For example, the monomial 3XY multiplied by
the monomial of 7AB equals 4ABXY, and this again...
After all, the only thing this one
really thinks about, is BL stuff.
For example, the monomial 3XY multiplied by
the monomial of 7AB equals 4ABXY, and this again...
After all, the only thing this one
really thinks about, is BL stuff.
Hey Tanaka.
You've been spacing out since earlier.
Tell me what you're thinking about right now.
Right now?
Right now, I was thinking about BL stuff.
Oh, that's wrong. I was thinking about Kikuchi-san,
who's thinking about BL stuff.
What?!
Oh, that's wrong. I was thinking about Kikuchi-san,
who's thinking about BL stuff.
What?!
I wasn't thinking that!
Then what were you thinking about?
Obviously, about monomials and polynomials!
Saginomiya-san.
I have admired you since middle school.
So, that's BL after all.
Don't make me out to be some freak!
The fact that we'd unexpectedly be in
the same high school and the same class is...
What the hell is monomial and polynomial BL about?!
The fact that we'd unexpectedly be in
the same high school and the same class is...
You guys are being loud. Sit down.
The next problem goes to...
Next after Nishimura is...
Based off the student attendance list order, I'm next.
I have to show myself in a good way to Saginomiya-san.
Then...
Kikuchi.
Yes sir!
What?!
Um... If you consider it an X equation,
then the "top" is... I mean, um...
Huh?
Um... If you consider it an X equation,
then the "top" is... I mean, um...
I forgot my gym clothes!
What am I supposed to do about
the gym class that's next?!
Hey, look over there.
A wild granny has appeared!
Lv. 76  Wild Grandma
Don't make it sound like she's
some monster from somewhere.
Speaking of, I've seen her before.
That's Loli's Granny.
Seriously?
Maybe she has some matter to attend to here.
I'll just go get Loli.
Okay.
Let's go, Robo.
Hey!
Hey, Loli's Granny!
Loli?
I'm in the same class as Loli. I'm Tanaka!
Tanaka-san. By any chance, by Loli,
do you mean Saku?
Yeah, yeah, Loli!
Loli Granny, whatcha come here for?
Loli Granny...
Huh?
Is that Loli's?
That's right. I came to deliver the item
that Saku forgot, but...
Then, do you want me to pass it along to her?
Thank you for that, Tanaka-san.
But now that I've come, I thought I'd also take
a quick look to see how Saku is at school.
Loli!
Huh?
She's not here. Maybe she went to the gym?
I don't want to get yelled at
if I say I forgot my gym clothes,
but on the other hand, there's no one in
the class next-door whom I can borrow from...
Infirmary
I guess the only choice left is
pretend to be sick and be absent.
But having a pretend illness
isn't something a person should do!
She's a really good girl, you know.
And yet, she'll do a funny thing and
pretend to be all strong and take up a big attitude,
so I just get so worried, you see.
Ouch. Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Wh-what's wrong, Loli Granny?!
My legs aren't doing so well, you see...
You okay?!
I'm fine. I'm fine.
It won't be a problem if I go up slowly.
All right!
Get on, Granny! I'll carry you to wherever Loli is!
What?! But I feel bad.
I'll be fine! I'm more than 90 years
younger than you are, Granny!
I don't think there's that big of an age difference, but...
Can you even say that you'll be fine, in that state?
Oh!
My shoelace!
Granny, hold on tight!
Damn it!
Well, I would think that's how it'd turn out.
The shoelace...
It's like I should reach it, but I can't reach it...!
Damn it!
If I knew this was gonna happen,
then I should've drunk vinegar every day
and made my body flexible...!
There is the alternative of putting me down
and tying them, you know.
Oh yeah!
You're an odd child.
Whew! I'm gonna take a quick break.
You mean, here?
Yeah. You got anything?
You know, grannies often have stuff like mandarin
oranges and baked sweet potatoes in their bags, right?
It's not like all the grandmothers in the world
carry mandarin oranges and potatoes, you know.
Huh. Well, that's okay.
Then, tell me more stories about Loli!
Oh...
Like super fun ones, okay?!
Well, let's see...
Yeah, that's right. And then...
Uh, um...
I...
I'm in Class 1-2. The name's Saku Momoi, but...
When Saku was still eight years old...
I've got gym class next and...
It turned out that her father was being
transferred overseas to Germany for work.
Where's Germany? Is it far?
It's not too far away.
Originally, the family should have all gone together, but...
The city is very pretty
and they say the country is easy to live in.
Grandma, you're not going? Why?
There's no way I can go overseas at my age.
I plan on living and dying in this town, so.
Don't worry about me. The three of you should go.
It's not as if we'll never see each other again
for the rest of our lives.
No! Saku's staying with Grandma!
She really is a kind girl, you know.
She stayed behind for my sake, you see.
She probably actually wanted to be
with her parents, but...
So, that's probably why...
If you don't mind using mine.
I think it might be a bit big, but...
She's not very good about
depending on people other than me.
Oh!
Th-thank you...
Oh, Loli! We finally found you!
Huh?
Granny, that was a good story.
Although there wasn't a single
funny thing in it to laugh about.
It wasn't meant to make you laugh in the first place.
Grandma!
Huh?
And Tanaka?!
What's up with you lounging with
someone else's grandma on the landing?!
Why are you together with the likes of Tanaka?!
Has she done anything weird to you?
Hey! What the hell do you think I am?!
She's treating you the same as a degenerate.
Saku, when I came to deliver the items you forgot,
she treated me kindly, you see.
Huh?
Those are...
Oh... I-I borrowed them from someone
in the class next door.
You, Saku? By yourself?
Yeah.
Oh! Then I guess it was unnecessary
for me to come deliver them.
Th-th-that's not true! It wasn't unnecessary at all!
That's right!
Huh?
Same as unnecessary hair,
there's nothing that's unnecessary!
Granny's peach fuzz around her mouth
isn't unnecessary.
That's proof of evolution!
This is just aging.
But, you're right. I'm definitely glad I came.
Grandma...
Oh yeah!
I got to hear a whole lot of good stories
about Loli, from Granny!
You...! You bastard!
What are you saying you heard, huh?!
Hey! Spit it out!
I can't say it right now.
It's been a long time since I've seen her
seem like she's having that much fun.
I can't say it right now.
It's been a long time since I've seen her
seem like she's having that much fun.
Spit it out now!
It's been a long time since I've seen her
seem like she's having that much fun.
I wanna savor this for a little while more first.
It's been a long time since I've seen her
seem like she's having that much fun.
Don't savor it!
Seems fun... Is that what you call that?
I could totally savor it over at least three rice bowls!
Don't turn it into a snack!
Loli...
Please continue to get along well with Saku,
from here on as well.
You can count on me! Tell me some more
good stories about Loli again, okay?!
See ya, Granny! Take care!
What a nice grandma who loves her grandchild.
They seem to get along very well.
Yeah. Her sense of humor is so-so, but...
she was a good granny!
Why're you trying to expect that?!
That's right.
Huh?
My Grandma is my pride and joy!
Noisy and loud
But also endearing
The laughter from that day
A story that can't be rewound
The thing about youth is, it's always light and shadows
Inside the darkness
A shining inferior star
Looking back are complicated
Far too beautiful days
Springtime has always passed by unexpectedly by then
Your words reverberate in my heart
Someday springtime will take it all away
Until that day, being stupid is all right
Because I'll run past it
H-here are the gym clothes and...
a box of confections as a thank you for lending them!
A box of confections?!
G-Grandma said I should bring them.
Request to conserve water
M-maybe it was just my imagination...
Lizardoon...!
Whew...
What's wrong, Yamai? You look like a person
who was first to discover a murder scene.
A lot came out...