Hey, can I say something amaz-?
Stop it.
Cheap shoes are-
Enough.
Risqué dancing is-
Zip your hole.
Stinky turtles are-
Shut up!
Mainly in broad-
La la la! Can't hear you!
PET bottle!
Cut it the hell out already!
I'm ticked off as it is, because I can't
come up with an idea for a manga!
You self-absorbed fool! Just open your ears a little!
If you take the first letters of the phrases
Baka tried to say just now...
CHeap shoes
Ch...
ri...
CHeap shoes
RIsqué dancing
st...
CHeap shoes
RIsqué dancing
STinky turtles
ma...
CHeap shoes
RIsqué dancing
STinky turtles
MAinly in broad
CH
RI
ST
MA
That's aweso-!
PET bottle
"PE"?
Well, this year IS almost over.
Yo
Mic check
JK (High school girl)
Huh?
Yeah!
Isn't that usually where one-two is best?
The moon is a quiet beast during the daytime
What about the moon? That was sudden
Once it becomes night, under cover of darkness
You're so dazzling, wallflower
Want to be like you, lunatic girls
Want to jump on that bandwagon, dazzling JK
The present state of
Always lazing around is okay!
Everything in your mind...
Emptying all that will make you efficient
Is that so? You know?
Animal instinct (Meow!)
A word to society, a maiden's roar
Ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Innovative shout
Ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
So, there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
So, "dass" is German, huh?
Background music that makes you want to
eat curry so hot that you cry!
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather 'round
Mic check JK, one-two, JK, one-two
Anything's okay, everyday
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Sushi, ramen, gyudon, tonkatsu, kishimen
Background music that makes you want to eat anything
Don't ever begrudge individuality
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather 'round!
Surprise it, toward an unlooked direction
Even if it's pointless let's go, a treasure before long
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you want to cry...
Wholeheartedly cry and cry, it's gratifying
Every day feels refreshing
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Even if you don't want to you'll cheer up
for sure, and yeah, you'll smile
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
Dream
It's no good!
I can't write a thing! I'm totally in a slump.
The nice young guy Sakuya and the delinquent Takuto...
They're exact opposites.
So, who should the main character end up with?
Sakuya
Erika
Likes
Takuto
They're both totally incompatible.
On top of that, Takuto is a scoundrel...
Takuto
Likes
It's fine by me...
If, instead of Erika, it's YOU who entertains me, that is.
L-let go already!
Why I can only move forward
if it turns into another kind of story?!
Time for a change of pace.
It's lovely
The song's way too good
Amazing!
A beautiful song
Teishotoku-P
This is Teishotoku P.
The speed at which every day goes by changes...
Teishotoku P's new song really is great!
How does he write such wonderful songs?
What kind of a job does he have?
What type of girl does he like?
He probably already has a girlfriend, huh?
Is there no way for me to convey
this passion I have for him?!
Oh! There might be!
The truth is...
I've bought all the equipment needed to do "Sang_It."
Note: A subcategory on J-website Niconico
where people upload their own songs
I was in pretty high spirits,
or maybe it was just a whim,
but it was a pain to get working, so I gave up.
Still, if this will convey my feelings to Teishotoku P-sama,
maybe I'll give it another shot!
The song I uploaded the other day
was a rather good one, if I do say so myself.
As usual, my numbers aren't
going up that much though...
Ah, yes.
It was a clear afternoon like this,
when I wrote that song...
Welcome!
Sorry. I didn't make an appointment...
Well, that's okay!
Are you a first-timer?
Yes.
This way, please.
His "sense" as a hair stylist is somewhat broken.
This will not turn out well...
Good. Okay!
All I do is look ahead
and before long, I begin to walk unsteadily
In the past I would often get lost, but
Hang on a sec. I'm gonna go get
some random magazines.
Now, in order to get lost, there are hardly any choices at all
Here you go.
100 Middle-aged Ladies
Found in Town
Bimajo VS Bumajo
I think you'll like these.
We Still Prefer Amateurs
So, how much would you like to cut off?
About five centimeters on both ends, please.
Five centimeters, huh?
That seems kinda half-hearted.
Wouldn't you rather go all out
and cut about 20 centimeters?
That would just be a buzz cut!
I feel more relaxed when it's longer, so...
A haphazard me always just had excuses lined up
Well, that's okay.
In the white moon that I see in broad daylight
I can no longer draw lines as clear colored as they were yesterday
It's strange.
The lyrics are racing throughout my body...
My cat really is cute, you know.
Okay, I'm going to raise the chair a little.
Now I'm lowering it!
The view from the top of the hill is beautiful
Okay!
Just like as if it was a creation
Now it's wash time!
The distinction between reality and ideal also becomes unclear
Dawn comes again
By the way, are you a cat fan?
Well, I wouldn't go that far...
Huh?
So, do you like them? Or hate them?
You like them?
Yes.
In a world where only "yes" can be said
Which do you think is smarter, a dog or a cat?
You'd think it would be a dog,
because they can do a lot of tricks, right?
Will my voice reach you all the way?
Nope! You'd be wrong. Sorry.
In a world that's full of information
You know how cats don't listen to what you say?
That's because they can think and act on their own.
My words will probably get twisted and unraveled
Well, if we're talking about Motchinyan,
I do rather like that.
Wait, what? What's that?
It's a character. A cat.
Oh, really?
Yeah, easily
What a heartbreakingly tender song...
4:20...
Nothing's changed at all.
Something like that happened, and then...
Yeah, it was a song I made on impulse.
I tried singing "16:20" ver...
I tried singing "16:20" Ver. akane
I sang this for you.
If you don't mind, please listen to it.
"Tried singing" it?
Someone sang that for me?
I tried singing 16:20 Ver. akane
I sang this for you.
If you don't mind, please listen to it.
Let's see.
Th-this is...!
I... I really uploaded it!
Please let it reach him...
Oh, Teishotoku P!
This is amazing...
Thinking back on it, I'm getting angry again.
Hey, Kikuchi.
What's with this notebook?
Mathematics
Akane Kikuchi
I thought I'd jazz it up a little!
This sort of decoration hardly counts as quality...
Still, you're uncannily good.
Well, of course!
This one's future dream is to become a manga artist!
Hey! You...!
What are you talking about?!
Oh. Kikuchi, have you already
decided on a career path?
C-career path?!
Uh, I don't seriously think I could become one, so...
I'm telling you, you can!
I think it'll be easier than humanity
deciphering the C-value paradox.
It's not like that. Really!
Dream...
A dream, huh?
Huh? Then what is it like?!
It's finally here...
Since when, I wonder
Did your voice become a special sound?
A one-of-a-kind, original CD!
Still...
Though this was the smallest count, 200 CDs is a lot.
I'll bring in 100 of them to the event venue,
and probably save the rest for mail orders.
Vocaloid Meister...
A fan-manga exhibit and pop-up sales event
held several times a year.
A number of Vocalo Ps that have
worked on famous songs also participate.
A lot has happened for me to get to this point.
But now, I've made these songs the way I wanted...
General comments
It's lovely
So nice
I'm here today again
Whoa!
You sure make nice songs
Teishotoku P-san, all of your songs are wonderful
And there are people who say that they like them.
I tried singing 16:20 Ver. akane
This is akane. This is the first time
I challenged myself to Sang_It.
Teishotoku-P-san, I am a huge fan of yours.
I will continue to always support you.
Someone even sang one for me!
I sang this for you.
If you don't mind, please listen to it.
I will be part of the event.
My booth space is S-23b.
Akane-san.
Wow! For real?!
I'm definitely going!
She's one of the few fans I have,
and she sang my song.
And she's coming, is she?
Then we shall meet for the first time.
Oh! You're so lucky, Robo!
Looks like Majo is reading your fortune!
Yes.
If you like, I can take turns reading all of your fortunes.
For real?!
So, Robo, what're you having her predict?
The year is coming to an end soon, so-
It's about your fortune for next year?!
I thought I'd have her tell me what fortune
I'll draw when I visit the temple for New Year's.
Wait, can you get a fortune
about a fortune you'll be told?
Here we go!
I believe you'll draw the "Excellent Luck" fortune.
Really?!
I'm next!
Okay.
A warning has been given to not eat cold things,
to prevent getting an upset stomach.
My stomach?!
It's not like its summer, so I'll be fine! No worries!
Sorry for the wait. Wota-san, what would
you like to know about the future?
Uh, well... I mean, on Christmas Eve,
will a certain someone...?
No, forget it! Never mind!
Huh? How come?
W-well, if the answer is too shocking,
I could get all anxious or...
I understand.
Well then, let me give you
my treasured good luck charm instead.
It's a mummified alpaca fetus.
Y-y-y-y...
You can keep that!
Vendor Unload Times
Group Entry &
Pamphlet Distribution Times
Doors Open
General Admission Begins
Direct Sales Event
In this area alone...
New release 500 yen
I have old songs too!
Teishotoku Studio
Peanuts
T-shirt 3000 yen
the oxygen grows thin.
A-121
Line Ends Here
Sure enough, it's different if you're a famous "P."
I knew this already, but... I'm just twiddling my thumbs.
Today is finally the day!
I'll be a little late, but I'll be there!
"I look forward to it."
I kind of get the feeling that this person...
I got my nails done for the event.
Is somewhat "JK" (high school girl).
Mathematics
I thought I'd jazz it up a little!
Kikuchi?!
Akane Kikuchi
Is she the "akane-san" who sang my song?!
And now she's on her way here?
A student is...
coming to her homeroom teacher's booth?!
No, it can't be.
A coincidence like this just isn't possible!
Finally... I finally get to meet him!
The man I so admire...
Teishotoku P!
Vendor Unload Times
Group Entry &
Pamphlet Distribution Times
Doors Open
General Admission Begins
Direct Sales Event
It's pretty quiet for both of us, huh?
Indeed.
It's like we're instant yakisoba
that hasn't been drained properly.
Right?
Y-yeah...
What does that even mean?
No, now's not the time for that.
It won't be long before Kikuchi...
I wonder where S-23b is...
gets here!
Come to think it, though, it's not like I've done
anything to be ashamed of,
so I should just act normal and with dignity, right?
Still, when she finds out the person
she admires is someone she knows...
Wouldn't that be a disappointment?
Excuse me.
Would you mind letting me borrow that towel for a bit?
Oh! It's around here!
Teishotoku Studio
Gero Onsen
What type of genre does this person belong to?!
Uh-um, one copy of the new release, please.
Here.
I can't get a good look at his face, but...
he's gazing at me so intently!
Without my glasses, everything is indistinct, but...
there's no doubt that it's Kikuchi.
U-um, I'm "akane"!
I reached out to you on social media a while ago.
Thank you for all your support.
What?
He barely talks!
If I speak too much, she might figure me out.
Maybe he's just the quiet type.
U-u-um! I-I've really been looking
forward to meeting you!
I couldn't sleep at all yesterday!
It's kinda hard to breathe!
It's like there's no oxygen!
Teishotoku P-san...
I absolutely adore you!
I said it!
Yeah, yeah. I can understand that.
That feeling where you can't help but be elated.
It's like peanut butter that's been
left to sit overnight, right?
That would get anyone excited!
Who the hell is this?!
And what's this about peanut butter?!
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean to butt in.
Who the hell is this?!
And what's this about peanut butter?!
Um...
Wh-what was I saying?
Oh, yeah.
U-um, the first time I encountered
one of your songs, Teishotoku P-san,
I'd been fighting with a friend.
I was close to hating myself but...
The more I listened,
I was able to realize my true feelings.
Ah! I'm friends with her even now, at high school.
It's like an inseparable bond or something...
Actually, I...
Well, it's not music,
but I'm trying to do creative work too.
I-it's just manga, but...
Oh! I'm nowhere close to being able to
show it to other people, though!
The truth is, I'm really terrible!
I'm not good at, like,
drawing joints of the human body...
Things like knees are really hard!
Gah! I'm going more and more off topic!
A-anyway! When I listen to your songs,
it's like the creativity just rises up inside me.
It's like they nudge me forward, and...
they encourage me!
I went on about myself way too much!
I should just hurry up and leave!
Th-that's why I'll do my best to be able
to show you my work someday!
I'm sorry for taking up so much of your time!
Please stay healthy!
Was that... a good thing?
To deceive her like that...
I will always always support you.
I like you a lot.
To not return her kindness.
Was that really for the best?
Go after her.
I can watch over your space.
It's like when something is stuck in your teeth
and suddenly comes loose,
and when you chew it, it's spicy
because it's black pepper.
Everyone's felt that way sometimes, right?
That's the way you'll end up feeling.
Well? Go on! Go!
What could this mean?
He's been making nonsensical
metaphors this whole time...
I don't know what they mean!
Generally...
it's the ones who overly rely on metaphors
who are the absolute worst at them!
Every time that guy made some abstract expression,
my emotions were once again reset.
And yet...
Thanks to that, I was able to calm down.
I am a teacher!
Facing a student's sincere feelings head-on...
that's what makes a teacher!
Kikuchi!
The truth is, I am Teishotoku P.
Huh? Sensei, what are you doing here?
I'm sorry if I've crushed your expectations,
but this is the truth.
I am actually Teishotoku P.
That's a good one. What are you...?
Gero Onsen
I only just realized that you are akane-san, and...
Wait.
I thought you would be disappointed,
so on the spur of the moment, I opted to mislead you.
But that was a mistake.
Wait, wait, wait, WAIT!
I'm sorry.
What is this? What's going on?
What does this mean?
So then, that...
That...
And that...
All of that...
And even earlier...
everything up till now has been
directed toward Waseda?!
I-I wanna die!
I want to just disintegrate and
be blasted to far reaches of outer space!
It's because of people like you, who said they
liked my songs and always supported me...
I think that has what allowed me
to continue making music.
I am grateful to you, Kikuchi.
Thank you.
So it's true.
It really...
...was Waseda!
This is just cruel!
It's too much!
How am I supposed to face him at school now?
This is Teishotoku P.
This is my seventh song.
On a tree-lined boulevard
Sure enough... I like him.
Stretched with streetlamps that illuminates a quiet night
He could be a 100 kilogram-plus giant of a man...
Walking around searching for a vending machine,
Or even my homeroom teacher.
But I wonder why, can't find one
It doesn't change my feelings. I like him.
Even though I've gone through this season many times up until now
I'm like a bunny that has strayed into an unknown world
The first snowfall that stains footprints in white
It's not fair! That you're so levelheaded...
That might disappear before daybreak
so kind, and so mature...
That I thought about you so much!
Since when I wonder
And I...
Did your voice become a special sound and start to resonate
I want to get to your level!
Fingertips go numb with cold, heat that lingers in the ears
And if I do...
Would you think about me, even a little?
Sleep again tonight
Excellent Luck
Mathematics
Hmm?
Dear Sensei
Before I graduate, I'm going to make
my debut as a manga artist!
I'm going to become even more famous than YOU.
I look forward to it.
Good work the other day.
I hope you'll support me.
I listened to that CD you gave me.
It had an honest feel to it, and was quite good.
Everything always tastes better when it's fried.
Everything always tastes better
when it's fried.
All said and done, that's what it's like, right?
Song writing, that is.
Mute Conversation
All right!
I'm gonna finish one by spring
and submit it for a manga award!
There's no stopping me!
What do you want to have for lunch?
Just you wait...
Udon noodles and seaweed topped with natto!
Huh. Is that even a thing?
Teishotoku P!
Noisy and loud
But also endearing
The laughter from that day
A story that can't be rewound
The thing about youth is, it's always light and shadows
Inside the darkness
A shining inferior star
Looking back are complicated
Far too beautiful days
Springtime has always passed by unexpectedly by then
Your words reverberate in my heart
Someday springtime will take it all away
Until that day, being stupid is all right
Because I'll run past it
Wow! You're amazing, Majo!
Me, I got crazy diarrhea!
It was Christmas Eve, and I kept
eating snow and got too cold!
Are you a child?
Me too.
My fortune was "Excellent Luck."
Awesome! Majo's predictions seriously come true!
That's kind of you.
Based on past experiences,
I'd say I'm right over 90% of the time.
The truth is...
What should we have her predict next?
How about this year's airborne pollen levels?
Wouldn't it be better to ask a weatherman?
Well then, how about what will
be for dinner for the week?
Just ask your parents that!
When I was reading Baka-san's fortune...
In that case, how about when I'll get a boyfriend?
What if it ends up being 38 years from now?
This card came up as well.
I wouldn't believe it!
You're pretty optimistic...
Oh, I know! How about this:
Finding out which comes first, you achieving
your dream or me getting a boyfriend?