Hey, can I say something amazing right now-
Say it within ten seconds.
Or in a five-seven-five syllable verse.
A haiku, how artistic.
You see, the other day I went to go buy pants.
You know, pants.
That's unusual.
That Baka would go by herself
to buy things like clothes.
I figured I might as well become
an outrageous fashionista
that would make everyone's heads turn,
so I took a look at a lot of things, you see.
You know how they call these kinds of
cropped pants three-quarter length pants?
You know, since they go by full-length,
three-quarter length, half-length, and so on,
as they get steadily shorter, so...
There should be something like
zero-quarter length, right?!
It's the latest!
f I wear that, wouldn't I be at
the cutting edge of fashion?
Wouldn't I be a leader in fashion?
Isn't that amazing? Amazing, right?
Without a doubt, everyone's heads would turn.
Whoa!
This time, even Wota agrees!
Well...
If it's zero-length, then...
That's just plain old underwear, you know.
What...?
Zero-length vesture...
Wear it and cultivate it...
Potato pasture.
Amazing! She actually made a haiku!
Yo
Mic check
JK (High school girl)
Huh?
Yeah!
Isn't that usually where one-two is best?
The moon is a quiet beast during the daytime
What about the moon? That was sudden
Once it becomes night, under cover of darkness
You're so dazzling, wallflower
Want to be like you, lunatic girls
Want to jump on that bandwagon, dazzling JK
The present state of
Always lazing around is okay!
Everything in your mind...
Emptying all that will make you efficient
Is that so? You know?
Animal instinct (Meow!)
A word to society, a maiden's roar
Ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Innovative shout
Ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
So, there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
So, "dass" is German, huh?
Background music that makes you want to
eat curry so hot that you cry!
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather 'round
Mic check JK, one-two, JK, one-two
Anything's okay, everyday
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Sushi, ramen, gyudon, tonkatsu, kishimen
Background music that makes you want to eat anything
Don't ever begrudge individuality
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather 'round!
Surprise it, toward an unlooked direction
Even if it's pointless let's go, a treasure before long
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you want to cry...
Wholeheartedly cry and cry, it's gratifying
Every day feels refreshing
Ooh, round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Even if you don't want to you'll cheer up
for sure, and yeah, you'll smile
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
Fashion
C-c-cabbage and ground meat makes...
Tonight's dish, which will be rolled cabbages!
Today's grocery shopping was a perfect total success!
Hey, you're being slow!
What're you doing, you slowpoke?!
You'll never become strong if you're like that!
Special training! Special training!
Starting tomorrow, we're gonna add
one extra bag per day, all right?!
What're you crying for?!
Hey, you bastards! You shouldn't be bullying the weak!
That's not it. That's sweat.
He's just sweating from his eyes, right?
Huh?!
And you, don't just submit and do what they say!
Also, don't cry!
Who the hell are you?!
What elementary you from?!
I'm a high schooler!
What?! You're lying. I mean...
Right?
If you were a high schooler,
then you'd have more boobs, you know?!
"If you were a high schooler,
then you'd have more boobs, you know?!"
More boobs...
Boobs...
In the graph, circle O is...
Boooooooooobs!
Hey!
Loli-chan?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Oh, n-no! I just remembered something
unpleasant from yesterday and...
What?! That makes me curious!
Um...
Hang on a sec...
Wota, and you Majime, come here for a sec.
Huh? Um...
What's up?
Huh?
Huh? Breasts?
A way to... make them bigger?
You want to make them bigger?
Even if you say that...
It's not as if we did anything special, you know...
That is true.
Plus, being bigger has plenty of its own
unpleasant things associated with it, you see.
Right, right! I've always gotten teased by boys and...
I get that! And they always look at you
when you're running, right?
Plus, they hurt when you run.
They hurt on stairs too, you know?
If you're dressed lightly, there are older men
who unashamedly stare at you, right?
They hurt on stairs too, you know?
They're so dirty, you know?
And because of our breasts, there are
lots of clothes that we can't wear, right?
I can't button my shirts to close them.
Right, right!
If it's a one-piece dress, the front rides up
and the hem length ends up looking weird.
I totally get that! It makes you look a little fat, right?
H-Huh...
I totally don't get it...!
You know, coming from my perspective,
I envy those who are smaller.
The grass is always greener on the other side.
Oh...
Loli-chan.
Listen Loli-chan. Just remember this one thing.
What's important isn't bigger or smaller!
The first time you show your breasts to
the person you like, what's important is…
I'm sorry I'm small.
Don't look at me so much.
Is the shyness you show!
Oh yeah! Either one is good!
Why would you show your breasts
to the person you like?
What?
When? For what reason?
Hey, why? Why?
Loli-chan! Wanna go check out bras
on the way home?!
Really?! I'll go!
She overtly changed the subject, didn't she?
There are bras that can add a cup size up,
and I'll show you around the stores that I recommend!
She totally let herself be misdirected, though.
By any chance, is this the first time
you've been to a store like this?
Yeah!
What?! Then how'd you get by until now?
It was always camisoles with shelf bras.
Or bras for kids that were wireless.
Or stuff like that, so...
What?!
Since my breasts are small,
I didn't think there'd be any that fit me, so...
Here goes!
Huh?! What're you...?!
It's fine. Don't worry.
Why, Loli-chan, you're bigger than I thought.
H-How long are you gonna keep touching?
Oh! Shoot! I couldn't help but go into hunter mode...
Listen, okay? A bra size isn't really
about how big your breasts are...
You see, it's decided by the difference
between the top and bottom.
Loli-chan, your breasts may be somewhat small,
Note: 65B is USA size 30A
but your under is slender,
so you're probably around a 65B.
B?! No way!
B?!
I thought I wasn't even an A cup, so...
Well then, let's pick out something
cute and inexpensive...
Okay?
Yeah!
Whoa!
Huh?
H-How is this possible...?
I've got... Breasts?!
I can cup them in my hands...
Whoa!
School uniform
I can take off the bra straps too...
Whoa!
Bare shoulders
If it's this, then...
Those stupid brats will have to acknowledge...!
That I am...
an onee-san!
Hurry up!
Hey! You bastards!
Special training! Special training!
Stop bullying the weak!
Jeez. It's this jerk again.
Yeah...
Huh?!
Wh-whoa!
They're shocked and cowering now.
After all, I am a B-cup!
This jerk is dangerous!
This jerk has a weapon hidden in her stomach!
Huh?
Whoa! Is it a bomb?!
Crap! Run!
What...?
Bra 101.
If you wear a bra without straps,
it can occasionally slip down,
and you'll end up looking like someone with
super low-hanging breasts, so be careful.
U-um...
Th-Thank you... for saving me... Onee-san!
Oh my. They say that one can
cry so much the pillow gets wet,
but for you to cry so much
that grandma's chest gets wet is, well...
Just what exactly happened?
I wonder what I have to do, in order to become
more mature-looking like Lily...
Bras are dangerous, and my height
won't increase right away, so...
My face?
If it's my face, then will it change
even just a little, if I put makeup on?
For example, even if it's just my eyebrows...!
Hey, Wota, what're you laughing for...?
Huh? I'm not laughing. What about you?
The corners of your mouth are turned up, you know.
Well, I've always had this kinda face.
Anyway, seriously, what're we gonna do about that?
Well, no one's saying anything.
Yeah... That's not something that can be
easily brought up, you know...
Especially those eyebrows...
No can do! I can't stand it anymore!
I'm gonna go tease her a little!
Hey!
Hang on a sec, Tanaka-san!
You're not trying to tease Loli-chan again, are you?!
What's it to you?!
Regardless of how she looks, she's personally
serious about it, so it'd be cruel, you know?!
Then, are you saying that it's better
to leave her alone as she is right now?
You're desperately holding back
on laughing as well, aren't you?
I'm not trying to hold back!
Uh-huh... Then what's with your hands shaking?
She's really holding back!
Be careful not to cause internal bleeding.
Loli-chan.
Lily...
You seem like you've got a different vibe
to you today than usual.
Oh...! Can you tell?
I decided to shape my eyebrows a bit.
Yeah... They're super cute, but...
I-I think that a bit more natural look
would fit you better, Loli-chan.
Hey, if it's okay with you,
will you let me help you out again?
What?! You sure?!
This eyebrow liner isn't coming off easily...
Loli-chan, you drew these by yourself, right?
What did you use?
Um... I shaved them with
the t-shaped razor I had at home,
but since I shaved too much off,
I drew them in with a 2B pencil.
A 2B, on top of a t-shape?!
Hey, there are lots of different things sold
like razors for eyebrows and thin scissors,
so it's better if you use things like that.
Huh!
Also, when you draw them, it's better to use stuff
like eyebrow liner so that it looks more natural.
W-wait! Don't say it all at once! I'm gonna take notes!
Ah, well we might as well start off
with shaping them, okay?
She really doesn't know anything about this stuff.
Th-This makes me...!
So want to kiss her!
Okay, it's done.
Wow! Amazing! Thank you, Lily!
Huh?
What happened to your cheek?
Don't let it bother you.
I was just snuffing out the wretched part of me.
I'm gonna show-off to Tanaka and the others!
Well, well.
Majime!
Look, look!
Oh, all right...
Pardon me.
Based on what I can tell, you're at 36.6 °C,
so I think you're very much at a normal temperature.
However, if you're worried,
then you should go to the infirmary.
Aw! That's not what I meant!
What?!
If only I could become more
fashionable and mature-looking.
In that case, shall we do some studying?
Okay?
Hunter mode
Oh! Robo says that she's already at
the meeting point. Let's hurry.
Aw! This is boring!
It's such nice weather, and all I'm doing is
accompanying Wota on her anime goods hunting...
Aren't there any high school girl-like
high spirited holiday feeling stuff to do?
If you're gonna bitch and moan, then go home.
Oh, it's Majime!
Oh... Tanaka-san.
Whatcha doing? You going somewhere?
Today I have a study group and...
A study group?! You really are boring.
Isn't working your brains even during
a day off, like way too much?
Huh...? Well... That is...
Just because your brains are on vacation all year
long doesn't mean that you get to pick on her.
Huh?! Hey! What the hell?! What're doing?!
Sorry about this, Majime.
My brains aren't on vacation!
Oh, not at all. Take care.
Don't just go ahead and put me on vacation!
And what do you mean, vacation?!
Hello!
Thank you for having us over.
Well, well, come on in.
Th-Thank you for coming.
This is just a little something, but...
Oh my, that's kind of you.
Th-the rooms! I'll show you around!
Let's see! Over there is the living room,
and here's Grandma's room.
And then...
Both of you, hurry up and come in. Come in.
That the day would come that Saku
would bring her friends over...
Thank you for having us over.
Well then, if you will...
But you know, Saku...
The bathroom is here! And this is the toilet!
I don't think you need to show around
every single room, you know....
And then the second floor is...!
Wow!
Amazing!
So, this is Loli-chan's room, huh?!
It's very feminine-like.
Y-You think so?
And you have lots of clothes!
P-Papa and Mama send me lots of them
every month from abroad, you see.
Well then, shall we get started with
today's main subject right away?
Loli-chan's fashion study group!
Th-thank you in advance for your help!
Then, for starters, shall we have you
take off everything?
What? Everything?
Ev-ery-thing.
Okay...
Momoi-san, shall we learn about
how to doubt people as well today?
What?!
Come on! Kanade, don't you get in the way now!
Someya-san, you are one...
I'm glad I came along.
So, which is it? Do I take it off? Or don't take it off?
- Take it off!
- Don't take it off!
Someya-san! You are taking your jesting a little too far!
Y-You know, it's unfair for you
to suddenly get so close like that!
Well, forget about it.
All right! Once more, it's the start of the study group!
Loli-chan, when a girl like you, who's short in height,
wants to wear a long skirt, then...
Miracle change!
Your top should be accented with color
and make the bottom a high waist!
By doing this, you style up!
You are cute!
Next up is, overalls, which tend to
end up looking rather rustic...
Miracle change!
By slipping on a long cardigan,
you turn into a relaxed-cute fashionista!
You're right!
You are relaxed-cute!
You coordinate a boyish-look with girly hair
to create a gap in styles.
S-so cute...
In addition, something like this, where you
loosely wear a course-knit one-piece.
See, even just this is cute, right?
Honestly! You're too cute!
Huh! I see!
Crap... We haven't said
anything but cute for a while now.
Well...
there is simply no other way to describe her...
God is unfair, you know...
Why, you...!
You've been blessed with a body to this degree,
so how dare you ask for more!
You big-boobed buster!
B-Buster?!
At times, obsequiousness and modesty can
irritate people, you know. So, keep that in mind!
M-My apologies.
That was lucky!
Majime, do you want to study
how to become cuter too?
What? Well, of course, if I could be,
then I'd want to, but...
Then let's do that!
Let's go to Majime's house right now,
and then Majime, you can have
a fashion study group too!
Sounds good! Let's go! Let's go!
What?!
Aw! I'm hungry! Let's eat something!
Huh?!
Huh?! Salted green onion kalbi bowl?!
You're kidding me!
Obviously, something like that's gonna be tasty!
Hmm?! Damn it! How dare they season it with
sesame oil! Well of course it's tasty!
Hey, what're you having over there?
Huh?! A soft-boiled egg pork cutlet bowl?!
There it is! How dare they think they can
just make it a soft-boiled egg...! Fine!
Soft-boiled gooeyness is like righteous!
Shut up!
When Wota consumes something delicious,
she loses it, you know...
Of course, it's delicious! Not to mention, it's pork loin!
It's gonna be invincible dripping with fat!
Robo, what's yours?! A juicy deep-fried bowl?!
Are you kidding me?!
It even has tartar sauce over it?!
That's totally breaking the rules! It's like the best!
Big Sis!
My friends are here to hang out right now, but...
Actually, they all really want to meet you, Big Sis.
So, she's Kohaku-chan's older twin sister.
Then that means she's the same age as us, right?
Do they look alike then?
I see.
Then go ahead and make it sound like I've died.
I will not!
Today's visitations have ended
(except Kohaku).
I-I'm sorry. Big Sis is considerably shy, so...
Big Sister, wanna chat with us?
Let's hang out together!
Big Sis, it's not scary!
Oh! A translucent Michael Jackson!
Here goes!
Wow! So cute!
So alike!
Oh no! You tricked me, Kohaku!
Sorry...
Oh yeah! Big Sis is very good at fortune telling!
What?! Hey!
That's amazing!
What kinda fortune telling?
And, there you go...
Wow! Amazing! She nailed it!
What?! Then I want you to read my fortune next!
O-okay...
I wonder if I can get a boyfriend by Christmas.
What?! Me first...
The time is coming soon,
when the one inside me is going to awaken...
Stop! Please stop!
Please don't...! Rage inside of meeeeeee!
Hey!
If you're not gonna eat your meal right away,
I'm gonna clean it up!
Wow! Welcome!
Kanade's friends? Come in. Come in.
Th-thank you for having us over...
Th-thank you...
Jeez. If you'd told me sooner,
then I would've baked a cake or something.
Oh, my apologies. Shall I go buy one
at the cake shop in front of the train station?
Th-This is...!
But that place's fresh whipped cream
is a little off, you know.
Yum! They're like an extravagant salmon-ikura bowl!
Salmon
Ikura
Wow!
So elastic!
Mom?!
Well, she's so cute!
Well, of course she's cute, but...
This girl over here is super pretty too!
Jeez! Mom!
Aw! It's fine! I'm having them share
their youthful essence with me, so...
Oh...!
Someya-san?
N-Now then, once again, the fashion study group starts!
First off, let us take a look at Kanade's closet!
Aye!
Sweats
Shirts
Are you a middle school boy?
I'm not good at thinking up coordinated outfits, so...
In general, I make do with about two or three styles.
You are a middle school boy...
Lily, I'm begging you! Please save Majime!
When you plead that desperately,
that does hurt my feelings, you know...
We've got no choice. We'll go shopping
for clothes again some other time and...
Let's make today a study group about hair styles!
Y-yes!
Aye!
Here goes!
For short hair that tends to end up too boyish...!
Miracle change!
Braided arrangement!
I can't do something like this on my own...
Silky straight with an iron!
I can't do this on my own.
A pompadour-style arrangement with a hair pin!
I don't feel like I could do this on my own...
Wow! Majime, you're cute!
H-huh... But it's not something
that I could do on my own at all.
What?! Hey! What's with that "I can't do this
on my own" thing you keep saying?!
Well, if someone else does it for me,
then I could possibly change temporarily,
but I guess I'm saying that there's no point
if I can't do it on my own.
Hey you! Do you think the girls of the world
just naturally become cute or something?!
Everyone makes an effort, you know! Effort!
Hey! Wait! Please... Don't knead them...
It's the same as that studying you're so good at!
Oh...! Ah...! Not... Not there...
Were you dangling both of these tremendous things
without knowing something like that?!
Well?!
Majime!
Oh...
It is just as you say, Someya-san.
I thought that without a doubt, the women of
the world naturally acquired fashion senses.
I will try to make a little more effort to do so...
Majime! Let's do our best together!
Yes...
It's fine if you understand.
A child who so disliked fashion is...
Let's master fashion together!
Yes. Until we're called fashion leaders!
The influence from friends is amazing...
If I make an effort, I'll be able to become
big like you, Majime, right?
(T-h-a-n-k y-o-u.)
If you make an effort, then for sure!
Thank you very much for today.
M-me too. I really learned a lot!
You're welcome.
It feels like all we've done is
just receive your help, Someya-san...
We should reciprocate in some way.
Plus, I haven't shown my gratitude
for the bras and eyebrow stuff.
What? I already received a lot!
Huh?
You see, that would be...
Lots of...
Side... dish... es!
But since I can't say that...
The fun memories I have of both of you!
S..Someya-san?!
Lily! You're a super good person!
I hope you'll continue to be there for me, okay?
Yeah!
Likewise!
All right! I'm gonna work harder to be fashionable!
Hey Wota, what's up with her this time...?
Stop that. I'm at my limit in a lot of ways right now...
Even the actual person in question...
apparently knows she might have
gone too far this time...
In terms of those bangs...
Instead of becoming fashionable...
Last night, I was up until midnight studying the
fashion site that you told me about, Someya-san.
Oh! Loli-chan's here.
Loli-chan, morning!
Good morning.
Oh... Good mo-
Hey! You guys! Don't you be hurting
Loli-chan's feelings like that again!
It's best if you think about
deoxyribonucleic acid, you know.
Just what exactly happened?
You look cute like a kokeshi doll.
No! Grandma, please give me your bangs!
There you go talking nonsense again. This child...
Noisy and loud
But also endearing
The laughter from that day
A story that can't be rewound
The thing about youth is, it's always light and shadows
Inside the darkness
A shining inferior star
Looking back are complicated
Far too beautiful days
Springtime has always passed by unexpectedly by then
Your words reverberate in my heart
Someday springtime will take it all away
Until that day, being stupid is all right
Because I'll run past it
What?!
LIKE
Not fair!
Stop being
so clingy!
What?! Long blond hair and sanpaku eyes.
Younger in age delinquent bottom!
Black-haired glasses-wearing average Joe.
Crybaby working adult member of society
and bullied child, who's a top?!
That's playing dirty!
In the middle of
consuming something delicious.
Is there anyone who wouldn't like that?
On the contrary! Thank you very much!
Hurry up and get married!
Let me deposit gift money to you!
For crying out loud, get buried in the same plot!
I'll even buy the grave! Hurry up and
let me deposit money for you! Thank ya!