Can I say something amazing right now?
You don't have to say it.
Hey...
What?
Can I say something amazing right now?
And I told you, that you don't have to say it.
In fact, don't say it.
What?!
Robo, you wanna hear it, right?
Svante Arrhenius advocated for the theory
of panspermia as the origin of life.
A mathematical formula that he solved
when he was five years old,
was later on reconstructed as Hubble's Law,
where a new hypothesis was established that
the universe is expanding by the speed of light.
If it's just amazing as that, then...
No, I've got nothing quite that amazing...
In that case, it can be something on par with
having discovered a hundred yen,
that had fallen underneath a vending machine.
You've suddenly lowered the bar there.
You could at least expect something as amazing as
if I'd won two consecutive Gorigori-kun prizes.
Then, something on par with the first time Japan
was successful with breeding lowland gorillas.
I can't tell which one is just how amazing or not!
Then something on par with a lowland gorilla picking up
one hundred yen from under a vending machine,
and buying a Gorigori-kun
that ends up winning a prize. Oo oo!
No, isn't that in its own way, pretty amazing?
Then, fine! Jeez!
BUDDA
Let's go with something like I picked up
a hundred yen from underneath a vending machine,
and bought a Gorigori-kun!
If it's that, it's embezzlement of
a found article and it's a crime.
Then what am I supposed to do?!
All right! It's fine, just hurry up and say it.
You know...
What's wrong? Hurry up and say it.
I forgot what it was, I was trying to say.
Yo
Mike check
JK
Huh?
Okay! Isn't that usually where one two is best?
So the moon is a quiet beast during the daytime
What about the moon? That's suddenly out of the blue
Once it becomes night, under cover of darkness
There you go being sparkly, wallflower
Want to be like you, lunatic girls
Want to jump on that bandwagon, sparkly JK
The present state of always lazing around is okay!
You're efficient if you can totally empty your mind of all thoughts
Is that so? You know? Wild instinct (Rawr!)
A word to society, a maiden's roar, ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Innovative Shout, ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
So there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
So dass is German, huh?
A BGM that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather round.
Mike check JK, one two, JK, one two
Anything's okay, everyday
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Sushi, ramen, gyudon, tonkatsu, kishimen
A BGM that makes you want to eat anything
Don't ever begrudge individuality
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather round!
Surprise it towards an unlooked direction
Let's go even if it's pointless. A treasure before long
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you want to cry...
Wholeheartedly cry and cry. It's gratifying
Everyday feels refreshing
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Even if you don't want to you'll cheer up
for sure, and yeah, you'll smile
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Everyday
Lily
A cool type...
A boyish type...
Oh! That girl's cute too!
So, the rumor was true that there's a lot of cute girls...
Mm-hmm! Yum!
A transfer student at this time of year.
That's unusual, you know. Hmm?
They say a transfer student's coming...
Apparently, she's really pretty.
Potato chips
Garlic chive gyoza flavor
It stinks! But you can't stop!
That stinks! What the hell are you eating?!
Garlic chive gyoza flavored potato chips!
Garlic chive gyoza in the morning
is a minor act of terrorism, you know!
It's a limited time product.
And, eating it together with this rayu chili oil
shiitake mushroom flavor makes it taste so good...
Oh! The "amazing" thing I was trying to
say this morning was about this!
Wow! She's super cute!
What a killer body!
Be quiet.
It's rather sudden, but starting today,
we have a transfer student coming to this class.
Would you mind giving a
simple introduction of yourself?
Yes sir!
How do you do? I am Lily Someya.
My father is Austrian, and my mother is Japanese.
Oh, but I grew up in Japan,
so I can only speak Japanese.
Please call me Lily.
What is with this social disparity?
Yeah, you think so?
She's not that different than me, right?
Uh...
Everyone, it's nice to meet you.
My favorite things are girls.
The things I don't like are males!
Hmm?
Talented person
Beauty
Normal
Talented person
Uh... All right.
I've arranged a seat right up front, so take a seat.
What? In that case, please make it the very back row!
I won't be able to survey
the back of everyone's cute heads!
Weirdo
It's definitive!
Nice to meet you, neighbor.
You're an awfully weird person, you know.
What? You think so?
You go, Tanaka-san...
You said what no one else could...!
You don't like men? Why?
What?! Because their very existence is dirty?
Their existence?!
The rest is, how do I put this,
a physical condition kind of thing too,
where if I touch or get touched by a man,
I get an allergic reaction.
For real?
Oh yeah! So, if I even touch just a little like this,
my whole body breaks out in hives and...
Huh?
Uh...
That transfer student also has a dragon crest...
On top of that, it's all over her body...
By any chance... is she a comrade too?
Hey Yamamoto.
Ew! Why?! Why, when you're a girl?!
Take your seat.
Regarding factorization, what is
most fundamental as well as important, is...
Whoa! Rayu chili oil shiitake mushroom flavor!
It goes well with the cold rice of my bento too!
What's up with you, Wota?
You listening to that Pukari-Pe again?!
You mean Vocalo-P...
I wonder why...
Up until now, something like that
has never happened before...
By any chance, that girl...
Has "one"?!
No, no, no matter what, something like that's just not...
Sainotama Girls' High School
This is a girls' high school after all...
Why, of all things, is Tanaka-san in
the women-only passenger train car?!
Oh! Lily!
I've been found out immediately!
On top of that, she's coming over here super-fast!
Tanaka-san, I see that you use this train car too.
Nah, today was just by chance.
Everywhere was crowded,
so I thought I'd try it and got on.
Whoa!
Just right now, due to the
emergency stop button being pressed,
we have made an emergency stop.
Please wait a moment while we conduct a safety check.
That was close! That totally scared me...
Lily, you okay?
Uh, what's that look about?
To be disliked that much is, well...
So, this is how it must feel for the old guys in this world...
Hey, what's with that wall?
Um, I was thinking that maybe I'll need
dictionaries in order to study Japanese.
I'm more surprised at the number of
tissue boxes than the dictionaries, you know.
Oh, well I kinda have chronic sinusitis.
You've totally mastered Japanese, haven't you?
Come to think of it, you said you "can only speak
Japanese" during your self-introduction, you know.
Not that I care, but...
I gotta be careful with this girl.
What the hell?! Don't freak out that much.
You're a rude jerk.
S-sorry... But, you're face-
Face?!
There's nothing I can do about my face.
Whatever. I'm gonna sleep.
Huh? Y-you're gonna sleep?
That was fast!
What's with this girl...? I totally can't figure her out...
But, no matter how you look at her,
she's a normal girl, right?
Well, she's not my type, but...
Like...
What? "Like"?!
Like empty stomach and beef.
"Empty stomach and beef"?!
Actually, isn't that normal?
I'll look it up, just in case.
"Empty stomach and beef."
I wonder if it's a proverb or something...
H-hey! What're you doing,
eating natto openly at school?!
On top of that, it's not even lunch break yet, you know!
Anyway, it stinks! It stinks!
Huh?! Whatever I choose to eat is my choice.
What? You don't like natto?
I hate it!
Anyway, how can you even put something
that smells like that in your mouth?!
Unbelievable!
Unbelievable! I've had enough of this seat!
Sensei! Please let me change seats!
I'm begging you! I can't stand it any-
Noooooo!
Very well. I'll allow the seat change.
Lily
Over there is...
Introduce me to your boyfriend's friends!
A group that's high in social rank
among the class cliques.
I'll ask him next time.
Over here's also high in social rank
among the class cliques,
This is only if my rank goes up
in the next nationwide mock exams.
You're so lucky Mika, to have a dad like that.
but they're the honors student group, huh...
The next class is in another room.
The three of us should go together.
Over that way is the normal girls' group and...
And that group over there is...
No really, I'm telling you,
this time for sure it's amazing!
The lowland gorilla I saw on the internet was
amazingly good-looking and in the next cage...
Kinda unclassifiable.
Since my bangs have grown out quite a bit,
I probably need go to a beauty salon soon.
Mikami-san!
Huh? L..Lily-chan!
Wanna come with me to the clothing classroom?
Let's go.
Y-you sure?!
That a lowly one like me should walk alongside
a sparkling girl like you, Lily-chan,
who's living life to the fullest.
What's up with that? I don't get it.
Lily-chan, you're really cute and popular,
but you're unpretentious,
so it's easy to talk to you, you know...
Yeah, you think so?
And you're also nice to someone like me.
I wish I could become like you, Lily-chan...
This! This is what I mean!
I keep my high social rank in the girl's world.
At the same time, I don't belong to any one
specific group and I get along with everyone.
Oh, it's Lily-chan!
She looks cute again today.
Is she a comrade after all?
I stay away from anything troublesome.
Ah! Feels so good!
I think everyone is well aware of the tag
that is on the inner side of clothing.
As to who someone like me has on her mind is...
Today, we will learn in detail on how to read this tag.
Along with an exceptional appearance that
appeals to girls; a sincere and caring personality.
This tag is based on household goods laws and...
Without a doubt, at this school, she's the
number one popular girl, Kanade Ninomae.
Like cotton and silk...
So, why is it...
When ironing and such...
That she's observing Tanaka-san...
And taking notes...?
Things that need to be paid special attention are listed...
What was that, just now?
That was Kikuchi-san just now.
That was the sound of her thinking about BL stuff.
Oh! That was me. Oh, e-excuse me, thank you.
Here go you.
What kinda noise is that?!
Thank you very much.
Anyway, don't blame it on me!
Also, don't say stuff like BL during class!
Hmm... I get it. So, that's it.
Then, I'll say boys' love.
Don't say boys' love either!
All right, now...
I-I've liked you, all this time...
It's weird, right? Since we're both girls...
No, not at all...
I guess I'd call it love at first sight and-
I'm sorry...
I really appreciate your feelings, but...
Right now, my duty as a student is...
Kanade!
Someya-san?!
I saw that!
You're awfully popular with the girls, ya know!
Please don't tease me.
"What's so good about me, anyway?"
Or so your expression seems to be wanting to say.
It's like I get the feeling that everyone is
judging me just by appearance and...
See? I knew it.
As for me, my only possible strong point
is mental arithmetic...
And I can only go so far as ten digits...
Actually, isn't that pretty amazing?
Do you think so...?
You know, Kanade, isn't it because you
so easily lend a hand if you're asked,
that people immediately misunderstand you?
I was hoping you could teach me how to study...
Sure!
We're short a starting lineup player
for the next game again, so...
If you don't mind that it's me...
Helping a person in need is the obvious thing to do.
You know, there always seems to be that kinda girl,
who's oblivious to her own popularity!
I-if that's the case, then Someya-san,
you're also a popular girl too!
Oh please.
A whole lot more than me!
Well, I'm popular because I try to be popular.
People live their lives with
far more self-interest, you know.
Self-interest?
Yep. Even now, I'm...
Hey, look at those two! Isn't that kinda amazing!
The two of them together is as
equally extravagant as an uni-ikura bowl!
Uni (sea urchin)
Ikura (salmon roe)
A feast for the eyes!
I'm using Kanade in order to
make myself stand out even more...
Maybe I should toy with her a bit.
Hey, if you're that unwilling to be popular,
then why don't you become an idiot?
What?
There's already one nearby, who's a good example.
Why don't you imitate her?
You're making the effort to takes notes
and study her daily anyway, right?
You've got that "How did you know about that?" look.
It's all quite obvious, you know.
Or, the person you actually want to study,
is someone else...
Perhaps.
Someya-san!
Please.
Regarding that matter...
Please keep it a secret!
C-close!
Too close!
Too close in many ways!
Th-this is... In a scene like this,
the next thing that happens is...
Without a doubt...
This!
Oh, it's the first bell...
Our conversation went too long. Let's hurry!
I'd planned on toying with her,
but I got toyed with instead! Scary!
Oblivious to their own popularity type girls are scary!
Well then, first of all, pair up
and do warm-up exercises!
Yes ma'am!
If you don't mind, Loli-chan.
Oh. S-sure.
She's like... an adult woman.
Okay, next!
H-hey...
Wh-what do you have to do,
to get an adult b-body like yours?
I-I went ahead and asked...
I haven't really done anything in particular but...
If I had to say, then...
To get an adult body...
I guess it would be to have
the person you like touch you a lot...
Oh...
Oh, that's it?!
If that's the case, I have that done every day!
What? Every day?
Yeah! Every night before I go to bed,
I get patted gently. By Grandma.
Grandma!
Saku, you're quite the cuddler, you know.
Grandma...
Loli-chan, do you know the topic about
just how babies are made?
Of course, I do!
I'm already a high schooler, you know!
Idiot! You making fun of me?!
R-right. Sorry...
A-A man and woman who like each other
write a letter that says they "want a baby" and...
They submit it to the country
and when that gets accepted...
the two of them get naked and hug each other, right?
What's that about "accepted"?! And "country"?!
W-well, to be totally honest, it's only recently
that I found out the details, though.
I heard it from Tanaka.
That jerk!
What?! Did I say something like that?
Don't remember!
You may have meant it as a joke,
but that girl is quick to believe things, you know.
If you leave her alone, she'll eventually figure it out.
Loli-chan's the one who'll be embarrassed, you know?
Shut up! You're being overprotective.
I'm saying this for Loli-chan's sake here!
If you spoil her, she won't turn into
a decent adult, you know!
What?! You of all would say that?!
It's because it's me, that I can say that!
It's a marital dispute.
It's a marital dispute of a family
arguing over their child's upbringing.
You're not in any position to say that!
Oh fine! I got it!
Then I should just go tell her the truth, right?!
Loli!
You know that topic I told you about before...
Hey! You plan on saying it right now?!
What? What topic?
You know, about how babies are made...
The truth is...
a man and woman-
A...
A-A man and woman smash their meats together,
and they say that's how they're made!
Oh...
Why do they smash their meats together?
What does that mean?
Right...!
I-I'll explain it properly, once I've
mentally prepared myself, so just wait!
I'm not cool with this!
Why is it that among the girls,
I'm the only that makes you break out in hives?
Even if you ask me that, I don't know why either.
You...!
By any chance, do you think that I'm a man?
I... I don't think that! At this time...
In the first place, when one talks about men,
there are children and elderly and all sorts of them,
but do you have something like,
which ones are bad and which ones are good?
I don't know about that either.
Well, then...
Number one. A male baby.
1. Male baby
Two. A male in drag.
2. Male in drag
Three. A male cat.
1. Male baby
2. Male in drag
3. Male cat
Four. A male goliath frog.
1. Male baby
4. Male goliath frog
2. Male in drag
3. Male cat
Five. The statue of David.
1. Male baby
4. Male goliath frog
2. Male in drag
5. Statue of David
3. Male cat
Six. A stamen.
1. Male baby
4. Male goliath frog
2. Male in drag
5. Statue of David
3. Male cat
6. Stamen
If it was among these?
I haven't touched most of them, so I don't know!
Plus, what is up with that
number four, goliath frog?
It's the world's largest frog. Dontcha know?
I didn't know that!
In her case...
Most likely, rather than being allergic to men,
it's some kind of androphobia.
Oh! Robo!
She perceives men as something
that is harmful to her.
If you put it the other way around, as long as she
doesn't perceive this, then it doesn't appear.
I will now prove that.
Prove?
Try putting this on.
I've seen that on a certain ranking TV program!
While in a state of being blindfolded,
we will each randomly touch your hand.
Even after that, if you react to only Baka's hand,
then your radar is genuine.
If you don't react, then it's just in your head,
and you are self-inducing allergies to appear.
I-I see...
As long as you slowly change your mindset,
then there is room for improvement.
Robo, you're seriously smart, you know!
But, why're you carrying around something like this?
It's for camouflage purposes to doze off during class.
Now that's dumb of you! As if you could hide that!
I'll give it a try!
I want to properly know about myself,
and if this physical condition could change...
I get the feeling that I could take a little step forward.
Lily...
So, it's been hard for you up until now, after all.
That's why...
Please go ahead!
That only makes it look like you're just making fun of us!
Well then, we're going to start right away, okay?
Yeah!
Thump!
A cold hand...
I wonder who it is. I can't tell, but it seems okay.
Next person's going to touch now.
Thump!
This time it's warm and soft.
I'm totally fine with this one too...
Maybe I'm okay after all...
Okay, next then.
It was slimy! Something was slimy just now!
Right now, something large and slimy
that isn't a hand was...!
Oh! Oh!
It's the goliath frog!
You put a male goliath frog on me, didn't you?!
My hand is a goliath frog...?
Why?! Why?! Why're you bringing
a goliath frog to school?!
Can you even bring one?!
It's supposed to be the world's largest, right?!
That girl's radar is genuine...
Yeah.
What about the Washington Convention?!
What was that last one? What was it?!
By any chance, was it David?
Did you mash up and smear a stamen on David?
I'm the only one who's an amphibian...
Girl
Amphibian
Was it a combination trick of David and a stamen?!
Noisy and loud
But also endearing
The laughter from that day
A story that can't be rewound
The thing about youth is, it's always light and shadows
Inside the darkness
A shining inferior star
Looking back are complicated
Far too beautiful days
Springtime has always passed by unexpectedly by then
Your words reverberate in my heart
Someday springtime will take it all away
Until that day, being stupid is all right
Because I'll run past it
Someone's calling me...
It's an awfully nostalgic voice...
Yamamoto!
Career Guidance Room
Yamamoto, do you have any idea
why you were called here?
Nopee.
That word doesn't exist in Japanese, Yamamoto.
This is the preferred course request form
I passed out recently.
Well, there's one person who hasn't turned it in yet,
so this is better than not turning it in, but...
Course Selection
Circle the course.
Humanities Course
Science Course
Other ("Still undecided" or etc., feel free to write in)
Both are correct,
and both are also incorrect.
What is this?
Explain the meaning of this.
Sensei, are you familiar with "Schrödinger's cat?"
Huh?!
In other words, that's how it is.
I see. I don't understand at all.
Me
In other words,
there is a me that could proceed to the sciences,
and a me that could proceed to the humanities.
They can both exist.
Me
It can therefore be considered as such.
Science me
Humanities me
I don't know what TV show you were
influenced by, but answer me seriously.
Sensei! I am always serious!
If you're undecided, then ask me for advice.
Even if it's a vague idea,
do you have something you're interested in,
or something you want to become in the future?
Uh...
What's wrong?
Whatever it is, you can go ahead and say it.
Dragon...
I want to ride on a dragon and go into battle...
So, is it like this?
Is my interpretation correct that you want to become
like a sort of entertaining martial artist?
That's not it!
I'm not a martial artist.
I use a bow... I'm an archer!
Are crazy. That's what you are.
I... I want to fight for someone else's sake...
At some point, I will face two ultimate choices.
World peace...
Or the life of my loved one...
No, it's two choices between the sciences or
the humanities that you're faced with right now.
But!
Nevertheless, I have decided!
I will protect my loved one,
even if I make enemies out of everyone!
But despite that... My loved one...
Realizes that and in exchange for world peace,
she ends up sacrificing herself...
Princess!
She's that kinda person, you see. My loved one...
P-probably...
So, sciences or humanities. Which one will it be?
Sensei. You're one of those people who don't get it...
I can't keep... This one...
Under my control any longer...!
Hu...rry! Run...!
While I'm... While I'm still me! Hurry!
Very well. Let's call your parents at once and talk.
Oh, I'll choose humanities.
She decided in two seconds...