Hey, can I say something amazing right now?
AriAri Hamburger
As for how amazing it is-
Yes, yes.
Hurry up and say it. Chop-chop.
You know, embarking on that "first step"
takes courage, right?
Note: Daruma-san ga koronda is essentially the same
as the Red Light, Green Light game
The... Dharma... Doll...
Fell down. Like when you play that game?
No, I'm talking about something on
a much larger scale!
For example...
The human race that first ate natto must've had
some ridiculous amount of courage, right?
Note: Natto is fermented soybeans
That stuff's practically rotten beans, you know.
Normally, would you even think of eating it?
Note: Durian is a large oval-shaped prickly fruit with a pungent odor
The first person who ate durian
must've been crazy too, you know.
Note: The "kusa" part of Kusaya means stinky or stench
Also, someone like Kusaya!
I mean, her name's Kusaya for crying out loud!
She's like beyond imposing!
Note: This is a nod to Princess Kushana from
"Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind"
Put it on top of piping hot rice! Skip the hot mustard!
More! More of the smell!
Give us the smell!
Ah! It's irresistible! This stench!
Long live Princess Kusaya!
Hooray! Hooray!
With that being said, I have decided
to embark on my first step too!
I, Tanaka, will...
at this time, gather up my courage and...!
I'll eat a loaf of bread that's
three years past its expiration date!
Nozomu Tanaka
Scary!
Go right ahead and eat it!
And then get an upset stomach!
That's quite the mold. It's like a forest.
Amazing! Isn't it amazing?!
It's amazing!
Huh?!
Who's that...?
Yo
Mic check
JK
Eh?
Hai!
Soko wa futsuu one two ga best?
Tsuki tte hiruma wa shizuka na beast
Tsuki ga nan datte? Ikinari toutotsu
Yoru ni natte kara kurayami magirete
Kirakira shichatte tereyasan
Ayakaritai lunatic girls
Sore binjou shitai no, kirakira JK
Genjyou shotchuu daradara OK~!
Atamannaka zenbu
Karappo ni dekita nara yuunou
Sou na no? You know?
Yasei no honnou (Nya~)
Seken ni hitokoto otome no otakebi
Wawawawawa~!
Zanshin shout
Wawawawawawawa~!
Tsuki tte usagi inai ndane
Dassu tte doitsugo nan dane
Karakute nakinagara curry ga tabetakunaru BGM!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Wa ni natte
Mic check JK one-two JK one-two
Nan datte OK everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Iki sutte
Shiisuu ramen gyudon tonkatsu kishimen
Nandemo tabetakunaru BGM
Kosei wa zettai dashioshimi shinai
Kusuburu honnou minna de wa! tto
Odorokashite sa, mada minu hou e
Muda demo let's go, itsushika treasure
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Nakitai toki wa
Omoikitte naite naite tsuukai
Soukai na kibun sa every day
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Hora sono ato wa
Iya demo kitto harete sou egao ni narusa
Wa! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
Crispy!
Whoa!
Juicy!
Please excuse me for calling out to you so suddenly.
Majo
Based on uniform and ribbon colors,
I realized that you're 1st-years at Saijo,
so I couldn't help it.
Oh, well that's fine, but...
Um, do you know of a person named Hisui Kujyo?
Kujyo...? I've heard of that name before.
I believe she's in the same class.
I'm her younger twin sister, and my name is Kohaku.
Um, this is a rather intrusive request but...
Would you become friends with my big sister?
The truth is, my big sister tends to
refuse to go to school and...
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen her much.
Since we entered school, I can probably
count on my fingers how often she's shown up.
At this rate, she won't meet the number of attendance
days required, and she'll probably be expelled.
So, that's why you're asking us to be friends with her.
My big sister has been a little different since childhood.
Wanta-kun, what should we play today?
Even with picture books and TV programs,
Hamburgers!
Not what you wanna eat!
rather than the heartful stories
that normal kids delight in...
Jeez Wanta-kun, you're such a pig.
She was the kid that preferred
the kind of grotesque ones
where blood would spray out everywhere.
And then she grew up just the same way,
and rather than real living human beings,
my big sister took an interest in
zombies and occult stories.
Gradually, she ended up
spooking everyone around her.
My big sister isn’t good at communicating for herself,
and even when asked why she's
not inclined to head to school...
She'd only say, "because I don't have friends"
or "because it's boring" or stuff like that...
I see.
Oh! I remember! It's Majo!
Majo?
Note: Majo, meaning Witch
It's the nickname I gave to Hisui Kujyo awhile back!
I see. Well, that fits my big sister perfectly.
Well, we're totally fine with being her friends.
Right?
What?! Uh, I guess...
A-are you sure?!
Never hesitate to do what's right!
Big Sis! Big Sis!
There's a bipedal tsuchinoko at AriAri Burger!
It's fast-moving, so it's might go off somewhere right away!
I'll keep an eye on it at AriAri Burger, so come quickly!
I've gone ahead and summoned
my big sister here right away...!
Younger sister, you sure act fast!
Unlike the older sister, the younger sister
is rather aggressive, I see.
Oh...
Yes... That's why I feel responsible and...
When we were born, I took away all of my big sister's
communication abilities and normal sensibilities.
It was said that maybe my big sister
was left with only remnant trash...
Normal
Leftover remnants
Those were some terrible things
that were said to you, Big Sister!
What's left is for my big sister to come-
Kohaku!
Big Sis, that was fast.
Way too fast!
Who are they?!
Big Sis, they're people from the same class as you.
Y-you tricked me, Kohaku!
Note: A Tsuchinoko is a mythical snake-like creature
from Japanese folklore
I came as fast as I could, because you said
that you'd found a bipedal tsuchinoko!
You came here, seriously believing that?!
You've got a pure heart!
Hello there. I'm the bipedal walking tsuchinoko.
You're gonna complicate things, so you shut up!
I-I'm going home!
Oh! Hey wait! Big Sis!
Big Sis!
Lemme go! I'm going home!
You sure you wanna go home?!
I'm going home! Lemme go!
Even when everyone has kindly said
that they'll be your friend?!
What?
R-really...?
Um...
Of course, it's for real!
Let's go tsuchinoko searching together!
So, you gotta come to school starting tomorrow.
Okay?
P-please let me think about it...
Or so she said yesterday, but...
Is she gonna come? That Majo.
Don't worry! If she doesn't come,
then I'll use this thing I took at the river recently.
Tamassie
I'll summon her with this photo of Tamassie,
the unidentified mysterious animal.
Hey, if you're gonna take a trick photo,
then put a little more effort into it!
Hey, she came!
Majo!
Here! Over here!
G-good morning!
H-hey...
U-um... This is a thank you for
having made your acquaintance.
I pulled an all-nighter and made these last night.
A friendship bracelet?
I-I put in a wish that you would be
friendly to me forever and...
I put my heart and soul into braiding them...!
Soul?
Or rather, this material is...
B-by any chance, is this...?
It's my hair but...
That's freaky!
What's it called? That yummy thing.
That thing where a cut is made around the belly
and then stuffed with rice and stewed.
Wh-when you say a cut is made in
the abdomen and rice put in and it's stewed...
Are you talking about torture?!
Sorry to get your hopes up,
but she's talking about cooking, you see.
C-cooking?! M-my apologies.
So, you were talking about human-eaters.
You just have to link things directly to that stuff, huh?
Aiight! I'll take on whatever you dish out!
I remember now! It's samgyetang!
Samgyetang!
Shut up.
Aw... I'm kinda getting hungry.
Uh... Um... That is...
Well, I do have salicylic acid.
What's that? Is it tasty?
If you drink it straight up, then...
I wasn't able to join the conversations at all...
Shoot! I forgot what Kohaku had told me yesterday!
Noooooo!
It's for friendship bracelets for
Baka-san and the others...
Jeez! Big Sis, why did you have to go
and be so you, Big Sis?!
Listen, okay?
If you don't want your friends to dislike you,
then you can't talk one-sidedly about the occult.
B-but... Then, what do I talk about...?
Don't worry!
"Right!"
"Funny!"
"Cute!"
If you reuse these three for different occasions,
then for the time being, you'll be able to
converse with high school girls!
"Right." "Funny." "Cute."
All right!
Hey you! I haven't seen you before.
I got suddenly talked to!
State your name.
R...
Right.
So, her name is "Right."
Hey you, why haven't you come to school more often?
What kind of attribute are you?
F...
Funny...
What?!
If you don't know, then I'll tell you, but you
shouldn't joke around too much towards me.
Despite how I look, I am the chosen one
with the hidden power of the dragon, you see.
As it were, I am a presence to be feared!
Cute.
She's totally messing with me...!
Y-you bastard! There'll probably come a time
when we'll fight each other.
Don't you forget it!
F-fight?!
I've been disliked without warning...
I wanna eat kalbi!
Well, I do have carbinoxamine maleate.
Is it tasty?
Stop checking every single time.
But that's most important, you know.
It'll be fine if you mix it in with the barbeque sauce.
Oh! Why Kujyo, it's you.
Huh?
It's good you came to school. Sensei is-
happy...
Paranormal photo.
Kujyo-san.
I went and gathered all the printouts
that were passed out while you were absent.
These are the materials from
world history, and these-
R-right thats...
What does that mean?
Am I interpreting it correctly with "right that"
as the demonstrative pronouns,
and "s" as the ending suffix?
Or is it an acronym?
Is she taking the first letters of Reimen,
The napolitan, and Somen noodles,
to make "Right ThatS"...? I don't understand...
I don't understand...
See ya.
See ya tomorrow!
I couldn't talk at all...
Loli!
I already told you, I'm not getting on!
Come on, don't be afraid. Don't be afraid.
It's absolutely impossible for me to have
I'll bite ya!
that kind of friendly conversation...
It's okay if you bite me, just get on!
Enough! I'm going home!
Maybe I'm not cut out for school after all...
Before you go home, get on.
Gimme a break!
Majo!
Let's head home together!
We take the train, so it'll only be part-way, though.
Uh...
F... F... F... F...
Funny!
Huh?! What is?!
Huh?! You don't have to worry about that.
You can say what you want.
That's right.
Like me. I open my mouth and
I say stuff like poop, you know.
You mend your ways.
Um, I...
P-people... And all of you...
That is, I'm scared of being disliked and...
I-I get so caught up just thinking about that and...
I just totally can't do it well and...
That's why... I shut myself away in my own little world...
Because it's safe if I stay there...
Because that way, I can avoid
being disliked and getting hurt...
But...
But... The truth is...
It's impossible to be liked by every single person.
You should just make sure to cherish
the people who do understand you.
Robo-san...
Gah!
Stop! Stop!
Let's stop with this gloomy mood!
It's gonna make me itchy!
Carbinoxamine maleate also works well on itchiness.
For real?! Kalbi does?!
No! She's not talking about kalbi!
"You should just make sure to cherish
the people who do understand you."
Will I be able to do it...?
Big Sis, let's go see a movie!
What?!
The manganji chili pepper
Do you know its flower meaning?
D-do we really have to see something like this...?
I Fall in Love with You Repeatedly
It's bad enough that it's a holiday
and there's a lot of people...
Something like a romance movie is...
That's setting the bar too high.
It's not high!
Big Sis, you've gotta know more
about the trends of normal girls.
But...
You want to be able to have fun conversations
with your friends, right?
Y-yeah...
Then, I'll go buy something to drink,
so wait here, okay?
You're...
In the same class...!
Um... I believe Baka-san said...
I believe Tanaka said...
Loli-san!
Majo!
Has communication issues
Shy at first
Are you in the same class as Big Sis?
What a coincidence.
Twins?!
I'm Kohaku, her younger twin sister.
So, are you here to see "Love with you" as well?
No, that's not it. I mean, yes, that's so,
but it's not as if I came to see this movie
because I wanted to, or anything like that!
Well...
Loli-chan, you may be able to
learn about the adult world,
by watching stuff like romance movies.
An acquaintance strongly recommended me to, so...
M-me too!
You see, I totally don't like these kind of chick flicks!
You're both so difficult!
I... I don't want Ryuji to have you after all!
Hey...! Where are we going?!
You've also got your girlfriend Lisa, you know!
I can't help it, now that I've realized that
Aw! So cool! This makes my heart skip a beat!
the one who's really important to me, is you!
This man... That he's forcing a woman who has
a significant other to go with him is...
But...
Yesterday, when I saw the manganji chili pepper
On top of that, he has his own significant other too.
in your bento lunch box, it made me think...
These bastards...!
They're skipping school like it's no big deal...
That I can't lie to myself, about my feelings anymore!
Their parents would cry if they ever found out!
But, that was Lisa's...
This kind of messy romance is normal?
Do you know the manganji chili pepper's
Humans are scary after all!
flower meaning?
I don't know something like that!
They're not even going out yet,
but they're holding hands!
Then, I'll tell you.
They're like super delinquents...!
It's "I won't let you go, for the rest of your life!"
No! If someone saw us like this...
If you don't want to, then stop me.
Aw! How wonderful!
I love you, Erika...
Aw... How boring that not a
single drop of blood is being spilt...
Yuki...
I'll never let you go again...
I wish someone would get killed soon...
Even if the manganji chili pepper's flower dies...
A maiden who's not even married yet is k-kis...!
Yuki!
What if a child sees something like this...!
The manganji chili pepper
Do you know its flower meaning?
That was good, wasn't it?
Awesome!
That was entertaining!
It was a tearjerker at the end, you know?!
The kind of thinking that as long as
you and your own are happy,
then you don't care about other people is...
horrifying...
It was like the movie was
jam-packed with people's egoism.
The serious main character was corrupted by
a delinquent and steadily became irresponsible...
It's a movie that should've gotten a R12 rating...
Do you go to the movie theater by yourself a lot?
That's like so mature!
What?!
Well, I guess. There' no one of
the same age that I can casually invite, so...
I can understand!
When it comes to high school girls,
just inviting them might make them say
something like "die!", so it's s-scary, right?!
What's with that?
Majo, it's like you don't stand out at school,
I-it seems like... Maybe Loli-san understands me...
but outside from it,
you're kinda different than what I thought.
Uh... Um, Loli-san...
Grandma!
See ya!
It'll be okay.
There'll be other chances to talk to her. Okay?
Yeah.
Baka-san, Wota-san, Robo-san!
Hey, what's up, Majo?
Um...
I came up with just a little game, but...
Oh!
What kind?!
Ways of Dying Amida Lottery
It's a "ways of dying Amida lottery."
Y-you pick the number you want,
and it'll forecast the way you'll die.
There's no need for you to explain it carefully.
We more or less have an idea of what it entails.
You've come up with another icky game again...
Sounds fun!
I figured you'd jump at it.
Then, number three for me!
Three it is...
Ways of Dying Amida Lottery
Let's see... It goes here and then this way and...
Death by accident
Death by illness
Beaten to death
It'll be "beaten to death."
Robo, you got just the right blunt weapon with you?
Well, the efficient thing would be
the corners of the desk or chair-
I'm not getting killed, all right?!
Then Wota, you do it next!
And then you can die in the most pitiful way possible!
Now that's just plain old bad-mouthing!
Target: Kujyo. Codename "Majo", spotted.
Anyway, this only has pitiful ways to die, doesn't it?
Even though that one hardly came to school at all,
she all of a sudden appeared a few days ago,
and before anyone noticed, she'd integrated
herself with Baka and the others.
Suspicious...
How about adding skewered,
skinned alive, or the Brazen Bull?
Danger level three.
I'll continue tracking from here on out.
It's where a person is put inside a hollow
brass bull and fire is put under it to...
Mayday, mayday. Please respond.
Speaking of danger levels,
Those are all executions or torture!
what you're doing there puts you
at the final stage, Yamamoto...
Isn't it wonderful?!
Gah! I'm gonna live!
Loli-san...
Oh, that's the girl from Class 3...
So cute. She looks like an elementary student.
Don't look at me, you airheads!
So scary!
Let's get cleaning!
Yeah, let's go. Let's go.
Anyway...
I wasn't able to talk to her again today...
You should just make sure to cherish
the people who do understand you.
It might be too difficult after all...
Hey. Hey you!
Uh... Huh?!
Up here.
I believe you're... Yamai-san?!
That's just an alias, though.
Majo, or whatever your name is.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
What?! Uh, um...
You may have been able to deceive the others,
but it won't work on me!
Oh, okay... Yamai-san...
What?! Just tell me!
Um...
You know... I can see...
your underwear...
You saw them?
Yes...
I see...
Gotcha!
Huh?!
I-I-I was showing it on purpose,
to throw you off guard, you bastard!
Huh?!
H-h-how's that?! You got thrown off guard, right?!
And it got you rattled, right?!
It's all according to plan!
You better not tell anyone
what you just saw. You got that?!
Y-yes...!
M-m-more importantly,
hurry up and give up your secret!
What?! E-even if you say that...
Secret... Secret...
Big Sis.
It's better if you don't tell normal people
that you like this kind of stuff, okay?
Uh, um...
Actually, I like seeing people's blood,
more than anything...
What...?
E-especially, I can't get enough of the sight of blood,
vigorously gushing out from the carotid artery...
This is...
Oh, and of course, I also love when the
internal organs pulsate after being dragged out...
Oh my!
...far more than I thought...
Like serious!
Hey you two over there!
We've got something to do, you see.
Can you take care of the rest?
Please?
Why the hell do we have to do
your share of things...?
Oh, um... I've got this...
I'll deal with their cleanup altogether, so...
What?!
She's gonna clean both of them up altogether?!
Cleanup done...
Y-you guys, hurry up and go!
Thanks!
Hey! There's no need to go that far, you know!
No need to do it by yourself, you know.
You know... You know... You know...
So kind...
Um, then since things are more or less done,
shall we also just finish up by throwing out the trash?
Y-yeah, sure! Let's do that!
Well then, I'll go get the dustpan, okay?
Yeah, please.
Hey! You dropped some...
Jeez...
Ways of Dying Amida Lottery
Beaten to death
Crushed to death
Death by falling
Death by accident
Death by poison
Death by drowning
Yamai-san! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, I already took care of it.
The trash?! With your bare hands?!
I'll throw out the trash too,
so you go ahead and head home.
What? B-but...!
I-it's fine. It's fine...
When it comes to Majo...
When it comes to Majo, I must not piss her off!
I didn't get to say thank you to Yamai-san...
but she sure is a good person...
Majo!
We've been waiting for ya!
Good job with the cleaning duties.
Sure enough!
Mature women are
aggressively proactive
You want as many Petite Petite
Cosmetic lipsticks as you can get!
Loli!
I'm hungry, so let's eat something!
Oh! Loli-san!
Majo?!
The Choco-bat's yummy, isn't it?
Y-yes!
I-I guess so.
Uh, um...
Loli-san.
U-um... n-next time... t-together... a-a-a movie...
Would you like to go see one...?
Oh, and the next one will be like a heartwarming story
with no delinquents showing up.
I mean, I'm sorry! That's a no, right?
We haven't even gotten close yet!
I'm just gonna go hang myself!
You said it!
You better invite me...
Yes!
Whoa!
Home run
Majo's Choco Bat is a home run!
Wow! It's true! Amazing!
That's the first time I've seen one!
Congratulations.
Lucky! You're so lucky! I wanna home run too!
About today, I...
You just keep striking out!
will probably never forget the taste of the
Choco Bat that I ate together with everyone.
Big Sis.
Please stop preserving anything
and everything in formalin!
Probably for the rest of my life...
Sawagashikute yakamashikute
Demo itoshikute
Ano hi no warai koe
Maki modesenai story
Seishun te yatsu wa zutto hikari to kage
Kurayami no naka
Kagayaku rettousei
Furi kaereba kojiraseta
Utsukushi sugiru hibi
Itsumo haru wa fui ni toori sugita ato
Kimi no kotoba mune ni reverb
Itsuka haru ga zenbu tsure satte shimau
Sono hi made wa baka de ii
Kake nukeru kara
This kind of movie really does
feel heartwarming after all!
Majo and Loli are probably enjoying
the movie about now!
Hmm? Robo, what're you drawing?
I've tried to make one for Baka as well.
A reincarnation Amida lottery.
It's one of those about what you'll become
if you get reborn, right?
Wow! Cool!
Reincarnation Amida lottery
Then, I pick number five!
Face mite
Face mite...