Sawagashikute yakamashikute
Clamorous and noisy
Demo itoshikute
But still charming
Ano hi no waraigoe
The laughter from that day
Maki modesenai story
A story that can't be rewound
Seishun te yatsu wa
The thing about youth is,
zutto hikari to kage
it's always light and shadows
Kurayami no naka
Inside the darkness
Kagayaku rettousei
A dim star that shines
Furi kaereba kojiraseta
Looking back doesn't help at all
Utsukushi sugiru hibi
It was way too good back then
Itsumo haru wa fui ni toori sugita ato
Spring was over before you knew it
Kimi no kotoba mune ni reverb
Your words reverberate in my heart
Itsuka haru ga zenbu tsuresatte shimau
One day spring will take it all away
Sono hi made wa baka de ii
Until that day, being stupid is fine
Kakenukeru kara
Because I'll run through it