Yo
Mic check
HS Girl!
HS Girl
Huh?
Okay! Isn't that usually where one two goes?
The moon is a sleeping giant at night
Switch up to the moon?
We move in silence at dusk
Once it becomes night, under the cover of darkness
There you go, standing out, wallflower
There you go being sparkly, wallflower
You're inspiring crazy girls
I want to be like you, lunatic girls
I wanna be like you, shining girl
I want to jump on that bandwagon, sparkly high school girl
Doing nothing all the time is perfectly fine!
Always lazing around as the status quo is okay!
Reset your mind!
Totally empty your mind
That'll keep you on the ball!
If you do that, you'll be efficient
Really? For real?? It's a feral feel (Rawr)
Is that so? You know? Wild instinct (Rawr!)
Really? For real? It's a feral feel (Rawr)
Really? For real?? It's a feral feel (Rawr)
Is that so? You know? Wild instinct (Rawr!)
A message to society
A word to society
A maiden's roar, wawawawawa~!
A maiden's roar, ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
A brand new cry wawawawawawawa~!
Innovative shout, ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
There really ain't a man in the moon, huh?
So there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
So "Voll" is German, huh?
So dass is German, huh?
A beat that makes you wanna eat  curry so spicy you could die
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
A beat that makes you wanna eatcurry so spicy you could die
A beat that makes you wanna eat curry so spicy you could die
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
A beat that makes you wanna eat  curry so spicy you could die
A beat that makes you wanna eat curry so spicy you could die
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
A beat that makes you wanna eat curry so spicy  you could die
A beat that makes you wanna eat curry so spicy you could die
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather round!
Gather round
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Mic check HS Girlone two
Mic check, high school girl, one two
HS Girl one two
High school girl, one two
Whatever's okay, everyday
Anything's okay, everyday
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dries!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Sushi, ramen, beef bowl, pork cutlet, kishimen noodles
I'll eat whatever to this beat
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat anything
It's always admirable to try and stand out!
Don't ever begrudge individuality
Burning instinct, gather round
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather round!
Show off something completely original!
Surprise it towards an unseen direction
No worries let's go one man's trash is treasure to some
Let's go even if it's pointless, it'll be treasure before long
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you wanna cry...
When you want to cry...
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Crying is all right, let it all out!
Wholeheartedly cry and cry. It's gratifying
Every day is a brand new day
Every day feels refreshing
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll! Dies!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
You can resist all you like but you'll smile for sure!
Even if you don't want to, you'll cheer up and smile for sure
Ooh wee! Wane! Voll Dies! Every day
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Everyday