Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Kikuchi Akane
My dream
I want to be a mangaka!
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Saginomiya Shiori
My dream
Microbiologist
Tanaka Nozomu
My dream
Amazing high school girl
Tanaka Nozomu
My dream
Amazing high school girl
Tanaka Nozomu
My dream
Amazing high school girl
Tanaka Nozomu
My dream
Amazing high school girl
Tanaka Nozomu
My dream
Amazing high school girl
Tanaka Nozomu
My dream
Amazing high school girl
Whoa!
Oh!
Watch out!
I want to be an amazing high school girl.
I want to become an amazing high school girl
and be really popular with the boys.
And then I want to get
a really hot boyfriend and go out on dates.
What an idiot.
Yo
Mic check
High school girl
JK
Huh?
E?
Okay! Isn't that usually where one two is best?
Hai! Soko wa futsuu one two ga best?
So the moon is a quiet beast during the daytime
Tsuki tte hiruma wa shizuka na beast
What about the moon? That's suddenly out of the blue
Tsuki ga nandatte? Ikinari toutotsu
Once it becomes night, under the cover of darkness
Yoru ni natte kara kurayami magirete
There you go being sparkly, wallflower
Kirakira shichatte tereyasan
I want to be like you, lunatic girls
Ayakaritai lunatic girls
I want to jump on that bandwagon, sparkly high school girl
Sore binjou shitai no kirakira JK
Always lazing around as the status quo is okay!
Genjou shocchuu daradara OK~!
Totally empty your mind
Ataman naka zenbu
If you do that, you'll be efficient
Karappo ni dekita nara yuunou
Is that so? You know? Wild instinct (Rawr!)
Sou nano? You know? Yasei no honnou (Nya~)
A word to society
Seken ni hitokoto
A maiden's roar, ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Otome no otakebi wawawawawa~!
Innovative shout, ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-round!
Zanshin shout wawawawawawawa~!
So there's no rabbit on the moon, huh?
Tsuki tte usagi inainda ne
So dass is German, huh?
"Dass" tte doitsugo nanda ne
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat spicy curry while you cry!
Karakute nakinagara curry ga tabetakunaru BGM!
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Gather round
Wa ni natte
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Mic check, high school girl, one two
Mic check JK one two
High school girl, one two
JK one two
Anything's okay, everyday
Nandatte OK everyday
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Take a breath
Iki sutte
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Sushi, ramen, beef bowl, pork cutlet, kishimen noodles
Shiisuu, ramen, gyuudon, tonkatsu, kishimen
A soundtrack that makes you want to eat anything
Nandemo tabetakunaru BGM
Don't ever begrudge individuality
Kosei wa zettai dashioshimi shinai
A smoldering instinct, everyone gather round!
Kusuburu honnou minna de watto
Surprise it towards an unseen direction
Odorokashite sa mada minu hou e
Let's go even if it's pointless, it'll be treasure before long
Muda demo let's go itsushika treasure
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
When you want to cry...
Nakitai toki wa
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Wholeheartedly cry and cry. It's gratifying
Omoikitte naite naite tsuukai
Every day feels refreshing
Soukai na kibun sa everyday
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
So, after that...
Hora sono ato wa
Ooh round! Moon! Dass! Cry!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Even if you don't want to, you'll cheer up and smile for sure
Iya demo kitto harete sou egao ni narusa
Round! Moon! Dass! Cry! Everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry! Everyday
Amazing
Girl's High School
Entrance Ceremony
Long time no see.
Whoa...
Why do you have jam?!
And you're gonna put it on?!
Nasty...!
Euglena
Oh! We're in the same class!
1st-year Class Lists
And...
Kikuchi Akane
Saginomiya Shiori
Tanaka Nozomu
We're in the same class!
1st-year Class Lists
Starting today, you are all high school students.
An infinite future lies ahead of you.
During your three years of high school life...
Hey. So, I made a really big mistake
that can't be undone, but...
Like what?
This school is a girls' school...
Why did you only realize it now?
Because no matter where I looked during
the entrance ceremony, it was all just girls.
You'd already know that by
looking at the high school's name.
I thought it was just the name of the school.
What kind of name is that?
Sainotama Girls' High School
But wait, why didn't you realize it
during the entrance exam?
I was asleep.
How'd you pass?!
Why does being a girls' high school
make it a mistake that can't be undone?
Well, if there are no guys,
then even if I want to be popular with them, I can't!
What's amazing is that you think
you'd be popular if it were coed.
Worst case scenario, I guess there's
the teacher angle, huh?
There's the possibility
that the homeroom teacher
will be a young hot guy who's fresh out of college...
Um, I will be in charge of Class 1-2 for the next year.
My name is Sawatari.
First of all, there are several things
I want to tell all of you, from the onset.
I prefer college women.
Just because I have been
assigned to a girls' school,
I am often looked at enviously by those around me.
Acquaintances have said that
I won't be found out if I secretly seduce a girl,
and there are some jerks who say ridiculous things
like "introduce me", but...
I will say this again and again.
I prefer college women.
I am a graduate of a famous university,
a civil servant,
handsome, twenty-seven years old,
and single with no girlfriend.
But I want you please to bear in mind
that although it may be unavoidable
to develop a crush on me,
unfortunately for you, I will not lean
even one millimeter towards that kind of feeling.
Also, one more thing...
In the situation where a male adult
and a female high school student
get involved and have sexual relations,
the adult will be charged with sexual misconduct,
unless there is parental guardian approval or they are engaged.
However, in the eyes of the law,
if it is a serious relationship,
then it is possible to marry
a female high school student...
However, how would they make it clear
that they are serious about their relationship
or that they are together
with the intent to marry and so on?
Do they get the parental guardian to approve?
For something like that, in most cases
he'd immediately get reported and his life is over!
In the end, a romance with a high school girl
is just a fantasy, you know!
Then why not just change the law!
Idiots!
That is all.
I look forward to being with you all this year.
No good.
No good...
This guy's no good!
Gaaah, I want a boyfriend!
There aren't any chances to meet guys!
Just where do I have to go to meet guys?
Why don't you get a part-time job?
Oh, hell no!
There's no way I'll have people
pushing me around to work like that.
How do the ones at girls' schools
with boyfriends meet them anyway?
Don't they get friends to introduce them
or something like that?
Get friends to introduce them...
No good.
I can't even imagine Kikuchi
having any hot guy friends.
Even if I did, I'd die before
introducing them to you!
Poteriodendron...
Poteriodendron
A Phytomastigina Chrysomonadina
Ochromonas family...
Introduce me to a hot guy friend.
Huh?! Wh-where did that just come from?!
And not like a microorganism or stuff like that.
Uh...
Unfortunately, I don't have
that kind of friend in this lower realm...
I...
... happen to know someone
who's a mage of the Dragonia race.
Except that he just pledged his loyalty
to the princess of the Altania Kingdom, so...
Uh...
That girl's tiny.
So cute.
Kinda like the ones that don't hurt
even if you put them in your eyes?
Grandkid?
Anyway, which class?
Isn't she cool?
Try talking to her.
I wonder if she'd eat candy?
You trying to bait her with food?
I wanna take her home!
I wanna put her up as decoration in my room!
She looked this way!
Damn it...
Yours truly here has a complex
about my appearance, you know.
I gotta make sure nobody looks down on me...
S-Stop looking at me, you scum...!
Oh!
Wha...?!
Whaddya think you're doing? Hey!
Hiss!
I thought maybe, you wanna get on...?
No, I don't!
Then introduce me to a hot guy friend.
What kind of logic is that?!
"Ichi"?
"Hajime"? How do you read that?
Oh...
Ninomae
It is written as the character for one,
but it is read as "Ninomae".
Ninomae?!
Apparently you can read it that way
because one comes "before two".
Oh! I see!
Amazing! Ninomae!
It is rare, isn't it?
I've heard that only about four hundred people in the
whole country have that name, if I remember correctly.
There are apparently a lot of them
in Kumamoto and Niigata.
Huh.
By the way, why do you always have headphones on?
For fashion?
Oh, no...
This is so that I can always
listen to financial Internet radio.
Plus, this way I can check things
like stock prices right away.
Y-you...
You're a serious person, aren't you?!
A serious person?!
Whatever, that's fine.
Introduce me to a hot guy friend.
A hot guy?
Oh, that I don't mind, but what is
the definition of a hot guy?
Even if one were to make an
overgeneralization about hot guys—
for example, there are pleasant types, wild types,
and a variety of others—
In any case, as to whether or not
I have hot guy friends,
I must first think about the definition of a friend.
According to the dictionary—
No good. Everyone here is all useless.
You're the most useless one here of all.
I also tried asking the others,
like Doorknob, Giant Squid, and Greece,
but it's no use talking to them!
Who the hell are Doorknob and Giant Squid?
In a sudden flash of inspiration,
I gave nicknames to everyone in class, you see.
Here...
Waseda...
Oh. That's the homeroom teacher
who likes college women.
Waseda University is a consistently top-ranked university in Tokyo
Doesn't he seem like the Waseda-type?
The others are...
Loli...
Majime, meaing "serious" or "earnest"
Majime...
Yamai, meaning "sickness"
Yamai...
You're bored, aren't you?
I thought up of ones for you girls too.
Saginomiya, since your emotions
have gone extinct, you're "Robo".
Kikuchi, since you're a creepy otaku, you're "Ota".
What?! I am not creepy!
Aw! How nice it must be for you!
Only you girls have characteristics!
Next time you shout without warning, I'll hit you.
I want un... Ain't there somethin'?
That kinda characteristic or like 'em identity things...
And there she goes with some mysterious
first-person Kansai-dialect like character acting.
Super annoying...
Minor character.
Oh! Yeah, that's it! Like that stuff! Gimme more!
Head makes up half her body.
Home probably stinks.
Air pollution. Gorilla. Protein junkie.
Walking dissonance.
Hey...!
Family are nudists...
You're casually mixing in insults here and there!
What the hell is up with your insult sensor?
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
These ones I don't mind, but...
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
Don't want to
be called this
Air pollution
Protein junkie
House probably
stinks
There's no way I'd want
to be called these ones, usually.
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
DON'T MIND
Family are nudists
Head makes up
half her body
Minor character
Walking dissonance
Head makes up
half her body
Then...
"Head makes up half her body" it is.
Now then, this problem goes to...
Tanaka.
Picking me when you know that I can't answer it...
Not cool, Sensei.
Are you trying to ruin this lesson?
Hey, you learned this section in middle school.
What were you doing all three years of middle school?
I was killing time.
If I were to elaborate...
I was mainly killing pimples!
What?
Pimples...?
You're getting supplementary lessons
for a week starting today, all right...?
This girl...
Her rebellious attitude towards a teacher,
and her poise at not being rattled by
the murmur of the class means...
Don't                         mind
Family are nudists
Head makes up half her body
Minor character
This will be
Takanka's
nickname
She's no ordinary human...!
Hey, hey! Hey Loli!
L-Loli?!
Don't call me Loli!
Last week on Sunday, I saw you at Jasco.
Wha...?!
You were with your grandma at the food court, right?
It was like you had a totally different vibe
than when you're at school.
And you're like a total grandma's girl.
N-now she's coming at me with my weak points.
How despicable...!
Tanaka...
This jerk is my enemy after all...!
You bastard...
Someday I'm gonna crush you for sure...
If you're gonna crush something,
then keep it to just pimples, okay?
Pimples can scar, so don't crush them!
Don't ever do it again, got it? Head...!
Huh?
Head makes up half her body!
You know what, it's irritating to be called
"Head makes up half her body" to my face after all.
Especially when Loli says it to me.
Head makes
up half her body
Then, go with "Minor Character."
Head makes
up half her body
Minor character
Hey Loli!
Hurry up!
Sh-shut up, Minor Character!
Minor Character, did you do the homework?
What're you eating, Minor Character?
Well...
"Minor Character" also subtly
whittles away at me mentally...
Then...
Family are nudists
Go with "Family are nudists."
Oh!
Family Are Nudists!
Family Are Nudists, where do you live?
Dubai... that's in the US, right?
U-um... Family Are...
Miss Family Are Nudists.
Just what am I supposed to do about my nickname?!
Haven't you lost sight of your objective,
Family Are Nudists?
Don't call me Family Are Nudists!
It's no use.
I just don't get it.
What's that? What part don't you get?
Supplementary
Lessons
Day 3
Why...?
Why am I this unpopular with guys?
I don't get it!
What kind of problem are you trying to solve?
Huh? A life problem, maybe?
Right now, do the math problems.
You idiot.
Yeah, but...
Instead of trying to solve this pointless equation,
shouldn't I be solving why I'm not popular with guys?
In terms of my life, isn't that far more important?
What are you gonna do
if no guys take notice of me for the rest of my life?
Solve five problems within thirty minutes.
Do that and a man will come near you.
His way of getting me motivated is... half-assed!
Oh, by the way Sensei,
you said that you like college women,
but what is it about college women that you like?
That has nothing to do
with your current problems, you know?
It does.
If I don't get an answer, then it'll bug me
and I won't be able to concentrate.
Well, alright...
A kid  probably won't understand, but...
If I had to say...
The standard interview business suits
of the job-seeking students.
That's what.
Whoa!
Hey! Stop looking so disgusted.
Enough about me here.
Hurry up and do that worksheet, won't you?
Yeah, yeah...
Ugh! Waseda's tastes are so… wew!
Huh?
Oh, I solved it.
Is that so? See, you can do it if—
It's not that I wasn't popular with guys…
I just didn't realize that I actually was!
Will you give me back
my moment of pure hope, please?
During elementary and middle school,
they liked me but couldn't say anything...
Or maybe they were trying to appeal to me
and I just didn't realize it...
Oh, oh crap!
I can't leave it like this!
Hey! Where do you think you're going?!
Home!
I'm gonna try and hit up all the guys in my yearbooks!
Hold up!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
What's making you go that far?
Sensei.
I really want to be popular with guys.
Think about how your old classmates would feel
being interrogated out of the bl—
Oh! An armpit stain!
What? That can't be...!
Wide open!
Wha—
Stop, Tanaka!
Don't jump the gun!
Oh no…
What if all… all of the guys in my class liked me?
What am I gonna do?!
Come to think of it, I don't really want that anyway.
I want something more like a fateful encounter.
Like what?
Like reuniting with a childhood friend who had moved away a long time ago…
No way...
Nozomu?
K–Ken-chan?
Except you don't have any childhood friends.
Or like trying to reach for the same book
at the library I go to often...
Oh!
As if you ever go to libraries.
Or, a hot guy gets in a traffic accident,
and they need type AB− blood,
but there's not enough…
As fate would have it, I happen to pass by
with my type AB− blood and share it with him.
I save his life, and when he's feeling better, I go visit him…
It's strange...
but I don't feel like this is
the first time we've met.
Or so he says. Then…
I was visiting a friend when the nurse
came running up to me…
… it slips that it was me who saved his life,
and it makes him confess to me.
Too long.
Besides, you're not even a type AB.
You're definitely a type O.
Or, we keep bumping into each other
at the same place...
This has got to be fate or something, isn't it?
Then he confesses and…
And their soup portions pretty big.
You guys are just frequent customers.
A super popular star is shopping incognito…
… when he bumps into me and his identity is revealed…
Ow, that hurts...
Crap! She's gonna cause a scene!
What are you panicking
and hiding your face for?!
Or so he thinks, but it turns out
that I don't know him and...
What?! Have you got a face that'll get you in trouble?
You really don't know who I am?
Huh?!
I don't care. Hurry up and apologize!
You don't know me and yet you talk to me in that way...
You're an interesting woman.
… is basically what he says.
A street musician, who's in a bit of a slump
and has lost his confidence…
I can't bear to listen to this.
You've been out of tune for a while now.
Huh? That can't be right. I have absolute pit—
What's out of tune is...
the tuning of your heart.
What a critic.
And then...
Why?
I feel like I can write songs now.
You're...
an interesting woman.
Or so he says...
Again with that "interesting woman" thing?
At a three-star restaurant, I leave some leftovers
of a dish that the prideful chef prepared and...
You couldn't even make me eat a single green pea.
In the end, that's all that your skills amount to…
… little boy.
Damn it!
Here it comes...
What is up with that mademoiselle?!
Here it comes.
What an interesting woman.
You really like that.
What's up with that "interesting woman" phrase
that keeps coming up?
You're way too into it.
What's wrong with that?
The only way for a heroine
who gets made fun of to get a hot guy…
… is by taking the "interesting" route, you know.
She's just barely self-aware
that she's being made fun of.
Thank goodness!
Or...
There's more?
when a hot guy is feeding the pigeons at the park...
Whoa!
You...!
Y–You're eating germ-covered
bread crumbs off the ground…
Let me guess: she's an "interesting woman"?
That's disgusting.
Or so he says...
He's disgusted?
No, being disgusted is the correct response!
But...
I'm a very tolerant person,
but nobody else has managed to put me off this much.
What an interesting woman.
Damn it! In the end, it was still the "interesting woman" thing.
You've been on the receiving end
of all these confessions so far.
Don't you feel like putting in some effort?
Huh?!
Obviously not!
I kinda got told off.
Well...
Well, because I...
I want someone to fall in love with me…
… just as I am without me having to put in any effort at all.
You haven't changed at all in all these years.
Did too! I became a high school girl.
Ah, there's a good nickname for you.
What is it?
Interesting woman.
No.
Baka.
They
settled
on “Baka”
Huh?! What's up with that?!
Noisy and loud
Sawagashikute yakamashikute
But also endearing
Demo itoshikute
The laughter from that day
Ano hi no waraigoe
A story that can't be rewound
Maki modesenai story
The thing about youth is,
Seishun te yatsu wa
it's always light and shadows
zutto hikari to kage
Inside the darkness
Kurayami no naka
An inferior shining star
Kagayaku rettousei
Looking back is complicated
Furi kaereba kojiraseta
Far too beautiful days
Utsukushi sugiru hibi
Springtime has always passed by unexpectedly by then
Itsumo haru wa fui ni toori sugita ato
Your words reverberate in my heart
Kimi no kotoba mune ni reverb
Springtime will take it all away someday
Itsuka haru ga zenbu tsuresatte shimau
Until that day, being stupid is fine
Sono hi made wa baka de ii
Because I'll run past it
Kakenukeru kara
Hey, can I say something amazing right now?
You know, when someone says something like that,
their amazing thing usually isn't.
No, it's pretty amazing.
It's so amazing, it's like when
a chimpanzee takes a banana—
Hurry up and say it already.
You know...
aren't we...
at our peak right now?
No, it gets amazing from here. Okay?
Show a bit more interest in it, won't you?
If you look at us objectively,
our faces and fashion sense are low-mid tier.
On top of that, our personalities are rotten,
and we're in no way popular with guys, right?
Since we have no other redeeming traits,
our one weapon is…
Yes! It's our youth!
Then that means now's our only chance, right?
We're at our most powerful right now,
with us being high school girls as our weapon.
If we don't do our best now,
we may never be able to get boyfriends, right?
Well? That was pretty shocking, right?
Kinda stirs up your sense of danger, doesn't it?
Amazing...
Oh?
You seem amazingly stupid.
Ro...
Robo, what did you think?
I thought it was amazing.
Oh?
I thought it was amazing
that you'd overrate yourself at low-mid tier.
What...?
Uh...
Low?
High-low tier...?
Lowest of the low?!