So, look...
We're friends, right?
Huh? Yeah, of course.
Then it's okay if I say something
really amazing right now, right?
What does it matter?
Even if I say "No," you're going to anyway, right?
Sure enough...
I feel a sharp increase in flabbiness.
Y-you think so?
A sharp increase! The flesh has expanded.
I don't see much difference.
Hey, Robo. You think so too, right?
You sense a significant weight gain as well, don't you?
Those legs are elephantine.
I knew it!
And it's like there's a pair of cow's teats up front!
We're on the cusp of a new species of animal!
It's just too frightening!
Wh-what's with you?
It's nothing to get that worked up about, right?
You're just overthinking things.
What are eating to make you so fat, Wota?!
You're talking about ME?
Say...
I've tired of this, so can we stop
DERAILING the conversation?
Whoa, Robo said that?
But why?!
Yo
Mic check
JK
Eh?
Hai!
Soko wa futsuu one-two ga best?
Tsuki tte hiruma wa shizuka na beast
Tsuki ga nan datte? Ikinari toutotsu
Yoru ni natte kara kurayami magirete
Kirakira shichatte tereyasan
Ayakaritai lunatic girls
Sore binjou shitai no, kirakira JK
Genjyou shotchuu
Daradara OK~!
Atamannaka zenbu
Karappo ni dekita nara yuunou
Sou na no? You know?
Yasei no honnou (Nya~)
Seken ni hitokoto otome no otakebi
Wawawawawa~!
Zanshin shout
Wawawawawawawa~!
Tsuki tte usagi inai ndane
Dassu tte doitsugo nan dane
Karakute nakinagara curry ga tabetakunaru BGM!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Wa ni natte
Mic check JK one-two JK one-two
Nan datte OK everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Iki sutte
Shiisuu ramen gyudon tonkatsu kishimen
Nandemo tabetakunaru BGM
Kosei wa zettai dashioshimi shinai
Kusuburu honnou minna de wa! tto
Odorokashite sa, mada minu hou e
Muda demo let's go, itsushika treasure
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Nakitai toki wa
Omoikitte naite naite tsuukai
Soukai na kibun sa every day
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Hora sono ato wa
Iya demo kitto harete sou egao ni narusa
Wa! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
Second-year Class Assignments
(If you wish to change courses, please notify staff ASAP)
Robo
I, Kanade Ninomae, have done it!
I thought she might go the Science route...
But then I thought she might go with Liberal Arts
to stay with Tanaka-san and the others.
That's what I gambled on, and I hit the jackpot!
Liberal
Arts
Shiori Saginomiya
Akane Kikuchi
It's like a dream, Saginomiya-san!
To think, we'd be in the same class again
for our second year!
Huh? Dude, didn't turn in your request form?
Pending
Nozomu Tanaka
That's weird...
I'm sure I turned it in!
You mean this?
Request Form, 2nd-year Course Selection
Please circle your preferred course
Liberal Arts
Science
Other (Enter "Undecided," etc.)
"Dozing Off Course"
I'll ask just to make sure:
Do you understand what "career path" actually means?
Sensei!
The thing is, I can't be pigeonholed into some "group."
That's like being, you know, holier than fowl!
I think you mean, holier than thou.
I can't believe you got that.
You know, you've only ever gotten
single digits on your math tests, right?
Just circle Liberal Arts and turn your sheet in already.
Hey! I did get a double-digit score
the other day. It was a 10!
Don't try to act proud over getting a 10.
Have you just sullied the 10 points
I almost killed myself to earn?!
Yeah, sure, you're so amazing.
Even rotting your brains out with that "boy's love" stuff,
you're still able to score a whopping 50.
BL has nothing to do with this!
You sure get defensive when you
hear the word "BL," huh? Lame.
The hell, man?! Now you've pissed me off!
Just don't talk to me for a while.
Fine! Who'd wanna talk to you?!
Um...
Don't worry. This happens all the time.
But wouldn't it be better if someone intervened?
I know how this works.
There's a little trick to it.
Why is she harping on me like that?
Is she in heat or something?!
Now, now. Just calm down.
Here, have this.
Oh. Thank you.
Jeez!
Just 'cause she can do a little bit better than me,
it's like she looks down on me
and treats me like an idiot...
Dammit!
All right, I'll be passing down handouts.
Here!
Thanks.
Did you see that?
Wasn't that just totally inappropriate?!
Now, now.
Here. Why don't you sharpen this?
I swear, that fool is rotten to the core!
Her proclivities are rotten too!
Ooh, that was a good burn.
This pencil shaving...
it's like one long, unbroken string!
Robo.
I don't want to see that fool's face while I'm eating,
so I'm going to the cafeteria!
Um, do you mind if I join you?
Thank you!
The hell is her problem?!
Now, now. Calm down.
Would you mind threading this needle?
Suits me fine, not having to look at that ugly mug!
Color me happy!
Dammit! It totally won't go through!
Dammit, dammit, dammi-!
Now, now.
Huh?
Use this.
Once you've finished lunch,
would you mind balancing this evenly?
Huh?
And once it becomes balanced,
you can have that drink.
The truth is, I'm not even that angry anymore.
But it's not like I can back down now.
Wota!
Check it out!
I got it to balance evenly! That's awesome, huh?
Idiot. Give me the tweezers.
Huh?
The right side is a bit heavier, right?
There. Now it's balanced evenly.
What is this sight that I'm being shown?
That was awesome, Wota!
Hey, by any chance, are you a Libra?
What is this sight that I'm being shown?
That was awesome, Wota!
Hey, by any chance, are you a Libra?
Oh, my. That was faster than expected.
Nah, I'm a Pisces. And today's horoscope
said my lucky item is lactobacillus!
Oh, my. That was faster than expected.
Nah, I'm a Pisces. And today's horoscope
said my lucky item is lactobacillus!
And I had already readied my next stratagem...
Lactobacillus?! So that's why!
You mean, that "trick" you mentioned earlier?
Not lactobacillus bifidus, though.
When overwriting undesired information,
it is effective to introduce a new task
that produces feelings of pleasure...
Anger
Bubble Wrap
Pencil Shaving
Needle Threading
Bubble Wrap
Anger
Pencil Shaving
particularly for someone with
a limited brain capacity like Baka.
That sounds like you're really
making fun of Tanaka-san...
You are shortsighted.
She is... a legitimate idiot.
L-legitimate?!
Note: Using the same word as her nickname, "Majime"
I'm fine. You drink it.
No, no. You drink it!
Not at all. You drink it.
I won't hear of it. You drink it!
Oh! Robo, what is that? A game?
It's Othello.
You can have the black pieces. Put one here.
Then, vertically, horizontally, diagonally...
You can turn them all over.
Whoa! That looks like it'd be a lot of fun!
Hurry up and try it!
That felt wicked good!
Let's do all white next!
She was indeed "legitimate."
I'll line them up, so you go next, Wota!
So, like, when I was in elementary school...
I wanted to try bringing dried sardines back to life,
so I put them in a fish tank overnight.
"Robo-san."
I still don't know her real name.
so I put them in a fish tank overnight.
You are just unrepentantly stupid, aren't you?
All I know is, that's what her friends call her.
It must suck to be you.
Huh? Wota, you've never tried that before?
Her friend, "Baka-san," simply talks a lot...
Why would I do something so idiotic?
All things considered,
she's like a pastry with nothing inside.
Why would I do something so idiotic?
All things considered,
she's like a pastry with nothing inside.
So, the next day, I checked the fish tank all excited,
but they were still all dried up.
"Wota-san" is bright-eyed
and always has a witty comeback...
The only thing I got out of it was some good fish stock.
"Wota-san" is bright-eyed
and always has a witty comeback...
Well, they were sardines, after all.
She's like some bird of prey.
I don't doubt you got some good stock.
Still, it was such a shock at the time
I assume they gave each other their nicknames,
but those are some rather bold
and straightforward names.
that it felt like I was in a dream!
but those are some rather bold
and straightforward names.
You know what would be more shocking?
Putting dried sardines in a tank
and they do come back to life.
Robo-san is...
Putting dried sardines in a tank
and they do come back to life.
She's as lovely as the bright blue Nemophila!
It's as if when she boards this train,
it becomes a field of Nemophila, a wave of azure!
Hey, whatcha eat last night?
We had yaki udon at my place.
Uh, we had katsu don over at ours, I think.
Nice! A big, fat katsu don!
Cut it out with the "big" and "fat."
How about you, Robo?
I imagine Robo-san had salmon
with a spinach cream pasta!
Idle grass.
Note: Echoing "Essays in Idleness,"
a work by the Buddhist monk Kenko
When asked what she ate last night,
she responds not with what she ate,
but with the title of the book she read!
How stately! You are so wonderful, Robo-san!
We sat in the yard and idly ate grass.
Again?! Your family always does that
just before payday, huh?
They live in that big house, but it's a mystery
whether they're rich or poor, isn't it?
Okay! Next, let's tell each other
what we want the most!
I want a 4th dimensional pocket!
What about you, Wota?
Note: A nod to Doraemon
Talent.
That's not an object.
What's the difference?
What you want only exists in the world
where there's cat-shaped robots!
And Robo-san? Don't tell me she wants a boyfriend!
What you want only exists in the world
where there's cat-shaped robots!
And you, Robo?
A bo...
A body of samples for anti-aging
DNA manipulation experiments.
Robo, I think you're going to get
arrested one of these days.
I would not make such a blunder.
I see...
I was born so that I could be a sample
for one of her experiments!
Well, see ya!
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Chikuwa Bookstore
I've made up my mind.
I was fine with just looking,
but if I could actually get to speak with you...
If our eyes could meet as we engaged in talk...
How brightly this world would shine!
U-um...!
Just calm down.
I've run through this simulation so many times.
And I have an ace up my sleeve.
That which is needed for a man and woman
who don't know each other to get acquainted...
Why is my Friend's House
Yes: Points in common!
Wh-where did you buy that book?
Uh, for... For a while now I've thought,
"That sure looks interesting!"
I've looked around for it
but I haven't been able to find it.
These days you can just buy things online,
so maybe this was a bit of a stretch...
The Chikuwa Bookstore
at the station's north entrance.
If you're that interested in it, I will give it to you.
Sh-she's talking to me!
It would seem the household of
a friend of yours is faced with difficulty.
She's really talking to me right now!
Why is my Friend's House
Slightly Smelly?
True enough, Sasaki kept five hamsters at home,
and Aoyama's house, where you had to pass
through the veranda to get to the bath...
both of these were slightly smelly.
Once I've found my own answer
to this philosophical dilemma,
I will try speaking to you again.
I swear... How bright the setting sun is!
GRAAARGH!
Hmph!
Bzzzt
C'mon, Robo. I said I'm sorry!!
This cannot be solved by a simple apology.
Let's get along
Though it may be hard for me to show it,
even I can get hurt.
Now Saginomiya-san and Tanaka-san are fighting?
S..Saginomiya-san!
P-please wait!
What the heck's going on?
I-It's sort of unusual for you two to be fighting.
Saginomiya-san, what happened?
You're always so calm,
so for you to worked up like this...
Yeah, Robo doesn't get angry that often.
She and I don't really get into fights.
But...
Yes. There may have been one time, long ago.
J-just tell me already!
I can't stand that look you've got on your face!
Please, you can confide in me.
If that will make you feel even a little better, that is.
The thing is, Robo, Wota, and I
went to the same elementary school...
Let's play Cops and Robbers!
I'll be the cop, and Kikuchi and Saginomiya
will be the robbers, okay?!
Come on! Again?!
We always played together after school,
but Robo ended up going to
a prep school in the next town over.
She may not look it, but she's super smart.
Then, when Wota and I went to different classes,
we just fell out of touch.
We all led our own lives in middle school...
but we ran into each other
during the summer of our third year,
and we started hanging out again.
By that time, Wota and I had
already decided to go to Saijo. Then...
I will go to Saijo too.
Huh? But you could get into
a much better school, right?
I have made my decision.
What the hell are you thinking?!
Don't throw your life away!
Do not presume to decide my life for me.
That was the first time I'd seen Robo get emotional.
I heard later that she was
pretty much alone at school.
Like, people couldn't tell what she was thinking,
so they just avoided her.
You need to figure out why she chose Saijo.
But then, Wota stopped talking to me too.
We all went our separate ways again.
S-so that's what happened?
That's why I was so happy
when the three of us met again in high school.
1st-year Class Lists
We're in the same class?!
You're right.
Not to mention, we're in the same grade.
Well of course that's obvious.
Oh, my! What a wonderful story.
So, what caused the fight this time?
The thing is...
After school yesterday, I kinda killed Robo's pet.
That's way too flippant!
Yeah, I kinda messed up!
That's just unacceptable!
I wouldn't be surprised if she hates you for life!
What? But, you get where I'm going, right?
When I say "pet," it's the
microorganisms that Robo cultivates.
Microorganisms?
Hey, hey! Robo!
That new comic "Shakure-zamurai"
is super entertaining, so you should read it!
New serial
Shakure-zamurai
Oh...!
So, I accidentally smashed it!
I kinda feel like I've wasted my time listening to this...
Oh! Robo!
You came back?!
Shakure-zamurai was quite entertaining,
so I will forgive you.
Wasn't it?! I'm looking forward to the next installment!
So, that's what happened.
If it had been me, would I have been able to say
she shouldn't throw her life away?
I'm ashamed of myself for simply being happy
at the grade-level advancement list...
There's no end of worry for a girl in love, huh?
What I have for Saginomiya-san is respect,
which isn't the same as romantic feelings.
You don't have to try to make it
black and white, you know.
A person's feelings are vague
and can fall into, like, gray areas.
You seem like you have some experience with this...
Because I do have experience.
I've heard a lot of your personal concerns...
Are you sure you're okay not swearing me to secrecy?
I might accidentally tell someone, you know.
I don't think you'd say anything, Someya-san...
Y-you don't know that.
But it's what I want to believe.
A classmate I can share my concerns with...
Someya-san, you may be the first one for me.
Is this what people refer to as "best friends"?
This! THIS is why you bug me!
What the hell?! You've got too much potential for this!
Is this because I went said we might be best friends?
I'm sorry for any bother-
There! That face!
You really stir up feminine instincts, you know!
The fact you do it without realizing makes it even
more wicked! Five years in prison for you!
I-I'm sorry...
See? There's that expression again!
Sorry to have you come all the way out here with me...
It's fine, Takahashi. Do you best out there.
I'll see you at school tomorrow, okay?
Yeah...
Today, I will definitely get closer to Robo-san.
And if things go well, to us being in a relationship...
I will watch from here and witness your brave stand.
After all, I'm your best friend.
So then, that convenience store employee-
Robo-san!
D-do you remember me?
A guy?!
You lent me this book a while back.
Yes, I remember you.
Do you have a moment?
I wanted to talk to you.
Yes, if it will not take long.
W-well then, we'll just be going now...
What for?! Let's hear what he has to say!
Read between the lines, you idiot!
No! I wanna break this apart!
I'm not gonna let you get the jump on us, Robo!
Get all complicated!
I-I'm sorry. It looks like you were out with your friends...
May all your front teeth suddenly fall out!
May you bite the inside of your cheek
I don't mind. So, what did you want to talk about?
and it gets all throbby!
Your left and your right cheeks!
Um... Th-that is...
Me... Me and...
I can't. When push comes to shove,
I don't have the courage to...
"Me and"?
Y-yeah. Me and...
Me and...
Me and this guy, his name is Aoyama.
We really get along, you see.
He's been my friend since middle school,
and he's a really good guy.
But, the thing is, his house is slightly smelly.
Huh? Wait, me?!
I was wondering why, and when I thought about it,
I came up with about 10 reasons...
Wh-what the hell am I talking about?
She couldn't possibly be interested in listening to this-
Why don't you tell me about it?
I can't believe it. She's interested in this?
The thing is, his house faces north,
and it's got bad ventilation.
Plus, there's damp, half-dried laundry
constantly in the room.
The garbage in the kitchen is in
a constant state of neglect.
Also, the shoe cabinet at the front door
is stuffed with old, worn-out shoes.
So, that more than meets the necessary definition.
Yes! The thing is, I thought about why people
perceive odors like that as being "smelly."
It's the perception of danger, born from instinct.
Yes! It's an intrinsic function,
for the purpose of avoiding dangerous things.
When I think of that, I'm left with one hypothesis:
The smell from Aoyama's house might mean that
I'm rejecting Aoyama on a genetic level!
So, I'm being genetically rejected?
This could also be the case when seen
from a philosophical viewpoint.
Does the smell at Aoyama's house
even actually exist? In other words...
Aoyama's house may not even actually be smelly.
It could be that the aversion I feel toward Aoyama
is just making me perceive it that way.
He straight-up said "aversion"!
And what is that aversion?
Aoyama has a childhood friend, a girl,
and they really get along well.
There might've been a part of me that was jealous,
because he could go in and out of
a girl's room like it was nothing.
Actually, I'm sure of it!
I see now...
The book you gave me helped me to identify
the negative feelings I've had.
Thank you. Today was about me
wanting to show you my gratitude, so...
Hey! Why do we have to
take the time to be considerate?
Still, if she gets a boyfriend,
he might introduce us to his guy friends!
You... You are smart.
If you can get this jealous,
you must like your friend very much.
Aoyama is my number one best friend...
Robo!
H-hey!
I've come to cheer you on!
Takahashi!
I like you a lot too, Takahashi!
Takahashi! Takahashi!
I like you!
I'll lend this to you.
It's an odor meter, "Smell Sensor-kun."
I made it to measure a wet dog's odor index,
but it seems like the situation between you two
is more dire, so please use it.
You can return it after the facts regarding
your friend's house have been clarified.
I shall be waiting.
Hey, Robo! Wait!
Never mind our almost smothering friendship,
Hey, wait!
the odor meter, and the slight awkwardness, she left...
Aw!
What happened to the plan to have him
introduce us to some guys?
By the way, did you actually like that Takahashi dude?
Well...
If such represents the elation of having found
a candidate for the purpose of
anti-aging DNA manipulation, then yes.
Yasaka Station
Oh!
Teishotoku P has uploaded a new song!
It's that Vocalo P you've been
nuts about from before, right?
He's still pretty unknown,
but he must be an awesome guy. I like-
To say that you "like" him,
when you haven't even met him is just, "Ewe!"
Shut up! You can get a feel
just by listening to his songs!
If you met him in person, what would you do?
Well, I'd say that I like him, of course!
Eew!
The afternoon song shines, in the corner of the room
Secret•Sequence
Teishotoku P here. This is my fifth release.
I made this when I was gazing at sushi that just passed me by...
Teishotoku-P-san
Views
# of comments
# in my list
My numbers aren't going up...
All I do is wait, hoping for the revolution to begin
There was a time I thought
that if I became a famous producer,
I'd be able to go out with college women.
I have to hurry and come up with an answer
I'm here today again
You do make nice songs
This song really permeates
No way!
There's no way such a sweet deal could be real!
Though I don't know the reason why I should hurry
At the very least, I'm surrounded by high school girls.
But, no way! I'm glad I don't have one!
I'm free! I don't have to spend money on them!
Regrets, I repeat them and cry
I'm glad I don't have a girlfriend! It's awesome!
But I mourn the fact that I can't change
Soft
It's nice
I want the album
It's lovely
I should get some sleep...
The same class? Together? Let's see...
Second-year Class Assignments
(If you wish to change courses, please notify staff ASAP)
Shiori Saginomiya
Liberal
Arts
Akane Kikuchi
Nozomu Tanaka
Pending
Sawagashikute yakamashikute
Demo itoshikute
Ano hi no warai koe
Maki modesenai story
Seishun te yatsu wa zutto hikari to kage
Kurayami no naka
Kagayaku rettousei
Furi kaereba kojiraseta
Utsukushi sugiru hibi
Itsumo haru wa fui ni toori sugita ato
Kimi no kotoba mune ni reverb
Itsuka haru ga zenbu tsure satte shimau
Sono hi made wa baka de ii
Kake nukeru kara
Yamamoto, you know I said I'd be
collecting notebooks after the test.
The only ones who haven't turned them in
are you and Tanaka!
You can look away all you want,
but that won't make it go away!
Yo! Last night was the night before the test!
So, together, come on, say what?
I went to my usual noodle shop.
And what I ate there was tsukemen, yeah!
The store owner's like, "How's today's noodles?"
Took only a sec to fire back with:
"Barikata."
That's "firm" to you, y'all. Oh!
What's gotten into you this time, Yamamoto?
Men men me-me-men! Men me-men!
Note: MEN means "Noodles"
Yamamoto. I am asking about your notebook.
Men men me-me-men! Men me-men!
Men men me-men! Me-me-me-me-me-men!
Men men me-men...
Yamamoto!
I forgot my backpack at the ramen shop.
I've caused a lot of trouble for my parents. Seriously.
So then, it was in your bag,
which you left behind at the ramen yesterday?
Why didn't you just say so?
Also, if you sang that chorus again,
I would have used a pressure point to immobilize you.
Wait! Please, just let me just say this!
Sorry, for real!