I like it
No matter how many decades I may live...
It's a really great song
Sure is nice...
You're low-income?
Teishotoku P
Ryusei Meteeshika  -  38,000 views
This is my first upload. Both my name and my present situation are "Low Income."
Nice...
Awesome
Love it
Teishotoku P
Ryusei Meteeshika  -  38,000 views
This is my first upload. Both my name and my present situation are "Low Income."
I wanna go to a paradise of good-looking guys too!!!
Stop having weird fantasies and just go to bed.
I'm going to sleep. Good night.
Tanaka:  Hey, can I say something amazing?
Stop having weird fantasies and just go to bed.
I'm going to sleep. Good night.
Tanaka:  Hey, can I say something amazing?
When you mention summer
I'm going to sleep. Good night.
Tanaka:  Hey, can I say something amazing?
When you mention summer
That means scary stories, right?
My true feelings...
I've sealed them up and put them to sleep
Tanaka:  Hey, can I say something amazing?
When you mention summer
That means scary stories, right?
This one is super scary, though.
I don't want to let anyone touch my passion, so...
That means scary stories, right?
This one is super scary, though.
In the park behind my house, there's this one cat
straight outta
You better not say "PURRgatory"
In the park behind my house, there's this one cat
straight outta
You better not say "PURRgatory"
PURRgatory
Hey, don't beat me to the punchline.
What's scary is Baka's brain,
for having thought that was funny.
Hey, don't beat me to the punchline.
What's scary is Baka's brain,
for having thought that was funny.
Wait, no.
This is where it really gets scary.
I used to have a pet turtle
and it was so
You better not say it walked ac-CURSE-dly slow.
I used to have a pet turtle
and it was so
You better not say it walked ac-CURSE-dly slow.
I used to have a pet turtle
and it was so
You better not say it walked ac-CURSE-dly slow.
ac-CURSE-dly slow.
Scratch that.
This is where the amazing stuff starts.
Listen up.
Whoa!
Nice
This song is great
Gave me goosebumps
You gotta reach higher
A hazy room, illuminated by moonlight
Yo
Mic check
JK
Eh?
Hai!
Soko wa futsuu one-two ga best?
Tsuki tte hiruma wa shizuka na beast
Tsuki ga nan datte? Ikinari toutotsu
Yoru ni natte kara kurayami magirete
Kirakira shichatte tereyasan
Ayakaritai lunatic girls
Sore binjou shitai no, kirakira JK
Genjyou shotchuu
Daradara OK~!
Atamannaka zenbu
Karappo ni dekita nara yuunou
Sou na no? You know?
Yasei no honnou (Nya~)
Seken ni hitokoto otome no otakebi
Wawawawawa~!
Zanshin shout
Wawawawawawawa~!
Tsuki tte usagi inai ndane
Dassu tte doitsugo nan dane
Karakute nakinagara curry ga tabetakunaru BGM!
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Wa ni natte
Mic check JK one-two JK one-two
Nan datte OK everyday
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Iki sutte
Shiisuu ramen gyudon tonkatsu kishimen
Nandemo tabetakunaru BGM
Kosei wa zettai dashioshimi shinai
Kusuburu honnou minna de wa! tto
Odorokashite sa, mada minu hou e
Muda demo let's go, itsushika treasure
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Nakitai toki wa
Omoikitte naite naite tsuukai
Soukai na kibun sa every day
U~wa! Moon! Dass! Cry!
Hora sono ato wa
Iya demo kitto harete sou egao ni narusa
Wa! Moon! Dass! Cry! Every day
Buying Swimwear
Hey, so... We're like, really indulging
right now, don't you think?
Free soda refills at a casual restaurant is indulging?
Well, I mean, we'll only get one
summer vacation as 16-year-olds, right?
But we're wasting it by doing stuff
like blowing liquid onto straw wrappers,
Note: Mushoku means unemployed
reading reference books on barnacles,
and listening to Mushoku Pu songs!
You mean "Teishotoku P," and it's not a waste of time.
Reference books on barnacles
are also not a waste of one's life.
I mean, still! Summer makes you want to
go to the beach or something, right?
Also, doesn't it make you want to
get into a red-hot summer fling?
I'd say that, out of all the high school girls in Japan,
you have the least business
talking about a "red-hot summer fling."
But I would like to go to the beach.
I know, right, Robo?!
There would be barnacles there.
That's your...?
What other reason would there be?
Regardless of our "upper-lower" ranking, we're
16-year-old high school girls, and we're at our peak!
Armed with the right swimwear,
we'd be unstoppable, right?!
Higashi-Murayama does not have an ocean.
Still, it's just a short train ride to
Enoshima or Kujukuri Beach.
Heck, maybe we could go overseas!
Overseas? That's a bit of a stretch.
I mean, well, I've heard Japanese girls
get a lot of attention when they go overseas.
We should go to Hawaii, or maybe Dubai!
And how will this be paid for?
Don't we have some rich girl in our class
who owns a guest house or something?
That sort of thing only happens
in anime or manga! Not in real life!
And if there were someone like that,
they wouldn't be at Saijo!
Ah! I've got it!
We could do a raffle! Like the kind they
always have in anime and manga!
You know, where someone plays and
they luck out and grab the special prize!
Try Your Paw at our MEOWvelous Raffle
2nd Prize: LCD TV
Trip to Gero Hot Springs
Voucher for 3 days/2 nights (Pair)
1st Prize - Electric Bike
Who'd want to go to a hot spring
when it's already this hot outside?!
But if you won, you could
sell it for a profit on Mericar.
Even if the special prize doesn't pan out,
the first-prize electric bike
or even the second-prize LCD TV
could be sold for money.
Robo, you're a genius!
Try Your Paw at our MEOWvelous Raffle
Free Raffle Ticket for Every 3,000-yen Purchase
1st Prize: Electric Bike
Special Prize: Hot Springs Trip
But how do we get a ticket?
Every 3,000-yen Purchase
I say we just buy something!
If we're gonna go to the beach,
we should get some new swimwear, right?
The timing is perfect!
Wota, Robo, you buy something too.
Well... I don't know about buying something,
but while we're here, we should at least
try something on, right?
Well? What do you think?
Average, I guess. But you know, Wota...
You've got a pretty rockin' bod for an otaku.
D-don't say stuff like "rockin' bod"!
Your verdict?
Where did you find that?
And who the hell is the target audience?!
Sure enough, I'm goin' with this one!
Don't do it, Baka! It's too dangerous!
If you put that on, it will crush
the psyche of anyone who sees it!
What the hell?! Let go! I could try it on at least once!
Okay, let's do this! We all get one try - and I'm first!
Please Enjoy the Taste of
Pure, Ultra-filtered Water.
Straight from the Water Treatment Plant
Two-hour, All-You-Can-Drink Ticket
Please Enjoy the Taste of
Pure, Ultra-filtered Water.
Straight from the Water Treatment Plant
Two-hour, All-You-Can-Drink Ticket
Are they screwing with us?
The piggy bank?! We want the goods!
I was able to sell it on Mericar for 30 yen.
Considering the train fare to JUSCO
and what we spent on our bikinis,
couldn't we have just gone to the pool
at Hokuhoku-Seibuen Amusement Park?
Don't start.
As we have already purchased said swimwear,
rather than going overseas,
why don't we simply go to the beach?
There will be barnacles there.
Robo, what's with this recent fetish
you've had for barnacles?
I occurred to me I would like to confirm
the urban legend regarding barnacles.
"Urban legend"?
Wait, d-do you mean...?!
Yes.
A girl tripped in a rocky area
and landed on her breasts.
At the time, there was nothing out of the ordinary...
Ow!
But the next time she changed into her swimwear...
a crunching sound emanated from her chest area.
Th-this is the one where she's got barnacles
all up on her boobs, right?
No. And barnacles are not parasitic toward humans.
Instead, the barnacles had infested
the breast pads of her bikini.
Either way, that's scary as hell!
This urban legend is not "scary."
Barnacles are a highly regarded food item.
The young girl took the hint,
and was able to take those
breast-pad barnacles and cultivate them.
As urban legends go, it is a success story.
"Success"?
Sell me those!
Nurtured on my Boobs
I'll take 100 of them!
You're a genius!
We can raise our own boob-pad barnacles
and rake in the profits!
Barnacle Swimwear
I Raised These
Bred Off My Own Boobs
You really did it...
Well, Robo helped out.
This will make me a high school entrepreneur!
And my company name will be "The Barnacles, Inc."
That's not very inventive.
Is something wrong?
I barely put it up three minutes ago,
but it got reported and deleted. But, why?!
What's wrong with barnacles?
Is it because they're alive?!
It must be the "bikini" angle.
The whole thing reeks of something suspicious.
Well, they're barnacles
so of course they'll smell "fishy,"
but they shouldn't come across
as suspicious, right?!
I was just thinking I hadn't seen you at school recently,
but sure enough, you're just as moronic as ever.
Lily! Perfect timing.
Do you happen to have a guest house in Dubai?
I own no such thing.
And why Dubai?
I'm striking out with guys here in Japan, but I think
I'd be hot stuff at some luxury resort in Dubai.
If you're unpopular in Japan, I can guarantee
you'd be equally unpopular in Dubai.
Fine, then tell me how to get the guys!
Whether it's at some beach in Japan,
the pool at Hokuhoku-Seibuen Park,
or even the banks of the Karabori River!
There are several techniques for attracting men, but...
Well, I think even you, Tanaka-san,
can employ the basic of basics.
By which I mean, THAT.
Which "that" is that?!
You know, the "Five-S" strategy of any popular girl.
"Five-S"?
Ah, I've heard of that.
It's the order that popular girls
season food when they're cooking, right?
Sugar, salt, sushi vinegar, soy sauce, and miSo.
No, the other Five-S approach.
You mean, what you say
at singles' parties to get the guys?
Oh, I know that one! It was on TV the other day.
Go on and say them then.
"Sashimi for dinner?"
"Shika rice crackers for a snack?"
"Sushi rice sound good?"
"Spot me 1,000 yen, will you?"
Yup, that's it!
No way could there be a Five-S approach like that.
Why not?! They all start with "S," right?!
You could never combat the Dark Soul
with that sort of S!
Uh, this has nothing to do with Dark Soul.
We're talking about the Five-S method
of being popular with guys at singles' mixers.
"Mixers," you say?
I have no interest in such wicked gatherings,
but I know of the Fivefold S:
The Salamander, defeated at my hands!
The Signatures of the dead I count as allies!
The Stigma I must bear!
The Sounds of a world as it falls to ruin.
And... Stuff!
The last one was just "Stuff"? Really?
If the setting is a girl who is popular at a research
laboratory, I also know a Five-S approach.
Enough already!
Wait! I really want to hear this one!
Fine, go ahead. What's the first S?
"So, want to culture some bacteria?"
Okay, got it. That's enough.
No, I need to hear this to the end!
Y'know, it just hit me...
Our school has a pool up on the roof, right?
Why don't we ever use it for class?
It's cursed.
The Curse of Saijo
Introduction
Many years ago, a member of the Ping-Pong Club
died an ignominious death just before a swim meet.
After that, pool-related accidents regularly occurred,
until Saijo finally closed it down altogether.
Wait, why a member of the Ping-Pong Club?!
I'd understand if it was a Swim Club member, but this...
That is the most frightening and
mystery-laden part of this story.
Come to think of it, Saijo has had those stories
about Seven Spooky Things for a while, huh?
Like, the Anatomical Model in the Science Room,
or the Bach of the Music Room.
Oh, and The Running Nino-esque Guys, right?
Who the heck is "Nino"?
Kinjiro.
Note: Urban legend states that statues of 19th-century leader
Kinjiro Ninomiya will move at night
But you'll only find Kinjiro up through
elementary school, right?
You're not likely to see a Kinjiro at high school.
That's what makes it scary - a Nino shows up
when he's not even supposed to be there!
And they travel in packs!
Also, there's Hanamaru-san of the Toilet, right?
There is?
If you go to the girls' toilet on the second floor and
knock on the door of the second-to-last stall
and call out, "Hanamaru-san!"
a voice will respond, "I'm Shibasaki."
Hanamaru-san! Hanamaru-san! Hanamaru-san!
And if you just keep repeating saying
"Hanamaru-san," then...
Note: Hana is "Nose" and Maru is "Round"
Your nose will turn round!
And it will never go back to normal!
The heck?
Yasaka Station
It got late, while I was out having fun...
Huh?
Boo!
What's wrong, Loli-chan?
Oh, it's you, Lily...
If you're loitering about at this time of hour,
you'll get taken away by some scary man, you know?
Oh! A scary man...?
Scary men
Go away!
What?
Oh! N-not you! I didn't mean you, Lily...
Huh?
A-anyway, it's not like I'm
loitering about for fun, you know...
I forgot my smartphone at school,
so I'm heading there to get it!
Huh, so that's it.
Oh! By any chance, are you
afraid of the school at night?
I-I'm so not scared!
P-plus, Grandma said that ghosts
don't appear in front of good kids!
Loli-chan, you're cute...
Don't say I'm cute!
Don't get so angry... I'll tag along with you, so.
R-r-really?!
Ah! This kinda situation is nice too...!
Wh-what? You're trembling? Lily, are you afraid too?
It's nothing.
I'm just trembling because it feels way too good...
Huh?! What feels so good?
This is the second-floor women's restroom...
It was Hanamaru-san of the toilet, right?
Don't worry. That's nothing but an urban legend.
B-but, there was a noise from inside just now...
Oh! Th-there seems to be someone there...
D-don't!
It's not my fault if you get cursed by Hanamaru-san
and have your nose become knobby!
The second door from the back... I knew it!
Hanamaru-san!
Stop!
You've mistaken!
This is Kanade Ninomae! Please help me!
Say what?!
Thank you very much...
It appears that the lock broke, and for a moment there,
I didn't know what would become of me...
Were you stuck in there since lunchtime?
Yes. I tried calling out for help several times,
but everyone just kept getting scared
and would run away, so...
Well, once you uncover the truth of something like
the Seven Wonders, it's pretty much nothing.
After all, in reality, there are
no such things like spirits and ghosts.
Pablo Diego...
Then, what is this?! What is it?! What is this?!
José Francisco de Paula Juan Nepomuceno...
María de los Remedios...
E-even if it's a ghost, if it's a cute girl, then...!
Cipriano de la Santísima...
Trinidad Ruiz y Picasso ....
Uh... Majo?
What's going on, everyone, at this late time of night...?
Actually, that would be our line, you know.
Majo, what about you? What're you doing at this hour?
Just a little necromancy...
There was a section in world history for the
summer break homework that I didn't understand,
so I was going to evoke the spirit of
Vasco da Gama and ask him for the answer.
Oh, is that so? I feel relieved.
No! I don't feel relieved, you know!
That's scary in general!
What's wrong?
I feel an intense set of eyes or
something on me, from the classroom...
What?! Wh-what do you mean, a set of eyes?!
Wh-why, there's no one here after all.
Huh?! Kanade?!
You weren't able to get down again, right...?
W-welcome to the prelude of darkness...
I found it!
I'm glad, Loli-chan.
Well then, shall we head home?
Oh, I still need to...
There's something I want to ask
Amenhotep IV as well, so...
Isn't it better if you do things like that at home?
Wh-what was that noise?
I can hear it... The symphony of doom...
Do you think it's poltergeist rapping?
It appears the sound is coming from the rooftop pool.
Let's go check it out!
W-we're going?!
Th-th-they're playing table tennis!
This is, after all, the curse of the table tennis club!
Actually...
Hey! What the hell are you bastards doing?!
Well, we were thinking of helping the ghost of the
table tennis club member rest in peace, you see!
And will she? Rest in peace, that is...
We already made sure to get
permission from Waseda,
and once we finish playing table tennis,
we were thinking of playing in the nighttime pool.
You guys wanna joins us too?
Even though you've offered,
we didn't bring our swimwear, so...
Huh?! What the?!
What's with this, all of a sudden...?
It's the act of God!
In order to purify this corrupted world,
a holy rain was...!
Speaking of, you're all gonna
catch colds if you stay wet like that.
How about you take those off and dry them out?
While things are being dried out,
let's all go swimming.
Well, as I explained, we don't have swimwear-
You and swimwear! You're way too picky!
If you're a woman, then show enough guts to
be able to go so far as to swim stark-naked!
No, she likes getting wet with her clothes on...
The texture of her clothes,
tightly clinging to her bare skin...
To the feeling of the drops trickling down from
her skirt as they slowly flow down her thighs...
Instinctively, she becomes...
Enraptured...
Hey! Please don't do whatever you want
and make up some fantasy!
Hey! I found some brand-new swimwear!
What?!
What's all this?
Are they samples or something?
Did a teacher forget and
leave them behind in the locker room?
Oh!
Hey, it's here! Maybe I should change into this!
Don't!
Speaking of, why is that kinda swimwear at a school?
Then Loli, wanna wear it?
Wha...?! Wh-who, me?!
I also have another one I brought...
S..Saginomiya-san, you'd lend me your swimwear?!
As an apology, for having made up
a weird fantasy earlier.
Oh! B-by any chance, is it for barnacles?!
Are you trying to farm barnacles
with my breasts, Saginomiya-san...?
No, that's fine too!
If it's for your sake, Saginomiya-san, then why not?
I will happily offer my body as
an experimental subject.
Thank you very much!
So cute!
Loli-chan, something like this
would be perfect for you, you know?!
And this one would probably suit you well, Kujyo-san!
Oh! This is definitely made for you, Yamamoto-san!
I-I'm supposed to wear one too?
Th-that kinda stuff I don't really...
Come on. It's fine.
All right, get undressed. I'll help you.
Yamai, you surprisingly have a nice body!
Majo's not bad too.
Please don't look at me too much. It's embarrassing.
Loli-chan, you too. Don't hide in that corner
while you're changing. Come over here.
D-don't worry about me!
Kanade, you too. Come on, will you
come over here and unhook my bra?
P-please do something like that by yourself!
Whoa! Majime! You've got some nice tits there!
Hey! I would ask you not to touch them.
Aw, come on! Just a little.
Wota, let me squeeze yours too. Yeah!
What?! Don't squeeze my butt!
Aiight! Everyone's changed, right?!
Then, let's go!
Woo-hoo!
Please wait! First off, we have to do warm-ups!
Come on. It's fine.
We can do without the formalities!
Venti soy milk no water ristretto shot-
What incantation is it this time?
So that everyone will not get into a water accident...
Just a little prayer...
Whatcha doing?! You guys hurry up and come in!
What the hell was that for?!
Now then, Majo, you too...
Yes...
Yo! Hey Loli! Come on...!
Loli... It's fine, get on...
Fly! Make me fly!
Hey! Amazing doesn't even start to describe it!
Hey look, Robo! There are barnacles here!
Why, these are barnacles!
Live!
If you fall, you'll die, Yamai!
Aw! It's supplementary lessons by myself,
the day after a school day...
Last night sure was fun! The nighttime pool...
I did bring my swimwear again today,
so maybe I'll go swim by myself
before the supplementary lessons.
What?!
What does this mean...?
Then...
What was all that yesterday...?
What in the world...
Was that nighttime pool thing about...?
...and that, is the amazingly scary story
I thought up. Well?
Amazing!
Love this
Gave me goosebumps
A truly good song
You're low-income?
It sure is nice...
Teishotoku P
Shooting Star Meteeshika  -  38,000 views
This is a new work. My name and present situation are both low-income.
I created everything by music programming.
For a little me that made a wish...
I don't have the strength to find the answer...
What in the world...
Was that nighttime pool thing about...?
...and that, is the amazingly scary story
I thought up. Well?
Actually, that's a common punch line, you know.
...and that, is the amazingly scary story
I thought up. Well?
Actually, that's a common punch line, you know.
Tanaka:  Aw! Robo, what about you?
It was amazingly scary, right?
I thought it was scary.
That Baka's breasts were twice as big than reality.
That part?!
Also, the barnacles.
Sawagashikute yakamashikute
Demo itoshikute
Ano hi no warai koe
Maki modesenai story
Seishun te yatsu wa zutto hikari to kage
Kurayami no naka
Kagayaku rettousei
Furi kaereba kojiraseta
Utsukushi sugiru hibi
Itsumo haru wa fui ni toori sugita ato
Kimi no kotoba mune ni reverb
Itsuka haru ga zenbu tsure satte shimau
Sono hi made wa baka de ii
Kake nukeru kara
Nothing beats the job-seeking students'
standard interview business suits, after all...